Previously, on "Suits"...
Where have you been?
I've been looking for you
all morning.
Okay, if you must know,
I overslept.
- I'd love to go out again.
- Is tonight too soon?
Let me check my calendar--
Yep, I'm free.
You will not determine
the type of lawyer
I want to be.
- What's that supposed to mean?
It means I'm willing
to say I owe you one.
So make an enemy of me...
or not.
That's the best
you're going to get.
I never sent
the documents over.
- Are you shitting me?
- It's my fault.
- I'll take the bullet.
- They're not gonna
give a shit
whose fault this is.
- You must be out of your mind.
- Scottie I'm in trouble here.
- I need you to help me.
- I'm sorry, Harvey,
but I've said yes
to you to many times.
A year after I stopped
with my therapist,
I started seeing her.
- I'm guessing
it didn't work out.
- It was complicated.
Did Donna have anything
to do with that complication?
Still drinking sidewalk
coffee, I see.
That's because
it's the best in the city.
I don't know about that,
but their croissants
are pretty good.
Since when do you cross town
for a croissant?
Since I had a meeting nearby
and wanted one.
I'd ask you how you are,
but I saw the announcement
in the Journal.
Louis as Managing Partner.
How did that happen?
If I told you,
you wouldn't believe me.
Does it have anything
to do with
the two new names on the wall?
One of which I've never
even heard of before.
- Just because you never
heard of her doesn't mean
she's not a badass.
- What's that supposed to mean?
- It means the type of work
that Samantha Wheeler did
before she got
her name on the wall
didn't exactly show up
in the Journal.
Now, why don't you get to
why you're here,
because this is no chance
encounter.
Told you,
I had a meeting nearby.
And I think that meeting's
with me because
I bet you have a case
against us.
Well, I'm sorry, Scottie,
but I'm not gonna let you get
in my head.
I think we both know
if I wanted to,
I could live in your head
rent-free.
It makes you feel any better,
I don't have a case
against you, Harvey.
Well,
it's good to see you though.
Maybe next time it won't
be by chance?
Katrina.
Samantha,
are you having a nice--
Do you mind if we skip
the chitchat?
- I'd like nothing more.
- Great.
Because I need your help
with something.
- With what?
- With getting out of a deal
I negotiated for
a mobile payment app
with our client's credit card
provider.
But this is
a three-year deal
and you're only
three months in.
- That's what makes it fun.
- Let me get this straight.
You want to get
out of this contract,
you don't have any
legal grounds to do it,
and you think I can fix
your problem for you?
What I think is if I can find
a reason to pay into a trust
instead of to them directly,
then we can squeeze them,
make them take a buyout.
And if you already have that
idea, why are you coming to me?
Because I need precedent,
and legal minutia
is one of your specialties.
- In other words, I owe you.
- You sure do.
And you better come up with
something fast,
because I need something
by noon.
- Noon?
- Why noon?
Because I already started
paying into
that trust yesterday,
and their douche bag attorney
moved the hearing up to today.
So unless you want
to owe me twice,
stop asking me questions and
start getting me some answers.
Harvey, you needed to see me?
I need to know what case I
got coming up against Scottie.
As far as I know,
you don't have any cases
pending against Scottie.
- Then look again,
because I just ran into her
at the coffee cart.
There's no way that was
a coincidence.
I don't know, Harvey.
The Scottie I remember
would never come at you
from the side like that.
I thought the whole point
was that you two enjoyed
attacking each other directly.
Well, things change.
It looks like she's operating
out of a new playbook.
If she is coming after us,
we need to be prepared.
Exactly, so why don't you
drop whatever you're doing
and figure out what case
she's got against us.
Consider it dropped.
Hey, Doc, listen,
before we get going,
I just want to tell you
I may need an hour and 15--
Holy shit, what's wrong?
Nothing, Louis,
but I'm afraid I'm going to
have to postpone our session.
Stan, are you okay? Because
if you need something, there
isn't anything I wouldn't--
- I'm fine, Louis.
It's a personal issue, and
I would rather not discuss it.
Well, I've known you
for years
and I've never seen
that look on your face,
so me walking out of here
without knowing
what's going on
isn't gonna happen.
Then if you must know,
it's a legal matter.
What kind of legal matter?
I don't want to talk
about it.
Well, that's too bad.
Because I can't represent you
if you don't tell me
what happened.
Louis,
it's out of the question.
My personal life has nothing
to do with you.
Nothing to do--
Stan, don't you get it?
I care about you.
I'm a lawyer.
And if you're in some
kind of trouble--
Louis, please.
This is not that serious.
Just not every day
I'm served with papers.
So if you will be so kind
as to reschedule,
I would greatly appreciate it.
Okay, Stan.
I'll see you next week.
♪ Suits 8x14 ♪
Peas in a Pod
Original Air Date on February 13, 2019
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ I'll even eat a bean pie,
I don't mind ♪
♪ Me and Missy is so busy,
busy making money ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ All step back,
I'm 'bout to dance ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
♪ The greenback boogie ♪
First of all, Mr. Kendrick,
I'd like to thank you for
sitting down with us.
I know your situation's been
difficult.
The situation
is my wife died.
- Difficult doesn't cover it.
- Of course not.
Can we just get on with it?
We made a few amendments
to your offer.
As you can see,
I've red-lined the sections--
Hang on. This says we admit
it was out fault.
- Because it was your fault.
- No, it wasn't.
And as tragic as
this death was,
we're under no obligation
to pay anything.
- Then why are you?
- It doesn't matter why.
I'm not admitting to something
that isn't true.
- Tony, let me--
- No, my machines regulate
insulin better than any human,
and I've dedicated my life
to helping people.
I'm not gonna let them say
I didn't.
Well, I dedicated my life
to caring for my wife.
She's dead now
because of your machine.
All right, there's no need
for hostility here,
so let's calm down,
go back to the offer--
You think I care about
your offer?
No amount of money's going
to bring my wife back.
All I care about is preventing
this from happening
to someone else,
and that means
making you take responsibility.
- Mr. Kendrick--
That's enough.
A woman is dead
because of
your client's product,
and if he won't admit it,
we'll make a jury admit
it for him.
This is our final offer.
Take it
or we'll see you in court.
Well, Ms. Wheeler, looks like
you're going to get to pay
into that trust after all,
because if they're not here
in the next two minutes--
- Sorry, I'm late, Your Honor.
I had a last-minute SNAFU.
Hold on, I thought
Larry Samuels was on this.
He was, but Larry's who they
call when they don't need me.
- Dana Scott.
- Oh.
- Heard a lot about you.
- Have you now?
I actually used to work
at your firm
back when there were only
three names on the wall.
Now there's so many
it's hard to keep track.
Well, after this,
you'll keep track just fine.
Because you haven't lived up
to your obligations,
and according to these
six precedents,
we have the right to nullify
this entire deal right now.
You don't have the right
to do anything.
You're in violation of
your contract.
Paying into a trust
isn't a violation.
No, but meeting with
the competition is.
I don't know what you're
talking about.
No, you just didn't know
I'd find out about it.
Because that SNAFU, Your Honor,
was waiting on confirmation
that Samantha Wheeler
has engaged in a pattern
of dirty tricks,
unethical behavior, and
borderline illegal activity
all in the name of
"representing" her clients.
And you're gonna say that
about me,
better damn well be able
to back it up,
which you can't.
Here are three of
Ms. Wheeler's old cases,
and then you'll find
payments forced,
settlements withheld, and
meetings with the competition
just like she did last week.
How the hell did
you get those?
Doesn't like you're denying
they're true.
Ms. Wheeler, did you meet
with the competition last week?
Your Honor, my past cases
have no relevance here.
No, but your answers
to my questions do.
Did you meet with them?
Yes, but--
You came into my chambers
ready to lie
and cheat
and God knows what else,
so you are going to dissolve
that trust,
you're gonna pay her client
the money you owe them,
and I don't ever want
to see you
in my chambers
on this case again.
All right, Tony,
it's just you and me now.
Please tell me you're 100% sure
this wasn't your machine.
Alex, have anyone in
the world test my machines,
every reports gonna say
the same thing.
That woman's death
wasn't our fault.
Then what else could have
caused it?
Because you heard that man.
We're going to trial.
This doesn't have to go to
trial, Alex, and you know it.
Just like we both know
what caused her death.
- Shit.
- Yeah, I know.
It was him, and we're gonna
have to prove it.
The question is
when the time comes,
are you gonna have the stomach
to do what needs to be done?
No, no, not right now, Donna.
I'm in the middle of something.
Well, I'm in the middle of
something for Harvey,
but these quarterly reports
aren't gonna sign themselves.
Well, put them
right over there.
"Boyd versus Lipschitz"?
- Lipschitz as in Dr. Lipschitz?
- Yes.
He's being sued, and he tried
to make it like it was nothing,
but then I pulled
his legal filing and--
- And it's not nothing.
- No, it's not.
One of his patients
is a construction foreman,
had a meltdown at work,
there was an accident,
put someone in a coma,
and now he claims it
only happened because Lipschitz
prescribed the wrong meds.
- Oh, my God.
- Yeah, gets worse.
Instead of coming to me,
he went to Dick Horman.
They lose this case, Donna,
he could lose his license.
Wait a second,
are you talking about
trying to convince Lipschitz
to let you represent him?
Yes, Donna, and I know you're
gonna tell me it's a bad idea.
It's not a bad idea, Louis.
If someone I cared about was
in a similar situation,
wild horses wouldn't stop me
from trying to protect them.
How could I not support you
in doing the same thing?
- You really mean that?
- Of course I do.
Well, then what do you say
you help me figure out a way
to convince Stan
to let me take his case.
- Samantha, how'd it go?
- I'll tell you how it went.
I got my ass handed to me
because they found out about
our meeting with their rival.
What meeting? You didn't
tell me about any meeting.
I didn't tell anyone,
which mean there's no way
they could have found out
unless they put someone
in their competitor's office.
I don't know, Samantha.
That sounds kind of extreme.
No, Katrina, it sounds shady,
and in my experience,
the other side only does
something like that
when they have already done
something even shadier.
So you think
they're hiding something
and you're gonna find it.
- No, we're gonna find it.
Because there's no way in hell
I'm gonna let Dana Scott
get the better of me.
- Wait, who?
- Dana Scott.
I know she used to work here
or something.
- She didn't just work here.
- What does that mean?
I'm not sure it's really
my place to--
Katrina,
do I have to say it again?
You owe me.
She and Harvey were together,
so if she knows things
she shouldn't,
he's the first place I'd look.
Hey, Harvey.
Dick over any of
your partners lately?
Samantha,
nice weather we're having.
- Did you hear what I said?
- Yeah, and I ignored it
because I have no idea what
you're talking about.
The name Dana Scott
ring any bells?
Because you just helped her
make me look like a sleazebag
in front of a judge.
Slow your roll, Tiger.
I didn't help her do anything.
All I said was, "You're
a badass and sometimes..."
Sometimes what?
I work in the gray?
Because she used
that against me.
All right,
I guess I did give her that,
but I didn't do it to help her.
Well, whether you meant
to help her or not, you did.
So how about leveling the field
and helping the home team?
No way.
I'm not getting involved.
- Why not?
- Because it'll just make her
want to win all the more.
Oh. So you're that
kind of guy.
What kind of guy?
Handsome, powerful men--
goes one of two ways.
You either want a woman who
doesn't challenge you at all
or you want one who challenges
you all the time.
I'm sorry,
I stopped listening after
the handsome
and powerful part.
The thing is, Harvey,
with someone who challenges
you all the time,
there's always
unfinished business.
This is your chance
to finish it.
No, Samantha, this is just a
chance to rip open an old scar,
and I'm not doing it.
Well,
she just ripped me open,
and I'm gonna do whatever
it takes to return the favor.
You don't want to help me,
don't,
but you sure as hell better
stop helping her.
- Katrina.
- Harvey.
- What are you doing in here?
- Just having a coffee.
No, you're here
because you know
I'm working with Samantha
in her office
and you don't want her
to hear what you have to say.
What if I don't?
You gonna tell her about this?
I guess that depends
on exactly what it is you want.
I want to know if there's
a deal to be had here.
I don't know. Right now,
Samantha is so pissed
I don't think
she'd take anything less
than an outright win.
- And on top of that,
Samantha won't stop looking
for leverage
until she finds something
that gives her the upper hand.
Pretty much, yeah.
Tell me this...
what would a compromise
look like?
Louis, what are you doing?
I'll tell you
what I'm not doing.
I'm not leaving until you sign
this engagement letter.
I told you,
I have the matter handled.
By Dick Corman
who couldn't handle his way
out of a paper bag.
Now either you let me do this
or you tell me what's going on,
but I'm a better lawyer
than this guy.
- Louis, please.
- Stan, don't you believe
that I'm great at what I do?
Because if I thought
you didn't think that,
I wouldn't have seen you
all these years.
I do believe you're great
at what you do,
but you overreact.
Particularly when it involves
people you care about.
God damn it, Stan,
your career is on the line.
You hire me, you have my word
that won't happen.
I am well aware my career
is on the line, Louis.
It is all I can think about.
Well, then think about this.
How many times have you told me
that I get in my own way?
Well, now you're getting
in yours,
because I am the best man
for this job
and deep down you know it.
Okay, Louis,
you can represent me,
but under one condition.
I just told you I'll keep
myself in check.
No, Louis.
One other condition.
- Thanks, Bill.
- Who's Bill?
Just one of my many lovers
calling to say hi.
Or your doorman calling to
say he's got your dry cleaning.
Why can't he be both?
Now why don't you tell me
what you're doing
in enemy territory.
See, that's the thing,
Scottie.
You're an opponent.
You're not an enemy.
I don't want to see
you get hurt.
- What is that?
- A way out.
We buy your client
at a fair price,
they make a fortune,
everybody comes out ahead.
I don't believe it.
I win the championship
and you want me to share
the trophy?
You didn't win anything yet,
and she's not letting this go.
- So what?
So you two are on
a collision course,
and it isn't gonna be pretty.
- I didn't pick this fight.
But you escalated it by using
information you got from me
to go personal against
my partner.
I did what I had to do on
behalf of my client.
Well, Samantha's
gonna do what she has to
and trust me,
what she's willing to do
isn't something
you want a piece of.
Does she even know
about this?
I should have known.
Get out of my office, Harvey.
I don't believe this.
You lie to my face about taking
a case against me,
and now you're upset
that I don't have
Samantha's approval
before coming over here?
I said that I didn't have
a case against you, not her.
Well, now you do have
a case against me
whether you like it or not,
because I gave you that offer,
which means you have to
present it to your client.
You are not one of the
attorneys listed on this case.
I do not have to present
anything,
and even if I did,
I can tell you what they'd say.
- "Go to hell."
- Scottie--
Thank you for the warning,
Harvey,
but I'm doing just fine.
Okay, have it your way,
but don't come crying to me
when she figures out
how to turn the tables.
- Hello?
- Samantha, it's Dana Scott.
Dana,
to what do I owe the pleasure?
Look, we got off
on the wrong foot today.
You obviously don't want to be
in business with us anymore,
so I came up with a compromise.
- I'm listening.
You honor your contract
for the next 18 months
and reduce your fees
every quarter after that,
and we won't enforce
our exclusivity clause.
I get it--you get to keep
your revenue stream
so your earnings
don't take a hit,
and we get to quietly
pursue a new partnership.
Plus, you save the backlash
from me telling the judge
that you're still working
on this--like I know you are.
I gotta say...
it's a pretty good move.
And under other circumstances,
you'd have yourself a deal.
- What other circumstances?
- One where there wasn't
more going on here
than meets the eye.
There's nothing else
going on here.
Save it.
You're coming to me
with a compromise
when you have me?
You did something here,
and I'm gonna find it.
What makes you think I won't
find out more on you?
Because it took me
barely an hour
to find out
what I already did.
I think playing dirty
isn't your specialty.
You took a walk
on the wild side,
and turns out you
fucked with the wrong marine.
- Listen to me--
- Sorry, Dana.
I'm done listening
because I got to get back
to looking.
Gretchen, need something?
The report on that diabetes
machine came in.
Why are you
bringing me this?
Because I know you're gonna
use it to attack that husband.
Gretchen, if you're here to
tell me not to go after him,
I'm already twisted up
about it anyway.
As someone whose husband
died of diabetes,
I'm telling you
do what you have to do.
Your husband
died of diabetes?
He did.
And that man is grieving.
He's looking for an answer,
and I can't blame him,
but without machines
like that one,
my Carl wouldn't have lived
as long as he did.
Hey, how did you even know
about this case?
Well, we never really
discussed the client you lost
because of me.
- We didn't need to.
They never should have
asked me to let you go,
and I never would have
done it anyway.
All the same,
I never thanked you
'cause I didn't know how.
So you were keeping tabs
on my cases
waiting for a way to help.
I know it really
isn't helping, but--
Gretchen, you just showed me
it was okay to do something
I never thought I'd have to do.
If that isn't help,
I don't know what is.
Thanks, Alex.
All right,
we've been at this for hours.
It's getting us nowhere.
We need to shake down
some employees.
And that's all well and good,
but if we don't know
what to ask, we're not
going to get any answers.
Yes, we will.
They don't know
what we don't know.
Yeah,
that's what I just said.
No, Samantha, I'm saying
according to this report
their accounts are growing
by 200% a month.
Wait a second,
if that's true,
why are they clinging
to this deal like a life raft?
Because maybe they're not
really growing by 200% a month.
Look.
February...
5 million new users,
but 60% didn't meet
the transaction threshold,
parsing a likelihood
of the fact--
Katrina, English.
60% of these card holders
don't even seem to know
they have the cards.
Holy shit.
The people are real,
but the accounts are fake.
This isn't just shady,
this is the type of shit
that lands someone in prison.
- Wait till the judge sees this.
- The judge?
Why don't you just leverage
them into letting us out?
Because I have
the upper hand now.
I'm not giving her
a chance to get it back.
Samantha, if she has anything
to do with this,
it would ruin her.
And if she didn't want
to be ruined,
she shouldn't have gotten
involved in this,
and she damn sure shouldn't
have fucked with me.
I want everything you have
ready for court in 36 hours.
Scottie,
what are you doing here?
I need to know if
Samantha Wheeler
is really the attack dog
Harvey says she is.
No, I heard about you
tricking Harvey
into giving you information.
I'm not gonna let you
do the same thing to me.
This is not about tricking
you, Donna.
This is about me
staying out of prison.
What?
Please.
My clients have been creating
fake accounts.
I found out about it, and I've
been helping them cover it up.
- How could you--
- I know.
I put a stop to it, but if
I can buy them some time,
they can dig themselves out,
and hundreds of good people
can keep their jobs.
Scottie, what exactly are you
here to ask me?
I want you to convince Harvey
to make Samantha
honor that contract.
Are you crazy?
With a company
that's committed fraud?
They're making up for
the fake accounts,
but they lose their contract,
they go under,
and everything comes out.
Okay, let's say
that I believe you.
Why are you coming to me
and not Harvey?
Because he came to me
with a deal
and I told him to go to hell.
- Why would you do that?
Because if we take that deal,
they open up the books
and everything
comes out anyway.
And that all sounds great,
but Harvey's gonna find out
one way or the other,
and you want me to tell him
instead of telling
him yourself.
So what the hell is really
going on?
Okay, fine,
you want the truth?
I'm ashamed of what I did,
and maybe I
wouldn't have done it
if it didn't save those jobs,
but maybe I would have...
because I signed that company.
I put my ass on the line
for them,
and I wasn't going
to let them fail.
And if that's the case,
Harvey would
definitely understand because
he's done the exact
same thing himself.
Maybe he would,
but I need him to do this,
and let's face it.
For a long time now,
you've had a lot more
sway over him than me.
I convince him to help you.
From now on,
you steer clear of our firm.
You mean
steer clear of Harvey.
I said what I meant,
Scottie.
Yes or no?
- Mr. Grant, you have a moment?
- Actually, no.
Yeah, I don't care.
My name is Louis Litt,
and I'm representing
Dr. Stanley Lipschitz.
I thought Dick Corman
was representing--
You thought you got lucky and
Dick Corman was handling this.
Well, unfortunately for you,
the big dogs are here.
Well, they better be here
with a big, fat settlement
'cause my client lost
his livelihood
due to your client's mistake.
Your client lost
his livelihood
because he had
a manic episode at work.
And I have 50 years of
precedent that says
you cannot blame a doctor
for reasonably prescribing
medication.
Now normally,
I would walk in here and say
I've got you by the balls,
squeeze a little tighter
until you beg me for mercy,
but I'm not gonna do that.
- Oh, no?
- No.
I'm gonna offer you
a reasonable settlement
that you're gonna take,
because there's not one person
on the planet that believes
my client was at fault here.
Actually,
there is one person.
And he just happens to be the
leading expert in the field.
So you're gonna take whatever
you're offer was
and add two more zeroes,
because I got you, asshole,
and that testimony proves it.
- It proves nothing,
and when I get through
with your so-called expert,
all the jury's gonna see
is a quack who is willing
to sell his testimony
to the highest bidder.
I'll see you in court.
Mr. Kendrick,
did your wife
manage her insulin levels
all by herself?
No, her doctor set
her base levels,
and I monitored
her daily needs.
And isn't it true
you recently changed
the brand of cartridge
you used?
Yes, we tried the newest one
on the market,
but your machine said
it would accommodate.
And it does,
but it also requires
the overnight dosage time
to be manually set by the user.
- Who did that?
- I did.
And I set the machine for
2:00 a.m. like always.
Then why did the machine
not deliver the dosage
until 3:00 a.m.?
- I don't know.
- Why don't you ask your client?
- I have.
I've also asked an expert third
party to check the machine.
And they both said
it was working fine,
yet that dose wasn't delivered
until 3:00.
- Is there a question here?
- Yes.
Is it possible, Mr. Kendrick,
that you set the machine
for 3:00 a.m.?
- No, absolutely not.
- How can you be sure?
Because I double-checked
the time.
I always double-check the time,
and it said 2:00.
- When did you double-check it?
- Right before we went to bed.
- And what time was that?
- I don't remember--
You don't remember the time,
but you remember checking
the machine.
Yes, I do, and it was
probably around 10:00.
So it was late.
You were tired.
- That doesn't mean--
- You could make a mistake?
Why not?
Because you're perfect?
You're a computer?
A machine?
- That's not fair!
- No, what's not fair
is you blaming my client
for your mistake,
because there are only
two factors here--
that machine and you.
And when I present all this
plus the fact
there is no instance
of our machine ever failing,
even if the jury finds
in your favor,
the judge will throw it out
as a matter of law.
I checked that time.
I see it in my mind,
and you are never going
to tell me different.
How low can you be
to pin this on him?
Don't give me that.
My client started this company
because his own family
needed it,
and the world's
a better place because he did.
We gave you an offer.
It still stands.
I'd advise your client
to take it.
Harvey,
we need to talk about Scottie.
- No, we don't.
- Yeah, we do,
because this isn't just
the usual case of you two
screwing each other over
for fun.
- She's--
- I know.
She's involved
in some shady shit.
You know? How?
Doesn't matter how.
Okay, then what are you gonna
do about it?
I'm not gonna do anything
about it.
She had every chance
to ask for help,
she didn't, and when
I came to her with a deal,
she told me to go to hell.
- Yeah,
because if she took that deal,
it would all come out.
Well, it's all gonna
come out now anyway.
I don't believe this.
What is wrong with you?
She's only in this mess
because
she tried to save
people's jobs,
and you might have done
the exact same thing.
Why the hell are you even
defending her?
- Why shouldn't I defend her?
- Because you've always been--
Been what?
Afraid to say it?
Yeah, that's not a surprise.
Well, Harvey,
believe it or not,
I care about her.
And every time
we've ever needed her
she's been there for us.
Not last year with
Stanley Gordon.
Maybe not every time,
but when it was
you on the line or Mike,
she was there for us.
And in case you forgot,
you basically did the exact
same thing with Teddy Doyle,
and not a week ago you
came to me to save your ass
just like she did this morning.
You two are peas in a pod,
you always have been.
And for a guy who says
loyalty is a two-way street...
you sure as hell
aren't acting like it.
Because we aren't
two peas in a pod.
She's supposed
to be better than me.
- Harvey.
- Donna, she did this.
She didn't even tell me
about it,
and now I'm supposed to make
my new partner,
who I unknowingly sold out,
take it easy...on the person
I sold her out to.
And I understand all that,
but if it were me,
I'd get Samantha
to back off anyway.
Gretchen,
can I talk to you for a second?
About what?
About how it went with
our plaintiff today.
Of course, what happened?
I hammered him
again and again,
but it didn't matter.
He stuck to his story
and said he didn't care
what I said
or the machine said
or that report said.
He checked the time,
and it was 2:00 a.m.
Alex, what are you looking
for me to tell you?
You made a mistake with me
you never thought
you could make.
I guess I'm looking
for you to say
the same thing
must have happened here.
- I can't tell you that.
- Why not?
Because I never followed up
with that messenger.
That was my mistake,
never following up.
But he's saying that he did
follow up,
and if that's the case,
you painted that man as guilty
when he wasn't.
And all that bullshit I said
about it being worth it
goes out the window.
All right.
- I need some time to think.
- No.
You need someone to help you
sort through this mess
and figure out
what's going on here.
Alex, what are you doing?
Couldn't wait till tomorrow
to bill me?
I wish that's why I was here,
Tony.
But something James said
didn't sit right with me,
so...I went back through
everything,
and I found this.
- What is that?
Turns out the software update
on those new cartridges,
the ones James used--
Glitched for exactly 12
minutes between 9:43 and 9:55.
The exact window
which I suspect
Anne Kendrick's machine reset.
Fuck.
Tony, I've got to ask.
Did you know about this?
You know me a long time,
Alex.
How can you accuse me
of that?
I'm not accusing you
of anything,
but I need to know the truth.
Well, the truth is
I didn't know about
this until eight second ago.
And if you hadn't been looking
where you shouldn't of,
you wouldn't either.
- What does that mean?
It means I need you to
pretend you never saw this.
Tony, a woman is dead.
Well, this isn't
gonna bring her back,
and she was
the only person harmed.
No, she was not.
Her husband lost his wife
and I as much as told him
he killed her
so you can keep making
this machine.
And I don't keep making
this machine,
how many people
are gonna die?
Because I shouldn't have
to remind you
we don't make sunglasses.
And I shouldn't have
to remind you
it's my duty to hand this over.
Then back up a truck full of
documents and bury it,
because your duty doesn't
include your guilt
putting my company
out of business.
So you're telling me they
did not accept our settlement?
Yes, and before you ask,
I did not overreact.
They bought themselves a
so-called expert that's saying
you should have known better
than to change
that prescription.
- What?
- Stan, trust me.
It happens all the time.
Now the next step--
Who do they have?
Some joker named
Paul Baxter,
and I'll admit that his
credentials look good on paper,
but trust me,
when I get him on the stand--
Louis, I know this man.
His opinion is not for sale,
and I will not let you
ruin his reputation,
because if he's saying
I caused this--
No, Stan, he's not saying it.
They're pushing him to say it.
And I just told you
they couldn't push him
to say anything.
What if I misprescribed,
Louis?
What if I am truly responsible
for my own patient's breakdown?
And if a jury decides that,
so be it.
But you're the one who
told me a thousand times
it's not an exact science,
right?
Craig Boyd is unstable.
Could have had a bad day
or a fight with his mother
or a thousand other things
that could have caused this,
but we are not going down
without a fight.
Okay, Louis.
Do what you must.
Put Dr. Baxter on the stand.
Good, and I'm putting
Craig Boyd up there too.
What?
Louis, you can't do that.
He's my patient.
Stan, if we don't get you
out of this,
no one's gonna be your
patient.
Louis,
let's say you're correct.
That he broke down
for another reason.
What do you think will happen
when you go after him
on the stand?
Hopefully, he'll have
another breakdown
which will show that
the first one
had nothing to do with
his medication.
Well, that is not something
I can hope for.
Stan, I did what you asked
with his lawyer.
I wasn't myself.
But you can't ask me
to not do everything I can
to get you out of this.
It's him or you.
Then let it be him
because if he were to hurt
himself or,
God forbid, worse,
I could not live with that.
- Stan--
- Louis, this is my final word.
So if you insist
on going after Craig,
I will find another lawyer.
Harvey, whatever it is,
it'll have to wait.
- I'm busy preparing.
- I know what you're preparing.
And I know instead of going
to the judge,
you could go to Scottie
with this.
She came to you,
didn't she?
Because she was in
on this thing.
- I didn't say that.
- You didn't have to.
The settlement says it
loud and clear.
- Look--
- No.
I've got proof
of serious fraud,
and you're here to get me
to let them off the hook.
I'm here to get you to let
her off the hook.
And why should I do that?
Because you used to
sleep with her?
Because she did it for
the right reasons
just like when
you buried evidence.
You said you did it for
the right reasons,
and by the way, you told me
you'd do it again.
That was to save
an innocent woman's life.
This is to save
innocent peoples' jobs.
I'm not gonna let you do
this to Scottie.
This is my case.
You told me you didn't want
anything to do with it,
and now you want me to sell
my client down the river.
I'm not asking you to sell
anyone down the river.
I'm asking you to have
her back.
This isn't about me
having her back.
It's about you having mine.
And you didn't
when you told her about me,
you didn't when I came to you
for help,
and you don't have it
right now.
Maybe I didn't have
your back,
but on this one I can't.
Guess I'm saying if you're not
willing to have her back,
think of it as having mine.
Donna,
can I talk to you a second?
Does this have something
to do with Lipschitz?
Yeah.
I have an idea,
but it involves
going to his patient
behind his back
and threatening to put him
on the stand.
Why can't you just put him
on the stand?
Because Lipschitz
won't let me,
and if he found out
that I even met with him,
could ruin our relationship.
- Then don't do it.
- But if I don't, Donna,
then he'll probably lose
his license.
And as hard as
that is to accept,
it's his choice.
So I say if you really care
about him,
you need to stop representing
him and start being his friend.
I'm not sure
if I can do that.
I hope you can.
- Louis.
- Yeah.
As long as we're talking
about mixing the personal
with the professional,
there's...
something that's
been on my mind,
and I haven't told you
and it's time that I did.
What is it?
Thomas Kessler and I have
been seeing each other,
and I know he's a client--
- Say no more, Donna.
Thomas is a good man,
and as far as I'm concerned,
if you two are okay
with seeing each other
while he's still a client,
then I'm okay with it too.
- Thanks, Louis.
- Of course, Donna.
I just have on question.
Have you told Harvey yet?
No, I haven't,
but I will.
I should've known.
You did all this.
You went to him, didn't you?
- Yes, I did.
- God damn it.
I came to you to help me.
You came to me because
I kick ass as an attorney.
And in case you didn't notice,
you wouldn't even be
in the position
to make a decision
if it weren't for me.
In case you didn't notice,
I have already made
my decision,
because I don't give
a shit what Harvey says.
We're in the fourth quarter,
we're up by ten,
and I am not taking
my foot off the gas.
What the hell
is wrong with you?
You have a chance to
let someone keep their life
and still get a win.
- Is revenge that important?
- It's not revenge.
- It's protection.
- From what?
She went after me in public.
- Tried to expose me as--
- As what?
Exactly who you are?
Well, here's a thought.
If you don't want
to be exposed at that,
maybe try not being that
in the first place.
I can't change who I was.
No, but you can start turning
it around right now.
And at the same time,
you'll have Harvey owe you
and Scottie owe you.
What good does it do
to have those people owe me
if they're just gonna be
like you
and not pay up
when the time comes?
I am paid up.
You just don't get
that because owing you
doesn't mean doing
whatever you say.
I am a senior partner and
I have done everything I can
to help you come out
a winner in this.
And if you can't see that,
that's on you.
So I'll just say
you're welcome
and leave it at that.
Gretchen, not now.
Yes, now.
Because you put in a request
for 50,000 documents
to all be delivered tonight.
I don't want to
talk about it.
Yes, you do or you
wouldn't have had
the request specifically take
priority over my case.
- I didn't--
- Don't bullshit me.
You did that because you don't
like what's going on
and you wanted me
to talk you out of it.
There is no
talking me out of it.
Well, we'll just have to see
about that then.
Because it doesn't take
a genius to guess
you don't need that many copies
unless you're trying to hide
something in them.
Okay, maybe I did want you
to talk me out of it,
but it's too late now.
They're already gone.
They may already be gone,
but it's never too late.
- Gretchen--
- No, imagine it was me.
Imagine you were letting me
think I killed my Carl.
Would it still be
too late then?
- Can I help you?
- Hi, I'm Louis Litt.
- I'm--
- I know who are you.
You're the guy representing
Dr. Lipschitz,
which means you can't see me
without my lawyer here.
Except I'm not here
as his attorney.
I'm here as one of his
patients.
- What?
- Yeah.
I've been seeing Stan
for a very long time,
which is why I know
how valuable
having someone like him
in the world is
and how much he's probably
helped you.
You don't know nothing
about me.
No, I don't.
But I know about me
and the thing about me
is I'd do anything to blame
others before I blame myself.
And if you think
that's what I'm doing,
then you can go to hell--
- What I think
is you're protecting yourself,
but what you don't know is
Stanly Lipschitz
is protecting you too.
What are you talking about?
I could put you on
the stand right now
and I can break you.
Look at me.
I can do it in a heartbeat,
but he won't let me do that
because of what
it would do to you
even if it means losing
his ability to help others.
Isn't that proof enough
that the world's a better place
with Dr. Stanley Lipschitz
doing what he does best?
I lost everything.
I have no job.
If I walk away from this,
what am I gonna do?
Two things. First, you meet
me in my office tomorrow.
I represent
the top construction firms
in the country, and we will
find you another job.
- And then?
- You call Dr. Lipschitz.
You set up an appointment,
and you start talking
this through...
because you need him now
more than ever.
- Get the hell off my driveway.
- I get it.
You hate me,
but I was doing my job.
It wasn't personal.
You accused me of
killing my wife.
Felt pretty goddamn personal
to me,
so tell me what the hell
you're doing here.
There's a truckload of files
on the way to your lawyer.
I was just gonna let them go
and--needle in a haystack,
but I couldn't.
so I made a second copy
of one file,
and I'm here to give it to you.
Why are you giving it to me
and not my lawyer?
Because this is the one
that says
there was a problem
with our software.
So you lied to my face.
We didn't lie.
We didn't know.
- Bullshit.
- It's not bullshit.
Antonio offered you that deal
when he honestly believed
his company had nothing
to do with this.
You're not here
to give me this.
You're here to ask me
to go easy on him.
No, James.
I'm here because in my heart
I know you had nothing to do
with your wife's death,
and I'm sorry
I ever said otherwise.
What happened was
one in a million thing,
and I also know
if this comes out,
more people are going to die,
not less.
I know you're a good man.
Please don't put
an end to this company.
Scottie, please tell me
it all worked out.
It did.
Samantha came to me
with a deal,
nothing comes out, we all
live to fight another day.
Well, that's great news.
Listen, if I came across
as judging you, I--
You didn't.
You came through for me, so...
thank you.
But?
Why did you do it?
Why did you help me?
There are a lot of things
that we're at odds
with each other about,
Scottie, but...
the one thing
we've always had in common
is that we both care about him.
And you've always
protected him.
That means something.
I called to tell you that
I'm going to live up
to my agreement.
From now on,
I'll stay away from him.
I told you
that's not what I meant.
I know,
but I'm going to anyway.
And, Donna...I hope someday
he sees what everyone sees.
I'm guessing somebody
got a call from Craig.
I did, Louis.
Going to him
as a patient
instead of as my attorney
was a wonderful idea.
I can't thank you enough.
However, there is still one
thing we must discuss.
Yeah,
if this is about payment,
you can just reinstate my
weekend texting privileges
and we'll just call it even.
You know that's not what
I was going to say.
You agreed that once
this was over,
I would no longer be
your therapist.
I am calling to discuss
our transition.
No, I don't accept that.
Louis,
you know too much
for me to effectively continue
as your therapist.
Well, pardon my French, Stan,
but that is bullshit.
Our best breakthroughs
were made
by you sharing
your personal life with me.
And those were wonderful
sessions,
but, Louis, you agreed.
- No, I don't care.
- Louis.
- Stan,
Even three years ago,
I would have gone behind
your back,
threatened to put Craig
on the stand,
and God knows what he might
have done to himself,
but because of you
I went to him with compassion.
If that isn't proof showing me
your human side is effective,
Stan, I don't know what is.
Weekend texting
will never return,
but I can try to answer
your e-mails
in a more timely fashion.
- Thank you, Stan.
- No, Louis, thank you.
Well?
He asked for twice the money
so he can set up
a foundation
in his wife's name,
but he agreed to keep
the settlement sealed.
What about Tony?
He figure out what you did?
- He did.
- What'd you tell him?
What I should have told him
in the first place.
That what he asked wasn't right
by me, James, or anyone else,
and if you ever ask me to do
anything like it again,
he can find himself
another lawyer.
He's lucky to have you.
And I'm lucky to have you.
- Are you hitting on me?
- No,
but I am inviting you
to dinner tomorrow night.
I could invite
my father-in-law too.
He's a widower.
Not bad-looking...
if you ask him.
And I will tell you
what I told Carl.
After he's gone,
there won't be any other men.
He didn't believe me either.
See you tomorrow night.
Invite Pops.
We'll see what happens.
Hey.
I just wanted you to know--
Scottie called to thank me,
Harvey.
That's funny.
She just called me.
Well, I guess she's grateful
to both of us.
I guess so.
Um...
did she say something
to you about...
About what?
- Oh, perfect timing.
- Thomas.
I thought we were meeting
downstairs.
Well, I got here
a little early.
I thought I'd come meet you.
- Harvey, this is Thomas--
- Kessler, we've met.
- Nice to see you again.
- You too.
Louis always spoke
very highly of you.
You too.
- Well, shall we?
- Of course.
- Good night, Harvey.
- Good night.
You look lost.
I was just...
I'm sorry I didn't
say yes sooner.
She pushed a button.
I let my competitive nature
get the better of me.
- She does that.
- She sure does.
Hey, I was gonna go to
my office and get a drink,
but now I'm thinking
I want to go out.
- You care to join me?
- Why not?
But you're buying,
'cause after all,
I had your back.
I am never gonna hear the end
of this, am I?
No, sir, you are not.
You got anymore ex-girlfriend
lawyers I should know about?
I'll send you a list.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
www.tvsubtitles.net