Previously on Suits
Gordon doesn't want a takeover.
He wants a deal
where his guys come back,
they vote to merge with Zane,
- and we cease to exist.
- I found out
my two partners,
Eric Kaldor and Ellen Rand,
are willing to stab me in the back.
We don't need
the sex phone anymore,
because you hit the bull's eye.
Oh, my God.
My boys can swim?
I've got a legal situation.
It's personal.
You need me to send one
of ours your way.
- I was thinking Alex Williams.
- I guess firm harmony
is why you want Alex
and not Samantha.
That and a little of
the nature of the case.
I got my period.
I'm not pregnant.
But the test said...
It was a false positive.
I'm so sorry.
Samantha Wheeler.
Normally I'm happy to see
a former colleague.
Just not one that walked out
the door with half our business.
Then you're really
gonna hate it when I attack
what little business
you have left.
You're suing Grayscale.
I'm not.
The federal government is.
Bullshit.
You don't represent
the government.
If a company defrauds
the United States,
any attorney can sue
to reclaim those damages.
You can spout any Act you want.
There's no way you give a shit
about the government.
I don't.
But what I do care about
is Grayscale coming over to us
like they wanted.
They never wanted
to go with you.
Why are you holding them
to their agreement?
And before you answer,
we both know
it's because if you
let them go, they'd leave.
Well, they might have.
But now that you're suing them,
you just tipped
the gray scales my way.
I forgot you and your puns.
Well, I don't have to pretend
they're charming anymore.
So this is how it's gonna go.
I'm gonna get you in a bear hug.
Your only way out is
to let them come to us.
So you can do it now
or you can do it later,
but trust me, it's gonna happen.
Thank you for stopping by,
Samantha.
I'd forgotten how much nicer
it is since you've been gone.
Louis, what are
you still doing here?
I took the day off.
And I called your office.
You're taking the day off too.
But... No buts.
I am taking you to
the happiest place on Earth.
Louis, as much as I love
Colonial Williamsburg,
I can't today.
Our costumes are already
in the car.
I appreciate that, Louis.
And it's sweet
you wanna distract me
from what happened.
But I was already planning on
taking today off, anyway.
You were?
Yeah.
Louis, we had a false positive.
If we want a real positive,
we have to stop
leaving things to chance.
So I made an appointment
with the top fertility
specialist in the country.
You really think
we need a specialist?
I think these things
can take time.
So the sooner we get some help,
the sooner we can hold
that baby in our arms.
What are we waiting for?
You don't have to come.
Listen to me.
This is as important to me
as it is to you.
And there is nothing
on this earth
that's gonna stop me
from being by your side.
Samantha, can I talk to you
for a second?
I'm a little busy right now.
What you mean is,
you're a little busy
leveraging Eric Kaldor into
giving us one of his clients.
Yeah, that's what I said.
You think this is funny?
I think Robert has been
going through something.
I wanna get him a little
present for when he gets back.
In other words, you heard
Robert and Alex bonded
over whatever he's been
going through,
you feel your chair
at the table's moving down,
and you're trying to move it up.
So what if I am?
The present you get him
better be that client.
Eric Kaldor is no lightweight.
And last I checked, the cases
I take aren't your concern.
They are
if there's a possibility
they could affect
this firm's record.
So if you take this guy on,
you better win.
That won't be a problem.
I know how Kaldor thinks.
I'm sure you do.
But in this instance,
you picked a fight
with the one person
who wants to beat you more.
I picked this fight.
I'm not backing down.
Unless you wanna give me a
direct order I wouldn't follow,
I suggest you get out of my way,
'cause I got a case to win.
Synced & corrected by MaxPayne
== https://subscene.com ==
There you are.
Gretchen,
where the hell is Louis?
You wanna try that again
with some civility?
What? How about, "Good
morning, Gretchen.
You look lovely today.
I brought you this fine latte."
You're right. I'm coming up
against a deadline,
but that's no excuse to be rude.
Good morning, Gretchen.
Don't you look lovely.
Now didn't that feel better?
Actually, it did.
It will feel better
when you tell me where Louis is.
I'm not so sure I will.
Louis is gone for the day.
Shit.
What's the problem?
White Mountain Water's
putting together
a national distribution deal.
We have to agree not to rep
any competition for a year.
You need Louis' approval
for a commitment like that.
He already agreed,
I just need his signature.
I need it by the end of the day.
Now it's my turn to say "shit".
Gretchen, I need that signature.
And you will get it.
I'm saying "shit"
'cause I know
where I have to go.
Gretchen.
Alex, just give me the document.
Tell me where you need me
to send it.
I give you my word,
it will get there.
Hey.
Cucumber or eucalyptus?
They have both?
They have everything.
See the waiting room? Leather
seats, soothing lighting...
I haven't met him,
but I love him.
- Ms. Sazs. Mr. Litt.
- Dr. McManus.
Thank you for seeing us
on such short notice.
No "doctor" necessary.
I'm Charles,
but everybody calls me... Chaz.
Chaz McManus.
That's right. Usually,
people guess Chuck. Heh.
I have your files,
but I prefer to establish
baseline health myself.
Is that okay?
Of course.
Uh, what do you need me to do?
We'll start with blood samples.
So just head down that hall.
The nurse will show you.
We can discuss
everything the two of you
would like to accomplish.
Okay.
I'll see you in a bit.
I'm sorry.
Do you not, uh...
remember me?
I, uh...
Louis Litt.
Scarsdale High.
Class of '88?
I'm sorry,
I don't remember you, Louis.
I never felt like I fit in
during high school.
I don't think about those days.
But I also know I wasn't
the nicest kid back then.
If there's any bad blood
between us,
I hope there's no hard feelings.
So there she was,
feet in the stirrups,
Louis looking, both of them
in hospital gowns...
Wait, why was Louis in a gown?
He didn't want her to feel self-conscious.
That's sweet.
You get to say that
because you weren't there.
I shouldn't have to remind you,
those gowns don't close
in the behind.
So between Louis and Sheila,
I had to walk that document in
like this:
Come on. Was she really
in the stirrups?
I caught 'em
before they went in.
That was the movie
that was playing in my head.
So as far as I'm concerned,
it's just as bad.
Well, the important thing is,
Alex got his signature,
and the score remains
Gretchen: 1,000,973.
World: Zero.
Damn right.
Good luck with your stack, Red.
You too, Gretchen.
Oh. And whatever you do,
try not to buy another ticket
to that movie.
She just had to say that.
Mr. Kaldor, this trial is not
scheduled for another two weeks.
You'd better have a good reason
for calling us.
I do. I would like you
to remove Ms. Wheeler
from this case.
On what grounds?
On the grounds that you were
an attorney of record
for my client.
Is that true?
Absolutely not.
I never worked on their case.
Well, according to this billing
sheet, uh, you absolutely did.
This was seven years ago
for two hours.
Your Honor, I was an associate.
Someone must've told me
to run copies and bill it.
A minute ago,
you never worked for them.
Now it's running copies?
Your Honor.
This is your billing sheet?
I mean, this is your
signature, isn't it? Yes.
But even if I technically
worked for Grayscale,
I never had access
to privileged information.
Unless you're lying about
your billables,
a disbarrable offense.
Then, technically or not,
you're bound by privilege.
Your Honor, she's prohibited
from bringing suit
against an old client.
I'm afraid he's right,
Ms. Wheeler.
Unless there's someone else
from your firm
not bound by privilege,
this case is dismissed.
Louis. You
little piece of shit.
You ratted me out
for cheating in bio.
You're right, I did.
Because it isn't fair,
Mr. O'Connor
grades on the curve.
That sounded like talk-back.
Aah!
Now, because of you,
O'Connor gave me an F,
and my old man is gonna kill me.
Know what that means?
You're gonna do my homework
the rest of the year.
You're not gonna say
a word about it.
No, I'm not.
And you can't make me.
Maybe you weren't listening.
I don't know bio.
Which means I don't know
where the kidneys are.
Now, are they here?
Aah!
Here?
Or here?
Still have
philosophical reservations?
Okay, I'll do it.
Just please, let me go.
That's my boy.
Every day, before first bell,
that day's homework
is in my hands.
You're ever late,
we're gonna take a trip
to the equipment locker
in front of the whole school,
and I'm gonna lock you in.
I spent the rest of the year
racing to school,
just terrified I'd be late.
The first time I was,
Chaz was true to his word.
He dragged me to the gym,
shoved me into
an equipment locker,
and said that if I
ever told anyone,
next time would be worse.
You've told me
what a hard time you had
in your youth, but this...
That's not even the part
that I've been thinking about.
You see, by the end,
I just stopped fighting.
So if I was late, Chaz would
walk me down the hall,
we'd get to the gym,
he'd open up
the equipment locker door,
I'd hand him his homework,
and I would walk myself
right in.
I can only imagine
what you must have felt
when you saw him again
after all this time.
All he had to say about it was,
"No hard feelings."
Well, there are hard feelings.
Feelings you have been carrying
with you ever since.
That's why
I wanna show you this.
It's something that I haven't
looked at in 30 years.
Louis, what did Sheila say
when you showed her this?
Show her?
No, I couldn't do that.
Why not?
I've been doing research
since we left,
hoping that it wasn't true.
But there's nobody
better than this guy.
If we want our best chances
to have this baby,
I just have to deal with
these feelings.
Then at least let Sheila in on
what you are going through.
Because if you don't
let off some steam,
there is likely to be
an explosion.
Harvey? I'm sorry to bother you,
but do you have a minute?
Ha!
I don't believe this.
Shit went sideways with
your case, and you want help.
I didn't say that.
You didn't need to.
You're here with your
pass-the-butter voice,
and I warned you
this would happen.
Maybe you did, but...
Not "maybe".
I said you were picking
a fight with the wrong guy,
and you said
you knew what you were doing.
Okay, Harvey.
You were right.
Wanna say, "I told you so",
or wanna help me beat this guy?
You don't know what I wanna do.
I can't do that,
I guess I have to help you.
If what you're wanting to do
is take a swing at me,
we can take this into the ring
once we're done.
I meant, I wanna tape
your mouth shut.
But I heard you talk a big game
with your boxing.
And trust me, you don't want
a piece of this.
I don't just box, Harvey,
I kickbox.
And my leg is 50 times stronger
than your arm.
Picking fights
outside your weight class
is how you got into this mess
in the first place.
You wanna figure out how
to get out of it, or you wanna
make up fairy tales
about how you'd kick my ass?
I wanna figure out
how to get out of this.
We're gonna go upstairs
and order
an extra-large pepperoni
and cheese.
Because I might not
have picked this fight,
but there is no way I am letting
Eric "I Need a Haircut" Kaldor
get the better
of one of my people.
Hey.
Oh, what is this for?
For being by my side today.
Of course.
I told you that I would be.
Well, it really set me at ease.
And I have to say,
Chaz is so knowledgeable,
and his bedside manner
is a dream.
Right. He's the best.
We're gonna be swimming
in babies by the time
he's through with us.
Louis, what's wrong?
Chaz was my bully
in high school.
He tortured me
my entire junior year.
That's awful. Why didn't you
say something to me?
It was 30 years ago.
I'm not gonna let
something from high school
keep us from seeing
the best specialist.
We can find
whoever's second best.
No, we can't.
If it didn't work out,
I would never forgive myself.
I can handle it.
Are you sure?
Trust me, I'll be okay.
Carla, I got your message.
I came as soon as I could.
You need to use that retainer
we pay to buy a faster car.
I found out we no longer have
a distribution deal.
What are you talking about?
Our distributor
you said we had a deal with
called to say
they got a better offer.
If they have a competing offer
that fast, they've been
negotiating in bad faith.
I don't give a shit.
I wanna know
what you're gonna do about it.
The only way
they can break our deal
is if that signature
didn't get there.
If they try to back out...
Don't you get it?
There is no other reason.
They're saying that signature
never got there.
Carla, I'm telling you,
that signature got there,
and they're not backing out
of anything.
You'd better be right.
Because our future
is based on this expansion.
And like I said,
you told me it was a done deal.
Tell me you sent
Louis' signature over today.
I did. Why?
They're saying
they never got it.
That's some grade A bullshit.
The courier came and took it
this afternoon.
The courier failed to deliver...
Or these guys
are straight up lying.
I need you to get me a receipt.
Then you'll have it by tomorrow.
Don't worry.
We'll fix this.
Thanks, Gretchen.
I appreciate you
being all over this.
Hold on.
If we can prove you never had
any contact with Grayscale,
we can argue no privilege
relationship existed.
It's an idea.
Even if we subpoena
everybody from back then,
it's not in their interest
to clear me.
Plus, Kaldor could
still say it doesn't matter
because you saw
confidential information.
Goddamn that man.
All I wanted was to get Robert
another client.
No, you're a saint and all you
were doing was God's work.
All right,
you don't have to rub it in.
I do if we're gonna have
any fun tonight.
Speaking of fun...
It's late,
we just shared a pizza,
I have to ask:
What is it with you and Robert?
I'm not talking about
me and Robert with you.
You can tell Donna,
but you can't tell me?
You know we went out?
Of course I do.
I know everything.
Even the time
that you tried to...
No. You don't know anything.
You're trying to get me
to spill the beans
because Donna wouldn't.
So what if I am?
Hmm. That's exactly
what I said to you
when you called me out
on doing this because of Alex.
So what if I am?
Maybe we're more alike
than you thought, after all.
That's what you tried telling me
when you first got here
when you flipped me the bird.
As I recall,
you flipped it right back.
Yeah, well,
maybe we really are...
Wait a second.
More alike than we thought.
What if it's
not just you and me?
What have you got?
Kaldor.
He said the only way I could
get around the billing sheet
was to say I'd lied about it.
What if he's the one who lied,
and that sheet never existed?
Looks like someone needs to pay
a visit to Eric Kaldor.
You think you can handle it?
Why would I handle it?
Because...
You helped me
when you didn't have to,
and you just said
you wanted to have some fun.
What better way to have some fun
than sticking it to Eric Kaldor?
I get it.
You don't just wanna get
Robert a present.
You wanna get me personally
invested in your success.
So what if I do?
Okay, Samantha,
I'll take care of Eric.
But before we call it a night,
this idea came from you
suggesting you're like him.
And then, you started talking
about fabricating evidence.
The answer is no, Harvey.
I've never fabricated evidence
in my life.
Hi. I need a receipt
for a package
I sent with your service.
Of course.
What's your order number?
One-two-six-five-seven.
Our records show
that package was never sent.
Your records are wrong.
I sent it.
I'm sorry,
I don't know what to say.
Don't say anything.
Put me through to the courier.
If there's no record, talking
to him isn't gonna help.
Our couriers are extremely busy,
and I don't have time to...
Listen here, young lady.
You don't think I'm busy? I am.
But not too busy
to find out where you live,
your mother's maiden name,
and anything else it takes
to make your life a living hell
if you don't put me through
to that goddamn courier.
I'll see if I can connect him.
- Hello?
- Leroy.
Thank God, it's you.
Yep. It's me, all right.
I understand there is a problem.
There sure is.
I left a package for you
this afternoon on my desk.
I know you picked it up
because it's gone.
Sorry, Gretchen.
It wasn't there.
I waited around, like,
for 10 minutes.
I asked the receptionist.
She didn't have it, so I left.
Oh. Thank you, then, Leroy.
Thank... Thanks for your time.
Sorry to put you out.
No problem.
Shit.
Hello.
You must be Missy.
That's right.
And you are?
A friend of Sandy McClusky's.
The woman who used to
cover this desk?
I remember Sandy.
She trained me.
Well, tried to, anyway.
Sandy and I came up together
in the pool at Johnson Powell,
along with Rebecca Hart
and Pat Nichols.
We went through a lot together.
How does that have
anything to do with me?
Sandy owed me a favor
before she retired,
and I need to call it in.
So call her.
Well, she's in Coral Gables.
You're the one on this desk now,
so the favor falls to you.
I need you to log that you
received this yesterday.
The problem with that is
I didn't receive it yesterday.
It was an honest mistake.
Honest or not, it's yours.
Why should I cover for you?
Because Sandy owed me.
That's how we
take care of each other.
It's been going on
since before you were born.
And your chance to cash in that
favor walked out when she did.
Listen to me, young lady.
No, you listen to me.
You're asking me
to lie to my boss,
and I'm not gonna do it.
So instead of coming in here
trying to get me
to put my ass on the line
to honor
some 80-year-old tradition,
why don't you not screw up
in the first place?
You think you're hot shit,
and you don't need anyone.
Well, one day, you're gonna be
in the position that I'm in,
and you're gonna wish
like hell you had a network
of people to call on for help.
Maybe I will.
But something tells me by then,
you'll be long gone.
Harvey Specter.
Don't tell me.
You're picking up the case
I had Samantha booted off of,
and now I'm supposed to be
shaking with fear.
You think I'd let you off
that easy, Eric? Not a chance.
What?
There's an old saying.
Accuse the other side
of that which you are guilty.
Another old saying:
Get to the point.
You said Samantha lied
about that billing sheet.
Which got us thinking,
you lied about that sheet.
Samantha never worked
for Grayscale.
You say that again, and I will
have you sued for slander.
I won't say it.
I'll just prove it.
You gonna get me to admit
something I never did?
No, Eric. I'll subpoena
every bill ever sent
and every billing sheet
ever submitted by Samantha.
When they don't add up, we won't
need this case to move forward
because you'll be disbarred
for fabricated evidence.
There's no way
I have to hand over
proprietary records
to a competing firm.
You really wanna take
that chance over one client?
Let this go, Eric.
It's over.
So it's not enough you had
to take my partner
and half my business?
You have to come after the rest?
I didn't come after anything.
But as long as we're talking,
I didn't take your partner.
You went behind his back
to try to steal both our firms.
If you think this little
sob story's gonna move me,
you might as well pick up
a tissue, dab your eyes,
and tell it somewhere else.
And when you're finished,
you can call Grayscale
and let them know
they're now represented by me.
Gretchen.
What brings you to my office?
I need help.
Let me guess.
You're coming to me because
you heard I fix things.
I'm coming because
when Louis lost his mind on you,
you didn't run to Robert.
You went to Harvey because
you knew he needed a friend.
And right now,
you need a friend.
I screwed up big-time.
Didn't send a document
that needed to be sent,
and now Alex Williams
is gonna be in deep shit.
Gretchen, I may be good,
but I can't
travel back in time for you.
I know that.
I asked that goddamn secretary
to cover for me,
but she wouldn't honor the code.
So you want me
to make it look like
it's her fault and not yours.
That's right.
I'm sorry.
I... I can't do it.
Is this because I told you
it could hurt Alex?
This has nothing to do
with Alex.
I'm telling you this
because what it would take
to fix this thing could make it
a thousand times worse.
And being your friend means
telling you it is not worth it.
But Samantha...
No buts.
You need to go to Alex
and tell him the truth.
Because this is his client,
and he deserves to know.
Louis, what are you doing?
You're missing dinner.
It's sloppy joe night.
I'm not missing anything.
I'm writing a contract.
What? Is that your Civics
homework or something?
No, Esther. It's
a legally binding document,
stipulating that I'm required
to get even with Chaz
by the end of the school year.
Because he's putting you
in the locker.
Yes, Esther, that's what I mean.
Trust me, Louis.
Whatever you're
thinking of doing,
Chaz is just gonna
make your life worse.
Like you know about
dealing with a bully.
Believe me, I do.
Remember when I dropped out
of band last year?
When you told Mom
you couldn't stand
being associated with me?
What I couldn't stand
was Carolyn Price
picking on me every day.
I didn't know that.
Well, now you do.
So do you want my advice or not?
I want it.
Lay low, do what he wants,
and hope he forgets
you ever existed.
He's not going to forget,
and neither am I.
Louis, don't you get it?
Guys like Chaz always
get their way in high school.
But high school ends.
And before you know it,
you'll be successful,
and he'll be pumping your gas.
Oh, my God, you're right.
I'm not powerful enough
to face him now.
But some day, I'll show him.
No, Louis,
that's not what I meant.
Now, excuse me. I need
to read over my contract.
Carla, let me
call you right back.
I think what we needed
just walked into my office.
She still pissed?
She won't be, once you
hand over that receipt.
That's just it, Alex.
There isn't one.
Come again? I never sent
the documents over.
Are you shitting me? You're
coming to me with this now?
I just realized last night
what happened.
Why didn't you come
to me last night?
I thought I could fix it.
No, no.
Let's just review.
After you gave me
bullshit about "Good morning.
You look lovely,"
you lied to my face.
It wasn't a lie. When I
found out, I tried to fix it.
Well, you didn't. When Carla
finds out this was on me...
It's my fault.
I'll take the bullet.
Take the bullet?
They're not gonna give a shit
whose fault this is.
It's my client.
It's on my head.
Is there anything I can do?
Yeah. From now on, do what
you say you're gonna do.
And if for some reason
you don't,
at least have the courage to
tell me before it's too late.
I know we demanded the client,
but I never imagined
you'd hand-deliver them.
The only thing I'm delivering,
Samantha, is an ultimatum.
The thing about giving
ultimatums, Eric,
is that you need to have
the upper hand.
You don't.
I thought that too.
Then I thought about
what Harvey said.
Accuse the other side
of that which you are guilty.
And I think
that's what you did to me.
Sorry to disappoint you,
but I have never fabricated
any evidence.
No, but you buried some.
Corman Ventures.
That was just a personal case
I took care of
as a favor to Robert.
I think you broke the law
to do it.
You don't know what
you're talking about.
Maybe not.
But Betty Palmer does.
See, it always bothered me,
the circumstances
around her leaving.
So I decided to give her a call.
Bullshit.
There's no way
she talked to you.
Why don't you stroll down
to Coral Gables to find out?
When you're finished,
if you don't want her
telling the world
what she told me,
you'll hand over
your oldest client.
I'm not gonna just hand over
my oldest client to you.
Well, I think you will.
Because you put me
in front of a judge...
"Your Honor, I didn't
fabricate anything.
Someone must have made
a clerical error."
She has got you dead to rights.
No. It's her word
against mine.
Well... Like Harvey said,
you know, you really wanna
take that chance over
one piece of business?
I'll expect my new client's
information by tomorrow.
How are you doing, Louis?
A little nervous.
You?
Sheila. Louis.
Thank you for coming in.
We're surprised you asked us
to come back so soon.
Well, I didn't wanna
concern you, but...
Oh, God. Is there something
wrong with my test results?
It's nothing we can't handle.
You have cervical fibroids
that, unfortunately,
your OB missed.
And I'd like to remove them.
You... You mean like surgery?
It's just a simple outpatient
laparoscopic procedure.
I've done it hundreds of times.
Okay, then,
I think we should do it.
I'll set something up
in the next two weeks...
Hold on a minute.
Maybe we should get
a second opinion.
You're welcome to get
But I think we should
schedule the surgery now.
That way, we have it
on the books.
For the record, this is my area
of expertise. I think that...
If you know
what's good for you,
you'll get in that locker.
Litt, I could punch you
before you get in
or you could just get in.
Aren't you forgetting something?
Well, Louis, what do you think
of that plan?
I don't give a shit
what your area of expertise is.
We're not gonna schedule
a goddamn thing
with you now or ever.
And if you lay one hand
on the woman I love,
I swear to God,
I'll beat the shit out of you.
Well, Louis...
what do you think of that plan?
I see no reason why
we need a second opinion.
We'll do whatever you say.
Great, then,
it's all settled.
Hey, Samantha.
Donna, whatever it is,
I'm kind of busy.
I can see that.
Does it have to do
with why you pushed three client
meetings at the last minute?
I didn't realize you kept
tabs on my calendar.
I don't.
When those clients get
brushed off by their lawyer,
I'm the one they call.
I told them
those meetings will be back
as soon as I'm back
from my trip.
What trip? You haven't
submitted a travel request.
And I won't be,
because this is personal.
Okay, does this have to do with
Eric Kaldor coming here today?
It has to do with me
needing to get down to Florida
and you not telling anyone.
Samantha.
Donna, just let me do what I do.
Let me get this straight.
You want me to keep something
from Harvey and Robert
that might blow up
in their faces
without telling me what it is?
Yes. I do.
I'm not sure I can do that.
You know what, Donna?
You wanna tell someone,
go ahead.
Doesn't matter, 'cause
I'm getting on that plane.
Okay, go ahead
and catch your plane.
I just hope you know
what you're doing.
Whatever you're up
to, it's not gonna happen.
'Cause you're not getting
on that plane.
Donna told you.
Damn right, Donna told me.
I don't believe it.
She led me to think that I...
When I asked you
if you fabricated evidence,
you said you hadn't,
and I believed you.
But now I think you have.
Harvey.
I think you fabricated evidence,
Kaldor is using it
to blackmail you,
and you're about to head to
wherever you're going
to stop it.
Are you finished?
Am I right?
I didn't lie to you.
And I never fabricated evidence.
What the hell's going on here?
Five years ago,
we had a case. Criminal.
One of our CEO's adult children
was charged
with attempted murder.
The pharmaceutical guy's daughter.
That's the one.
And I did what it took
to get her out of it.
And what exactly did it take?
I buried evidence.
I can't believe...
Before you say...
You let a guilty woman off.
She wasn't guilty,
and I know it.
That's exactly what
my old mentor sounded like
when it ended up
that he put away a man
for a murder he didn't commit.
Well, I'm not him.
I'm not gonna apologize
for doing what I had to.
I don't give a shit
if you apologize.
We're gonna fix this.
Damn right, we are.
We're gonna fix it
by putting Betty Palmer on ice.
Who the hell is Betty Palmer?
The woman I got rid of
from Rand Kaldor
who tried to stop me
from doing what I did.
Eric found her.
You know what?
I don't care who she is.
We're gonna fix this
by you giving them your client.
There is no way I am
giving one of my clients
to the man who stabbed
Robert in the back.
There's no way I'm letting you
do God knows what
to a woman who tried to stop you
from breaking the law.
Goddamn it. You...
That's enough!
Give him your client now,
or I swear to God,
I'll hand you in
for burying evidence myself.
I wanted to say something,
to tell him I don't trust him,
to tell him I hate him.
Anything.
But I didn't.
I just...
sat there... took it.
Louis.
I'd like to try
an exercise with you.
What kind of exercise?
Close your eyes.
Now,
imagine you are walking
down that hallway with Chaz
to the locker.
I don't want to.
Trust me.
Just try it.
And Louis, I'd like you
to envision yourself
not as a young person,
but as you are now.
So.
Tell me what you see.
It's horrible.
I wanna stop walking,
but I can't.
My legs just keep going.
I see people looking.
Some are laughing.
Some don't give a shit.
The worst are the ones
who pity me.
We get to the gym.
It's empty.
We walk up
to the equipment locker.
He opens the door.
I can't stop my hand.
I give him his homework.
I don't wanna go in there,
but I just don't have it in me
to fight anymore.
Louis, I need you
to go into that locker.
- I don't wanna.
- I know.
Okay.
Louis, one more thing.
Okay, he's in
here with me now.
Good. Now, what
would you like to say to him?
- I don't know.
- Louis.
I am telling you, I don't know.
I do. You signed a contract with
me and you didn't live up to it.
I wanted to. But I couldn't.
Why not?
Because it's not just
about my feelings anymore.
It's about Sheila,
our future, having a baby.
What good is having a baby
if you can't protect it?
That's not fair.
If I lashed out at Chaz,
I'd ruin our chance
at having a child to protect.
Bullshit.
That's just an excuse.
You didn't say anything to Chaz
because you were afraid.
That's not true.
You gave me your word.
The word of a stupid teenager
that didn't understand.
I grew up!
You didn't do anything
except let him
humiliate us again.
Like you swore
you would never do.
You're right.
I did.
I was afraid.
I'm still afraid.
I'll always be afraid.
No, Louis, you won't.
You don't have to be
afraid of Chaz anymore.
Why not?
Because I just remembered
another promise
we made to ourselves when
we were all alone in here.
You mean, if no one was looking,
we should just start...
Not that one.
Don't judge.
We were in here a long time.
I mean, we were
in here in the dark,
wondering if we'd ever get out.
We started to cry.
And we made a promise
to ourself that one day,
if we ever have children,
we'd teach our son
to treat people with respect
and to never, ever be like Chaz.
I'd forgotten that.
So did I.
Until you just admitted
you were afraid too.
If you don't mind, I'd like
to break that contract
so I can keep that promise.
I don't mind.
So it's a deal?
Deal.
Jesus, so this is
where it comes from.
Hey, look at that.
The door's open.
Come on. What do you say
we get out of here?
I don't know what to say, Stan.
I never would have remembered
that promise without you.
I just helped you see
that a part of you
has always still been
in that locker.
And what you needed was someone
to be in there with you.
You mean you.
No, Louis.
I mean you.
Stop right there.
I wanna take this in.
Samantha Wheeler coming in
to kiss my ring.
I'm not kissing shit.
I'm coming to give you this.
My ring or my ass,
I don't care.
I win either way.
No. Betty Palmer wins.
She's the one who's gonna
represent this client.
You wanna try that again?
I said, Betty is the one
getting this client.
And the only reason
I'm bringing their file here
instead of to her office
is because
I don't think the one
you gave her is big enough
for someone who's about
to make Senior Partner.
I don't think you quite
get how losing works.
You see, you don't get
to dictate the terms...
I didn't lose, Eric.
I chose not to fight anymore.
But I could change my mind.
Bullshit.
You're trying to ease your guilt
about screwing over a woman
who was trying
to do the right thing.
You're right, I am.
And you have no idea
how much losing this client
is gonna cost me.
But Betty does.
Which means she'd be more than
happy to dig through your files
and find my original
billing sheet.
You know, the one that can get
you kicked out of the bar?
Eric, you said
if I brought the client over,
this would be over.
It's not my fault
you're a shitty negotiator.
So make Betty
a Senior Partner and move on,
or this firm is gonna lose
another name off its wall.
And this time, it'll be yours.
Gretchen, can I
talk to you for a second?
- Don't tell me.
- You were right.
They did demand
that Alex fire you.
He refused.
No. Mm-mm.
I can't let that happen.
What?
I'm going to tell Robert
it was my fault. I'll retire.
Maybe that'll save Alex his client.
What happened
was as much my fault as yours.
Alex was right.
I-I should've
followed up with Leroy.
It was a simple mistake.
And I should have
been able to fix it!
I tried to call in
every favor I could.
That woman laughed me
out of the office.
And I always told myself
when I ran out of juice,
I'd hang it up.
Well, turns out
I'm squeezed dry.
Gretchen, I can't tell you
when it's time.
But I can tell you that
it took Mike going to prison
for Harvey to learn that
some mistakes can't be fixed.
And I'll tell you
something else.
The night that Mike went away,
Harvey thought about
hanging it up too.
But if he tapped out, he
couldn't fight to get Mike out,
and deep down, he knew
that he still had
a lot of fight left in him.
What if I don't?
You wouldn't be telling me
this if you didn't.
Because offering to retire
is just another way
of fighting to fix it.
How am I supposed to look
Alex in the eye tomorrow?
You just do it.
And it will be okay.
Because someone who would
offer to pack it in for him
doesn't come around very often.
In fact, when he finds out,
I bet he is in my office
bright and early,
saying you should get a raise.
You saying you're willing
to give me a raise?
No. You just lost this firm
a huge client.
Thanks, Red.
I hope that when you're
thinking about packing it in,
you have someone like you
to talk you out of it too.
Gretchen.
Get yourself on over here.
Hey.
Is it done?
It's done.
For what it's worth,
we threw some good punches.
It just doesn't feel that way.
Well, maybe that's a good thing.
How's that?
Because the next time
Kaldor comes around,
you're gonna remember
how this felt.
What do you say we hit the gym
and go a few rounds?
Not tonight.
Why not?
Because I'd feel bad that I lost
a client, and I'd let you win.
And I don't wanna let you win.
You really think
you can beat me, don't you?
I know I can.
Isn't that what you thought
about Eric Kaldor?
That's different,
and you know it.
Let me tell you
something, Samantha.
I never thought I could lose
until Mike Ross went to prison.
I still don't ever think
I'm gonna lose.
But I know in the back of
my mind that, one time, I did.
It's just a thought.
I'll keep that in mind.
Goodnight, Harvey.
Goodnight, Samantha.
Harvey.
Just so you know,
if I had another chance
to keep an innocent woman out
of prison, I'd do it again.
That's between you
and your maker.
But if there is a next time,
how about you make sure
there aren't any Betty Palmers?
www.tvsubtitles.net