Previously on "Suits"...
I'm here because
I want you to come home.
Back to the firm?
Yes, and not only that,
you can get the ten
best associates
from Robert Zane's
stable to come with you.
And what's in this for me?
I'll make sure that you are
the youngest senior partner
we've ever had.
As of this morning,
we're merging with Robert Zane.
When I came over,
you said my name
would be the
one to go up next.
You have my word.
Your name goes up next.
Alex, what are you doing?
I'm going through every one
of Samantha Wheeler's files,
'cause a fight's coming,
and I'm gonna be ready.
Katrina, are you sure
you're gonna be okay
firing people
you've worked with for years?
I'll tell you
what I told Louis,
that if I'm going to grow
in my role here,
this is something I'm going
to have to learn to do.
I gave you an order,
and you blatantly ignored me.
I did do what you
originally asked:
to objectively evaluate
the associates.
I don't care.
Brian is staying.
Gavin Andrews is a hell of a
lot more than meets the eye.
And a guy with your history
would want to be more careful
about who he gets
into bed with.
Tell me what
you're talking about,
or get out
of my goddamn office.
I admit I'm starting to see
what you see in her.
That's all I was hoping for.
Now I can tell you
why I was hoping it.
What haven't you told me?
Her name goes
up on the wall next.
I mean,
how was I supposed to know
she was married?
- I don't know,
maybe her wedding ring
could have tipped you off.
Mm.
I was 23, you know?
I wasn't looking
at no damn rings.
You really had some balls
when you were younger.
Still do,
thank you very much.
Now, why don't you get to it?
- Why don't I get to what?
- Harvey, you've got plenty
of friends to have drinks with,
most of them prettier than me.
You've got something
on your mind.
Let's hear it.
- Robert, do you remember
when you told me
you promised Samantha
her name would go up next?
- I do.
I made Alex the same promise.
- Why you telling me now?
- Because we're partners.
I don't want to keep
any secrets from my partner.
Then I guess there's only
one thing to do.
- What's that?
- Kick the can down the road.
Because there's no way
both of us are gonna be able
to keep that promise,
and for all we know,
one of them could get hit
by a bus before we have
to make that call.
- Then I guess
it's a good thing
both our names
are already up there.
- Sure is.
- Another drink?
- Yeah, make it a double.
And where are you going?
To make room for that double.
Excuse me, would you mind
giving me a minute to...?
Oh, I'm so sorry, I--
I didn't hear you come in.
Um, I'll just go.
- Are you all right?
Uh, yeah.
I, um--I just got a phone call.
Um, it's not important.
Excuse me.
- No, you stay.
I'll use the one downstairs.
Take as long as you need.
For what it's worth...
I hope everything's okay.
Thank you.
What are you doing
in my home?
I'm here because I have a way
to get your Renoir back,
but I'm gonna need something
from you.
- And what exactly is that?
- Give your ex the villa
in Bordeaux, and guarantee
she never pays a nickel
of upkeep.
- And why would I do that?
Because you asked me
to get that painting back
and this is the only way
that's gonna happen.
No, I mean
why would I do that
when your firm is about
to sign my biggest competitor?
- What are you talking about?
- I just learned
Samantha Wheeler's about
to sign Delta.
- God damn it.
- See, I thought
I made it clear
that if I sign with you
it is because I trust you.
Using me as a stalking horse
doesn't make me feel like
I can trust you.
- Gavin, that's not
what's going on here.
- I told you,
that painting
is personal to me.
I'm gonna tell you why.
My father was not
a wealthy man,
but he had an education.
If there's one thing
he appreciated
more than anything, it was art.
Every Sunday, we'd go
to a different gallery.
We'd walk through--
he would tell me
everything he knew
about every painting there was.
You know who
his favorite artist was?
Renoir.
I paid $8 million
for that painting.
It's worth twice that now,
but I would never sell it...
because every time
I look at it...
I think of him.
Gavin, I told you
I'll get that painting back
and I will.
And I'll tell you
something else--
There's no way
Samantha Wheeler's signing
Delta goddamn Airlines.
Thanks.
Alex, what a pleasant surprise.
Cut the bullshit.
I just found out you're going
after Delta Airlines.
Not just going after,
it's practically a done deal.
That was fast,
since you only talked to Delta
after you found out
I was pursuing Gavin Andrews.
One had nothing
to do with the other.
And I said cut the bullshit.
You did this because you knew
you'd either sign Delta
and I'd be out in the cold,
or Gavin Andrews
would accuse me of using him
as a stalking horse
and I'd be out in the cold.
- If you're so sure of that,
then what are you doing
standing here
ruining my morning bagel?
- I'm here to tell you
to back the hell off.
Well, that's not
gonna happen.
Listen to me.
I don't know
how you did things before,
but around here,
we don't stab each other
in the back.
- Then what do you call
going after my old client
for the sole purpose
of making me look bad?
Because I'm not gonna
let that slide.
Not to mention I warned you
Gavin Andrews
isn't worth the trouble.
You don't want to look bad,
or the client's
too much trouble?
Which one is it?
- It's both,
and if you can't see that
then it's not my problem.
What I see is you standing
between me and a client,
and if I were you, I'd get
the hell out of the way.
Well, then you'd better
sign your guy fast,
because I'm already on
the one-yard line with mine
and I'm about to punch it in.
♪ Suits 8x03 ♪
Promises Promises
Original Air Date on August 1, 2018
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ I'll even eat a bean pie,
I don't mind ♪
♪ Me and Missy is so busy,
busy making money ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ All step back,
I'm 'bout to dance ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
♪ The greenback boogie ♪
Hey.
Good morning, Robert.
- It will be
once this damn hangover
wears off.
- Out late last night, yo?
- Uh, no, I was here
forgetting my age
and matching Harvey
drink for drink.
Now, what can I do for you?
- Robert, you know,
if you're hungover, I can whip
up my nana's special remedy.
I just need some sugar, tea,
a little steamed milk,
and, of course,
two of my cuticles.
Thanks, but I'd rather
have the hangover.
It's about the tea, isn't it?
Because she's from
the old country
and I can substitute--
- Louis.
What in God's name
did you come in here for?
Okay. Robert.
The other day
when I was feeling left out,
you and Harvey let me know
that you clocked me.
Well, I realized
that there's someone
that I haven't been clocking.
- What are you talking about?
- When I brought Katrina over
from you, I told her
that she was gonna be
the youngest senior partner
in firm history,
and I want
to fulfill that promise.
Now, let me
get this straight:
you're holding me
to a promise you made to her
so that you could steal her
from me.
Robert, that's not the point
and you know it.
Katrina is a great lawyer,
and it's time.
Maybe it is time,
but senior partner
isn't just "lawyering," Louis.
It's about managing people,
and I don't know
how good Katrina Bennett is
with people.
Well, then you tell me.
What can she do
to prove herself to you?
Excuse me, Mr. Specter?
- I know you, you're--
- From last night.
I, uh...
wanted to return this.
You were very kind.
Thank you.
It's nothing.
I was just hoping
everything was okay.
- Actually,
that's the reason
that I'm here.
- What do you mean?
- I was upset last night
because I got a call
from my mother.
She needs an operation,
and I can't afford it.
What are you asking me?
I've worked
enough overtime hours
to make having
that operation possible,
but they won't pay me overtime
because my title
is Facilities Manager.
I don't manage anything.
I was hoping maybe...
- I'd be able
to get you your money.
- Yes.
- Listen, Miss...?
- Anna.
Anna Reed.
- Anna, your employer
is my landlord,
so if I get involved
things could get
very complicated.
But it's a simple matter
of paying me for my work.
If that were true,
why would he listen to me
when he didn't listen to you?
Because people like me
don't matter
to people like them.
I'm just the lady
that cleans their toilet.
Please, Mr. Specter.
I'm not proud
to ask you for this
but my mother needs this,
and when it comes
to taking care of people
we love,
pride has no place.
Okay.
I can't promise anything,
but I'll try.
Thank you.
I knew you were kind.
Don't tell me you're dating
the cleaning woman now.
- And what if I was?
- I'd say congratulations.
But why don't you tell me
why she was here.
I ran into her
in the bathroom last night.
She was crying.
The building isn't paying her
what she's owed,
and she asked me
to look into it.
You mean, she asked you
to pick a fight
with our landlord,
who I shouldn't have
to tell you
is a mean son of a bitch,
and this is a bad idea.
- Robert, I'm not an idiot,
and I'm not picking any fights
with David Fox.
I'm gonna talk to the man
for two minutes.
If he doesn't see it my way,
that's it.
Trust me.
Okay, Harvey.
I trust you.
There you are.
Been looking all over for you.
Louis, if there's any chance
whatever it is can wait...
It can't.
I need you to supervise
Brian Altman.
- What?
Louis, I am in the middle
of a case,
and there is a huge meeting
in an hour.
Well, then have him
help you with it.
I don't need any help,
and I can't
be mentoring someone right now.
It's not mentoring;
it's managing.
Then have someone else
manage him.
Damn it, Katrina,
this is your chance
to be senior partner.
- Oh, my God.
- That's right.
I just talked to Robert Zane
about making good
on my promise to you.
and I shouldn't even
be telling you this--
no one can know.
He's on board
as long as you can show
that you are a manager.
Okay, uh...
Look, then just do me a favor.
Please just tell Brian
to familiarize himself
with Bigelow Textiles
and meet me
in the conference room
in 45 minutes.
Katrina,
is something going on?
Why would something
be going on?
I don't know,
'cause I just told you
that your dreams
are coming true
and it looks like
you ate a bad clam.
I'm sorry, Louis.
This is amazing news.
I'm just crunched for time.
So, please, just tell Brian
to be there
and I will handle him
from here on out.
Okay, I'll let him know.
David Fox.
I'm Harvey Specter.
Of, uh, Something,
Something, Specter Litt?
Don't tell me
us changing our name
is gonna be an issue again.
- No, it's not.
Donna Paulsen saw to that
in your new lease.
Well, Donna has a way
of getting what she wants.
Speaking of what people want,
why don't you tell me
why you're here.
- I need your help.
There's a cleaning woman
on our floor
who can't afford to pay
her mother's medical bills.
Turns out technically
she's a facilities manager,
which means she's not eligible
to make overtime.
A maid
with a manager's title.
I mean, sounds to me
like she's being empowered.
You and I both know
that title is just a way
to get around paying
what she's earned.
- I don't know any such thing.
- Oh, bullshit.
She's your employee.
- Wrong.
I contract
all my cleaning services out
to another company,
a company I don't run.
You're gonna tell me
that company is anything more
than a piece of paper
and a PO Box?
Why don't you pay them
a visit and find out?
Listen, David,
all I'm asking
is do the right thing.
Pay her for her work.
- You know,
why don't you reach
into your own pocket?
'Cause that's what
you're asking me to do.
And I do this for her,
I gotta do it for everyone.
And if you don't
do it for her,
you will have to do it
for everyone.
You'd better watch
what you say to me,
'cause in case you forgot,
you're still living
under my roof.
- And if you don't back off,
I'll take that roof
and everything else you have,
because you just violated
half-a-dozen laws
by threatening a tenant.
- You want to take me on,
you go for it,
'cause I didn't get where I am
by letting people like you
push me around.
Last time,
Donna kicked your ass.
Well, I'm not Donna,
so you pay my client
what you owe her.
- Alex.
- We need to talk
about Samantha Wheeler.
- What does that mean?
- It means she's making a play
for Delta Airlines,
and I want you to stop her.
Delta would be a huge client;
why would I want to stop her?
Because she only went
after them to stop me
from signing Gavin Andrews,
and team mates
don't do that to each other.
This team mate talk
sounds great,
but you just went after
one of her old clients.
I didn't choose Gavin
because he was hers.
I chose Gavin because
he was the most valuable client
to Robert Zane.
The fact that he was hers
just wasn't gonna stop me.
Wasn't gonna stop you,
or was icing on the cake?
What difference
does that make?
Well, considering
what you're asking me to do,
it makes all the difference.
- Louis, after Zane ended up
as managing partner
I wanted to take her on,
but you said I should make
a friend of Zane instead.
So I went after Gavin
to impress Robert,
and if you're not
gonna stop her, I might as well
just have gone after her
in the first place.
All right, Alex, okay.
But giving up a client
with eight-figure billables
is going out on one hell
of a limb, so I do this,
you better deliver
Gavin Andrews.
I will, Louis.
You have my word.
Samantha Wheeler.
You and I need
to have a little chat.
Louis Litt.
To what do I owe the pleasure?
- Oh, you know who I am.
- Well, a man like yourself
needs no introduction.
- That is very kind of you,
but I'm not here for you
to blow smoke up my ass.
Let me guess:
Alex realized
he wasn't gonna stop me
on his own.
He realized
that you were trying
to undermine him, which is why
I'm here to tell you
that you're gonna stop
pursuing Delta.
I don't believe this.
Are you seriously
coming in here to tell me
I can't sign one of the world's
biggest airlines?
Yeah, I am.
And this isn't a discussion;
it's an order.
I hope you've had a chance
to think long
and hard about this.
Because I'd be careful
what you wish for.
You trying to intimidate me?
Just giving you
a little advice.
Well, listen here,
sweet face.
I get it.
You're the it girl.
Well, you know who I am?
I'm Litt man.
And you can try to sashay
your six-foot frame around here
like you're Brigitte Nielsen
in 1985--
turn me into a puddle,
get me to capitulate.
Well, I got news for you:
it's not gonna happen.
All right.
I'll drop Delta.
I knew you'd see things
my way.
But someday...
you're gonna come asking
for a favor.
Might not be today,
might not be tomorrow,
but it's gonna happen...
and when it does...
I'm gonna remember
this conversation.
And Louis?
If you think I couldn't
turn you into a puddle,
you are wildly mistaken.
So we're clear.
You'll drop the client.
I have to go somewhere now.
- Mm.
I'm sure you do.
Brian.
What's going on?
You look lost.
I'm not lost.
I'm just under the gun.
Have you seen Katrina?
- No, why?
Bigelow Textiles
is in the conference room
and the meeting was scheduled
for five minutes ago.
I don't know what to do.
- Easy.
Katrina's never missed
a meeting in her life.
If she's not there,
she will be.
Just go ahead and start.
- Thing is, I just got
the case an hour ago.
I'm hazy on the particulars
at best.
I think I should cancel.
- I don't think
that's a good idea.
- But what happens
if I start the meeting
and she doesn't show up at all?
And what happens
when you cancel the meeting
and she shows up
three minutes later?
- Donna--
- Brian, look.
I know your value,
and I believe
that Katrina knows your value,
but the truth is,
not too long ago,
you were on the chopping block.
If you've been invited in
on this case,
you're being offered
another chance.
And canceling a meeting
that Katrina's running
a little late to isn't the way
to prove myself.
No, it's not.
You're right.
I'll get it going.
Harvey.
Is there a reason
why the 49th floor toilets
have been backed up?
- Why would I know that?
Because when I called
to have it fixed, they said
they couldn't get to it
for another four hours
and in the mean time,
maybe you could
take a look at it.
Son of a bitch.
You, you, you.
Drop what you're doing
and meet me
in the conference room.
- We're working on something...
I don't give a shit
what you're working on.
Conference room, five minutes.
Harvey.
Donna, I'm in the middle
of something.
I can see that.
Do you mind telling me
what that something has to do
with those toilets?
It has to do with the fact
that David Fox wants a fight
and I'm gonna give him one.
- A fight about what?
He doesn't want to pay
our cleaning woman overtime.
Hang on, so you're pulling
the associates
off the Vistech merger
to help her?
Fine, you want me to use
different associates?
I will.
- I don't care
what associates you're using;
I want to explain to you
that David Fox is no joke.
And as noble as it sounds,
you don't want
to get in a fight with him
over something like this.
I know that, Donna.
That's what I said to Zane.
- But...
- But what?
Harvey, this isn't what we do.
- Mike would have done it.
And Mike's not here anymore
because he finally came
came to terms with the fact
that this isn't what we do.
Look, if you told Zane
you knew this wasn't worth it,
then you already know
I'm right.
Okay, Donna.
You're right.
Tell those associates
to get back to whatever
they were working on.
Mr. Bigelow, nice to meet you.
I'm sorry we're running
a little late.
I'm Brian Altman.
- Where the hell's Katrina?
I'm sure
she'll be right here.
In the mean time,
can I offer you--
No, no, no.
I don't have time
for the meantime.
If Ms. Bennett can't bother
showing up on time,
she can play catch-up
when she gets here.
Okay, I see you're
in a hurry.
Let's go through the report
from the top.
I don't need you
to read me the damn report.
What I need are some answers.
Um, all right.
What do you want to know?
What kind of exposure
are we looking at, here?
Well, Kineserve claims
you improperly broke
your contract,
but the board minutes
don't indicate any bad faith
on your part.
That's the good news.
- And the bad news?
The minutes don't show
any discussion of good cause
for terminating
the contract, either.
No good cause?
Did you see
the delivery manifests?
Um, I'd have to take
another look at them
before weighing in.
- Another look?
What about
the stress test results?
Right.
Let me just find that.
- You haven't even read
all the goddamn minutes,
have you?
I must have
just missed that part.
If you'd just let me find it...
I can see
what's going on, here.
Katrina didn't think
I was worthy of her attention,
so she pawned me off
on some incompetent,
second-rate associate.
- Mr. Bigelow, I can assure you
that is not the case.
Katrina values your business
very much,
and I am
a fully capable attorney.
Not from what I see.
And if I can't be handled
by a competent attorney,
I don't see why I should
be handled by this firm at all.
Please, Mr. Bigelow.
Um, if we could just reset,
I think we got off
on the wrong foot.
- You wanna reset?
Get your shit together,
'cause I'm not about
to sit here and watch you
bumble your way
through something you're
clearly not prepared for.
And the next time
you call me in for a meeting
without Katrina Bennett,
don't bother
calling me in at all.
I don't believe this.
- Brian...
- No, you sent me in
to a meeting by myself,
and you're, what?
Out taking a stroll
around the park?
- Please, not now.
- Yes, now, because I just got
my ass handed to me
by your client.
I wasn't taking a stroll;
I was in the bathroom
in a stall
because it's the only place
in this entire building
that's dark and quiet.
- What are you talking about?
- I had a migraine.
One of the worst I've ever had.
And when it was time
for the meeting
I opened the door,
but even with the sunglasses
the light made it feel
like there were icicles
in my head,
and I couldn't leave.
Brian, I'm so sorry.
I had no idea
you get migraines.
I haven't had one
since high school.
They're triggered by stress.
- You mean like the stress
of having to fire
a bunch of associates.
They started the day after.
- You need to tell Louis.
- No.
Louis is the last person
who can know about this.
Why would you want
to hide this from him?
Because you don't get
nine shots at senior partner;
you get one.
You're up
for senior partner.
I am.
No one is supposed to know
about this, not even me.
And if suddenly I start
getting migraines
that make it seem
like I can't handle the job...
No one's gonna find out
anything from me.
But Bigelow is pretty pissed.
- Well, Bigelow isn't going
to be at the motion
to dismiss tomorrow,
so as long as I win that,
we'll be fine.
In the meantime, I'd better
go face the music with Louis.
Brian, you don't have
to do that.
If I don't,
he's gonna find out
about your migraines.
Be direct.
Tell him you're sorry.
He might not be happy,
but he'll respect you.
Brian.
If ever there were any doubt
about you being
a valuable associate...
there isn't anymore.
- Anna, it's Harvey Specter.
- Mr. Specter.
I didn't expect
to hear from you so soon.
Does this mean that--
- I'm afraid
it's not gonna work.
- What?
I tried talking to them,
and there's nothing I can do.
You mean you don't want
to make a problem
for your firm.
- No.
Anna...
there's another firm out there
I can recommend to you.
I can't afford
to pay another firm.
You wouldn't have to.
Look, the guy who used
to do cases like this
doesn't work here anymore,
but he used to work
at a clinic, and I'm talking
about setting you up there.
I should have known
you'd pawn me off.
- I'm not pawning you off.
I promise, I will go down there
and make sure one
of the two lawyers I know
handles this personally.
Okay.
If you trust this firm,
then I trust you.
I'll be in touch.
Yes, absolutely.
I agree 100%.
Never again.
Hey, Louis, can I talk
to you for a second?
Sure as hell can,
'cause I wanna know
what the ---- happened
in that meeting.
- That's what I came--
- You know what, never mind.
I don't need to hear it,
because I just got
off the phone
with John Bigelow,
and he tells me
that you couldn't answer
a goddamn question.
- I know that, and I just--
He also says, and I quote,
"I never want
to be in another meeting
with Brian Altman again."
I--I'm sorry, Louis.
I'm sorry.
You're sorry?
That's all you have
to say for yourself?
Because you just
let down Katrina.
Do you understand
what I'm saying to you?
- I do.
- I do not think that you do.
Because she wanted to fire you,
Brian, and I wouldn't let her.
Then she gives you
a second chance,
and you do this?
What the hell is your excuse,
Brian?
Do you just suck at your job,
or are you actively trying
to undermine
a direct supervisor?
- I guess I suck at my job.
- Something like this
ever happens again,
forget about being fired.
You're gonna wish
you were never born.
Now get out, because right now
John Bigelow isn't the only one
who never wants
to see your face again.
Hi, can I help you?
Is Nathan Krueger here?
Nathan's in Philadelphia
on a case.
- How about Oliver Grady?
- Oliver's out with a client.
Is there something
I can help you with?
No, thanks.
Can I tell them
who stopped by?
It's okay; I've taken enough
of your time.
- Is that what I think it is?
- Renoir.
Signed, sealed, and delivered.
Mind telling me
how you pulled it off?
Absolutely, as soon
as you hand me
a signed engagement letter.
You know what,
I'm gonna do you one better.
Why don't you take out
your phone and check out
the latest edition
of the "Journal."
I don't believe it.
You issued an announcement
saying we're
your new attorneys.
I told you, you're my guy,
and I don't mind
the world knowing it.
- So where do you want this?
- I don't give a shit,
'cause it's not
gonna be here long.
What?
I'm shipping it
to the Cayman Islands
where a certain
airline company's
gonna pay me $55 million
for it.
I thought you said
it was only worth 16,
and that you'd never sell it.
Well, that's the thing
about art:
the value is in the eye
of the beholder.
I want you to behold this.
You want me on-shore
55 million from a blind trust
in the Caymans?
Gavin, I have to tell you,
this looks a hell of lot
like laundering money.
- Well, then it's a good thing
you don't know that for sure,
because if you don't know it
you can do it,
and you're going to do it.
I get it.
You gave me a bullshit story
about this thing
having sentimental value
to rope me in.
then you put out
an announcement saying
we're your attorneys.
And now, if I don't do this,
you drop us
and the world thinks
we shit the bed
inside of a day.
You catch on quick.
- I'm not doing it.
- Maybe you will,
maybe you won't.
But you'd better think about
how you're gonna explain
to Robert Zane
how you signed me and lost me
inside of two days.
There you are.
I've been waiting for you
to give me something to do.
There isn't much left to do,
so I'm handling it myself.
Katrina, come on,
there's a ton of work left.
I can see you're still in pain.
There must be something
I can do.
I'll be fine.
What if I turned
all the lights on?
Would you be fine then?
Katrina, 'cause that's
what it's gonna be like
in court tomorrow.
- Brian.
I heard what happened
with Louis,
and I'm not going
to let that happen again.
Listen to me.
I knew what I signed up for
when I said I'd keep
your situation a secret.
- And I appreciate it.
And now I'm going
to go into court tomorrow
and do the best I can.
Katrina, you gave me
a second chance,
and when you did,
you admitted you were wrong.
Not everyone would do that.
And someone that would
is exactly the kind of person
I want to have leading me
as a senior partner.
So if you won't let me
do this for you,
at least let's do it together.
Okay, Brian.
We'll do it together.
Alex, whatever it is,
I'm meeting a client
for dinner.
- That's okay,
I just have one question.
Did you know?
- Know what?
That Gavin Andrews
was gonna ask me
to launder money for him.
I don't believe it.
You knew it the whole time.
No, I didn't.
But I knew he was gonna
ask you to do something.
Then you and I
are gonna go upstairs
and figure out how
to get out of this, right now.
Are you out of your mind?
I'm not going anywhere near
that man's account.
Yes, you are,
because you knew my history
and you let me
sign him anyway.
Are you fucking kidding me?
I brought up your history.
And you knew I was
in no position to trust you.
And what I was I supposed
to do about that?
You could have given me
some goddamn specifics.
'Cause there's no way
you didn't have something
that would have convinced me
you were telling the truth.
And how was I supposed
to trust you wouldn't use
whatever I said against me?
- I wouldn't do that.
Oh?
So if I had said,
"Hey, Alex,
don't sign this guy.
He's gonna ask you
to cover up a murder."
You weren't gonna use that?
Is that what he asked you
to do?
This conversation is over.
You made your bed.
Don't come crying to me
because the sheets are dirty.
- I'm not gonna cry to anyone.
I'm gonna tell Zane
exactly what this man
is all about,
and we'll see what happens
when he finds out
whatever shit you did.
You don't think Robert knew?
Why do you think
he didn't fight
for Gavin's business
when we left Rand Kaldor?
You're saying Zane knows
you did illegal shit?
I'm saying, Robert Zane knew
what kind of a client
Gavin Andrews was,
that I knew how to handle him,
and that I stopped wanting to.
Then help me get out of this.
- Why should I?
- Because we're on
the same team,
and that's supposed
to mean something,
especially when it's about
breaking the law.
Please, Samantha.
I should have listened to you,
but I have a family.
I can't afford to do something
that'll hurt them.
Okay, Alex.
You are a family man.
He is not.
- What are you saying?
I'm saying,
you're the kind of man
that would go to any length
to protect your family.
Gavin Andrews
is the kind of man
that would go to any length
to protect himself.
So all we need to do
is open with material breach,
show severability
doesn't apply, then close
with impossibility
of performance.
We do all that,
it'll drive the stake
right through their claim.
We?
Yes, we.
Because although
I'm feeling better,
you did this as much as I did,
which means
we should do it together.
You sure?
I'm sure.
I do believe
that's the first time
I've seen you smile
since we started
this whole thing.
I was just thinking
about my senior year
of high school.
This is how I used
to do my homework.
You had an associate
write your papers for you
in high school?
- I had a study partner.
He was my best friend.
We used to write our papers
together by flash light.
Never thought I'd be doing
the same thing years later.
You in touch with him?
No.
But I feel like I am
after tonight.
Now you're smiling.
I know it sounds cheesy.
No, I was just thinking
about where we were a week ago
when I thought
you were cold and heartless.
And I went from that
to being your best friend
in record time.
- I wouldn't say best friends.
Well, you can only say stuff
like that to me
because we're, like,
best friends.
Well, I don't know
about that.
But we are close enough
for me to tell you
that you're going
to go to court
by yourself tomorrow.
But I thought you said
you were feeling better.
I am, but you did all this
to help prove
that I could manage people,
and what kind of manager
would I be
if I didn't give you a chance
to prove yourself
to John Bigelow?
You sure?
I'm sure.
What do you mean
you gotta go down to Central?
How long's that gonna take?
- It's gonna take
as long as it takes.
- What the hell
is going on, here?
- Robert, you all right?
You look like hell.
- The elevator wouldn't stop
on our floor.
Had to get off at 45 and hike
the rest of the way up here.
God damn, man,
you gotta keep in shape.
That was only five floors.
- Is that really the problem
we need to talk about, Louis?
- No.
In fact, an hour ago,
the elevators
weren't working at all.
- Shit.
And now this ass clown says
that he needs
to have landlord's approval
to order a simple fuse.
- What?
- I said that he's--
I know what you said.
I wanna hear it from him.
What do you want me to say?
I got orders
from my supervisor.
No new parts without Mr. Fox's
specific approval.
Louis, I know
what's going on here.
- What are you talking about?
- I'm talking about the fact
that this is
no goddamn coincidence.
Anna, it's Harvey Specter.
I've got good news:
I've decided
to take care of you myself.
Because I showed up
to work this morning
and they told me I was fired,
and that I shouldn't bother
applying to any...
- Anna, I got something
I can't reschedule
right this second.
I'm gonna have to--
- Please, Mr. Specter.
I was in horrible shape
before, but now I don't know
what to do.
- Look, I'll tell you
what we're gonna do:
I'm gonna call you back
in five minutes, you're gonna
tell me exactly what happened.
because I'm not gonna let them
get away with this.
Okay, Harvey,
what the hell is going on
with that cleaning woman?
- Robert...
You said you weren't going
to pick a fight, and you did.
And now our elevators
aren't working.
You wanna know
what's going on?
David Fox just retaliated
against Anna by firing her,
and I'm about
to knock his teeth out.
- You will do no such thing.
- Relax, Robert.
We can handle
a clogged toilet or two.
Did you hear
what I just said?
I'm not talking about toilets.
The man just shut down
our elevators,
and I'm not gonna let us
start losing clients
because you decided
the cleaning staff
is more important
than the needs of this firm.
I didn't do anything
that you didn't sign off on.
Bullshit.
You said that you were
gonna have
a two-minute conversation
with the man,
and if that's all you did
he wouldn't be sabotaging
our offices.
Well, you know what, Robert?
I don't care
what he's doing to us.
I care what he's doing to her.
- What did you just say?
- I said I don't care
what he's doing to us.
- Well, I do.
- Excuse me?
- You heard me, Harvey.
I don't know what it is
you think you're doing,
but it needs to stop.
- I don't believe this.
You're siding with him.
- Yes, Harvey, I am.
And you're not gonna want
to hear this either, Harvey,
but I am too.
Because if you keep
escalating this,
it's not just gonna be
about broken elevators.
He's gonna find a way
to kick us out of the building.
Well, none of you
are gonna want to hear this,
but I don't give a shit
whether he kicks us out
of the building or not.
- That's enough.
You don't go to war
with the guy
that owns your house
over something like this.
End it, and end it today.
May I join you?
You don't usually ask that.
And you haven't made
your own copies
since we were at
the DA's office.
I guess I haven't.
Harvey, I thought
that you were gonna
take this thing to the clinic.
That's what I did, Donna.
But Nathan and Oliver
weren't there;
there were cases piled high
on every desk;
and nobody there
would care about her
the way I needed them to, so...
I turned around
and I walked right out.
- I see.
- How did I get here, Donna?
I'm at odds with Robert
and Louis, and now even you,
over something two months ago
shouldn't have even shown up
on my radar.
I'll tell you
how you got here...
and I can't believe
I didn't see this
the second you started
this thing.
Harvey, you're missing Mike.
- What are you talking about?
- Don't you see?
This case has Mike Ross
written all over it.
And you didn't walk out
of that clinic
because Nathan and Oliver
weren't there;
you walked out
because Mike wasn't there.
Well, what am I supposed
to do about that, Donna?
Because this woman needs help,
and I am not gonna throw her
out on the street.
- Tell you what I'd do.
I'd call Mike.
If there's anyone who's been
in a situation
like this before, it's him,
and he's the best person
to figure a way out.
But Harvey, you've got
to do it soon,
because Robert and Louis
are right.
You have to let this thing go.
- Is it done?
- It is done.
Good.
Wasn't so hard, was it?
- Not for me.
What's this?
The hell did you do
with my money?
I found you a legitimate
business opportunity.
In the goddamn
Cayman Islands?
Funny thing:
most people want
to repatriate their money,
which means you can make
a pretty sweet deal
by investing locally instead.
You can't do this.
You don't have the authority.
I do now,
because you're looking
at the new trustee
of your account.
- That's impossible.
- Is it?
Pretty smart
making your niece trustee
to insulate yourself.
Of course, when I told her
you set her up
to take the fall
if authorities ever found out
where your money came from,
she was more than happy
to sign over control to me.
- I don't believe you.
Pick up the phone
and call her.
She's kind of pissed
at you, though.
Thanksgiving might be
weird this year.
You son of a bitch.
You sold me out.
No, Gavin, I didn't.
I did what's in
your best interest,
regardless of the fact
that you're too stupid
to see it.
- You're fired.
- I don't think so.
Because if I can do this
to you,
imagine what I can do
for you.
But if you ever ask me
to do anything like this
ever again,
I won't just turn you in.
I'll sign over every nickel
of this trust to your niece,
and every other relative
you've ever screwed over.
Are we clear?
We're clear.
Louis, can I talk to you
for a minute?
Of course.
But first, I understand
congratulations are in order.
I heard you won
in court today.
That's the thing.
It wasn't me who won, Louis;
it was Brian.
- What?
- Just let me explain.
Explain what?
That the client said "no Brian"
and you didn't listen?
I don't care
what the client said
because two years ago,
another client said,
"no Katrina" and "no Rachel,"
and you told them
to go to hell.
So why should I be
any different
as a manager than you?
- Because, Katrina,
the situation was different.
You didn't shit the bed;
Brian did.
No, Louis, he didn't.
I did.
What are you talking about?
I've been getting migraines,
Louis.
I used to get them as a kid,
and ever since I had
to fire those associates,
I started getting them again.
And you were afraid
to tell me
because of senior partner.
Yes, and I was supposed
to be in that meeting
with Brian, and he didn't
tell you about it
because he was protecting me.
So it wasn't Brian's fault;
it was yours.
It was.
And I know you're gonna have
to tell Robert everything,
and I know that probably means
I won't be senior partner,
but I can't let Brian
hurt his career for me.
Katrina, the only thing
I'm gonna be telling Robert
is that you're gonna make
one hell of a senior partner.
- Is that what I think it is?
- If you think it's the plan
to put this Fox thing to bed,
then yes.
This is good.
Mike's a pretty smart guy.
- It is good,
but Mike didn't
come up with it.
- I did.
- Well,
now that you mention it,
I do see a bunch of flaws.
Seriously, Harvey,
this is great, but...
why didn't you talk to Mike?
Because I thought instead
of calling and asking
for a solution, I'd rather call
and tell him a story
with a happy ending.
- And you don't send in
the puppy to clean up
the dog's mess.
- Something like that.
- In that case,
you're gonna need this back.
- No, I'm not,
because you're gonna be the one
to give it to David Fox.
- Why me?
- Because we still need
to get him to agree,
and we can either do it
with a sledgehammer
or a velvet glove.
I get it.
You're saying
I'm a sledgehammer.
Something like that.
Listen, Harvey, if you're
gonna send me in there
to negotiate this,
I need to know
that I have carte Blanche
to do what it takes
to close him.
- I know.
You do.
Hey.
How'd you think of this?
Easy.
I just thought,
"What would Mike do?"
Donna Paulsen.
- David Fox.
- You know, if you're here
to harass me
about this cleaning lady,
then you can just
turn right around.
I'm here because of this.
You're filing
a class-action lawsuit?
We're not;
East Side Legal Clinic is.
Which means that no matter
what you do to us,
it's not going away.
And if you try
to fire anybody else,
you'll be getting
another one of those.
And it won't be for overtime;
it'll be for retaliation.
You'll be in court
for the rest of your life.
Why are you here
instead of Harvey Specter?
Because if Harvey were here,
he'd drop that down
walk out,
and go to war with you.
I, on the other hand,
have a compromise.
- Which is?
- Give Anna Reed her job back,
you start paying those people
what they're worth...
- And?
- You get free legal services
from Harvey Specter himself
for the next year.
Oh, come on.
Bullshit.
There's no way
he agrees to that.
Oh, he'll agree to it,
all right.
So you mean he doesn't
already know about it.
No, he doesn't.
But he gave me the authority
to close this thing,
and that's what I've determined
it's gonna take
because neither one of you
is gonna compromise
unless you know the other one
is getting shafted.
- One condition.
- Nope.
This is take it or leave it.
- You won't even hear
my condition.
- No, I won't,
because I have no interest
in going to dinner with you
to close this deal.
So what's it gonna be?
War or win-win?
You set up the paperwork
in the morning, we got a deal.
I'll do you one better.
I'll send it down
in the morning.
I got better things to do
with my time.
What's this?
Floor-level tickets
for the UFC at Barclays.
- You did your homework.
- I did.
Like you told me
I should have done
with Gavin Andrews
in the first place.
I assume that means
you took care of him?
And the horse he rode in on.
Anyway, I know
we'll probably end up
going toe-to-toe
plenty of more times
before it's all over,
but for now, good night.
You're more than meets the eye.
Alex.
I know you think
we're in competition
for the same thing,
but we're not.
What are you talking about?
Robert Zane
made me a promise.
The next name that goes up
on the wall is mine.
Why are you telling me this?
Because we're never going
to trust each other
if you think I'm trying
to get ahead of you.
I'm not.
Because I already am.
Good night, Samantha.
Good night.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
www.tvsubtitles.net