Previously, on "Suits..."
One of my transport flights
was carrying some art.
The hull depressurized,
and one of the pieces
got damaged.
It had to be insured,
so what's the problem?
The insurance inspector's got
the balls to say
they'd be suing me
for the damages.
I made an appointment with
the top fertility specialist
in the country.
- You really think
we need a specialist?
- The sooner we get some help,
the sooner we can hold
that baby in our arms.
Two days ago, when you said
this shady son of a bitch
destroyed that painting
intentionally--
Is that how you talk
about your former clients?
Alex, this thing
is a loser for you.
- Get your client under control.
- Don't talk to me
about this case being a loser.
You're lucky we're even
in here.
- Bullshit.
We go to court
and I will clean your clock.
Samantha and Alex
are about to go to war.
- I told her to settle.
- Well, she didn't.
And if Samantha did that,
I'll deal with her.
How?
Because you've let her do
whatever she wants
ever since she got here.
I don't suppose
it would do any good
to ask you to let
Alex go up there first.
I'm not backing down because
I think I'm better
than Alex Williams,
and I'm not gonna say
that I'm not.
You have some
cervical fibroids
that, unfortunately,
your OB missed,
and I'd like to remove them.
- If we keep doing nothing...
It's worse than letting them
settle it themselves.
One case, head-to-head,
winner gets name partner.
As you both know,
Harvey and I each made
a promise
to put your names
on the door next.
And obviously it's not
possible for us both
to keep that promise.
This better not be you
telling us we're going up
at the same time, because as
far as I'm concerned,
that's as bullshit as telling
me you're giving it to him.
And for once,
you and I agree.
Good, because we
have another idea.
Are those what
I think they are?
Two conflict
of interest waivers
giving you the green light
to take off the gloves
and get in the ring.
You wanted a fight.
You got it.
The winner gets
their name up next.
Any questions?
I got one.
Is it gonna be "and Williams,"
or just "Zane Specter
Litt Williams"?
I can answer that.
It's not gonna be either one.
Then I guess we'll
just have to find out.
I guess we will.
Well, before you start
taking any swings,
I wanna make one thing clear:
This is a fair fight.
No using inside information.
No looking at the other
person's shit.
Are we clear?
- Yes.
- Clear.
And if no one else
is gonna say it, I will.
Let's get ready to rumble.
Harvey. What are you doing here?
I came to say I know this
isn't how either of us
thought this would go down.
And I wanted to make sure
you were good with it.
If this is what
it's gonna take,
then I'm not just
good with it.
I'm also good with this.
Let me guess.
You want me to take
care of this for you.
It's nothing you
haven't done before.
What happened to
you don't like it
when I get involved?
What I don't like is you
getting involved
when I asked you
to stay out of it.
This is me telling you
to get your ass in it.
All right, Alex.
Are you sure?
Because once I do this,
there's no taking it back.
Yes, I'm sure.
Because I guarantee you,
she's going to Robert
to do the same damn thing.
So the question is,
are you here for me or not?
I'm here for you, Alex.
I'm right the hell here.
- Good, you're here.
- No.
What do you mean no?
You don't even know
what I want.
- Bullshit, I don't.
You're here for some kind
of edge with Alex Williams,
and I'm not gonna
give it to you.
- Why not?
- Because if I step in
to help you, it undermines
the whole arrangement.
All I'm asking is to
delay the trial a week.
Samantha, I'm managing
partner here because
I stayed out when it was time.
Well, it's still time.
And if you wanna
delay this thing,
you're gonna have
to do it on your own.
- That is bullshit.
- And you're entitled
to your opinion.
Now, unless you got
some other business,
why don't you just let me
wash my hands in peace?
♪ Suits 8x10 ♪
Managing Partner
Original Air Date on September 19, 2018
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ I'll even eat a bean pie,
I don't mind ♪
♪ Me and Missy is so busy,
busy making money ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ All step back,
I'm 'bout to dance ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
♪ The greenback boogie ♪
Thank you.
You ending the night
or starting the day?
- Both.
- Same here.
Banker or lawyer?
What I am is not interested.
Well, you might
not be interested,
but you're going to listen.
Now, we can be formal
about this, Samantha,
or you can just call me Tom.
Okay, Tom.
I'm listening.
We know there's money
laundering going on
in your firm,
but we don't know how high up
the food chain it goes.
And the bureau thinks that
you'd be the perfect person
to help us answer
that question.
- Why me?
- We know that you served
your country once before.
This is a chance
to serve it again.
Well, you can wave the
flag all you want,
but I don't know anything,
and I'm loyal to the people
I'm in the foxhole with
right now.
Well, if you're not
gonna ask what you can do
for your country, then...
maybe you should ask what
your country can do to you.
- These records were sealed.
- They were.
And whether they stay sealed
is entirely your choice.
See what you can dig up,
and don't say a word
about this to anyone.
You don't usually come
in and sit right down.
- This must be important.
- I need to say something
about this trial,
and I need you to hear me.
Donna, if this is about
us not consulting you,
it was a name partner decision.
- It's not about that, Harvey.
I'm here to talk about what
we're gonna do when it's over.
- What do you mean?
- We're all still gonna
be here, and win or lose,
it's gonna be on you
to keep the peace.
I hope you're asking
the same of Zane.
- I'm not.
- Why not?
Because this is still more
your firm than his,
and everybody knows it.
So if Alex wins,
you need to be
magnanimous about it.
And Harvey, if Samantha wins,
you need to be the bigger man
and accept it with grace.
You don't think Alex can win,
do you?
- What if I said I don't?
- I'd wanna know why.
Because this isn't about
who the better lawyer is.
It's about winning.
And unless he suddenly becomes
a different person,
he's not willing to go
as far as she is to win.
Well then maybe he is
becoming a different person.
- What do you mean?
- I mean he came to me
for help, and he wasn't asking.
He was telling.
- And you gave it to him?
- I did.
Harvey, if Alex comes to you
asking for help again,
say no.
- Why?
Because this isn't just about
keeping the peace later.
If we're not careful,
this could rip us apart
before it's even over.
What's all this?
Just wanted to make sure you
had all of our discovery.
You're bringing me
a cartload of documents
to go through at 9:00 at night?
And this is just the tip
of the iceberg.
You might wanna order takeout.
How much of this is purely
to waste my time?
I'll leave that to you,
but speaking of time...
I don't believe it!
You moved the trial
to tomorrow?
I don't run the four corners,
Samantha.
I fast-break.
And right now, it's show time.
You think I don't know
what you're doing?
You're trying to speed this
thing up because you know
your client is guilty,
just like you know
if I have time to dig in,
I'll prove it.
I'm trying to speed this up
because the longer
this goes on,
the longer my client's image
gets dragged through the mud.
Spare me the song
and dance, Alex.
The judge might not
have seen through it, but I do.
You're right.
He did see it my way.
And the only thing you're gonna
see is me wiping the floor
with you starting tomorrow.
- Yeah?
- Louis.
Hey, I was just
thinking about you.
What's going on?
How was your day?
Well, I've got some good
news and some bad news.
- What happened?
- Dean Stanton's wife
was diagnosed
with breast cancer,
and he's stepping down
to spend some time with her.
Sheila, I am so sorry.
The good news
is he recommended me
to be interim dean.
Oh, my God, that's amazing.
I'm gonna come home right now
and we're gonna go out
and celebrate.
Louis, you don't have
to do that.
Well, I know I don't have to.
I want to.
No, I mean,
you don't have to do that.
Because I'm already here.
I am so proud of you.
Louis, it hasn't
happened yet.
It will.
I know it will.
Excuse me, Mr. Jarvis.
Do you have a minute?
Of course I do.
But first I'll need a name.
Samantha Wheeler.
Well, Samantha Wheeler,
what can I do for you?
When I was hired I was told I
could come to senior management
with anything.
- And you can.
We pride ourselves
on our reputation
for looking after
our associates.
Which is why I'm hoping
you can help me.
I was approached
by the FBI this morning.
They think something's
going on here.
Oh.
And, well, what did you say?
I said I'm loyal to my firm.
Well, that would presume
there's something
to be loyal about.
The guy that came
at me believes
we're laundering money.
What are you working
on right now?
The suit against Monsanto.
First thing tomorrow,
I'm farming it out
to someone else,
because if the FBI's right,
then I need someone
to dig into our books.
If I go to accounting, then
whoever's doing this is gonna
know there's something
rotten in Denmark.
- I'm on it.
- Good.
Oh, and Samantha,
if you find anything,
I mean, no matter how small,
please, let me know.
Ladies and gentlemen,
you're going to hear a lot
of numbers in this trial,
but the only number
that matters is seven.
That's how many safeguards
there are to keep a cargo hold
from depressurizing.
It simply can't happen.
Unless someone wants
it to happen.
20 years ago, I parked my car
outside a 7-Eleven.
When I came out,
it was totaled,
and it took me two years
to collect $1,800
I couldn't afford to lose.
Gavin Andrews stood to gain
millions of dollars
from destroying the very
painting he was charged
with transporting.
Now, imagine
it wasn't a Corolla.
It was a $100 million painting.
Think how hard they'll
fight not to pay.
Because it's what
insurance companies do.
They blame someone else.
They call it an act of God.
Or they just say, "Screw you.
Come and get it."
The truth is,
this is a crime,
and he should go
to prison for it.
Unfortunately we can't put him
away for this,
but what we can do
is make him pay for it.
Because they'll do whatever
it takes to keep their money.
And we're not gonna let
them get away with it.
Miss Wheeler,
your first witness.
Your Honor, I call
Gavin Andrews to the stand.
I guess you aren't
big on foreplay.
Oh, I like foreplay
just fine, Alex.
But you're right
about one thing.
You're about to get ----ed.
Mr. Andrews,
when a plane depressurizes,
the NTSB is supposed
to investigate.
But before they could,
you cleared out the cargo hold.
Why would you do that?
Because you don't leave
million-dollar works of art
to bake in the sun.
And thanks to my call, we were
able to save most of them.
Most of them.
But not the Vermeer.
And if there's one less
Vermeer in the world,
then yours in more valuable.
Sorry to disappoint you,
but I didn't want
that painting destroyed.
I wanted to buy it.
Then let's talk
about your other art.
Five years ago, you bought
a Renoir for $8 million
and recently sold it.
Is that correct?
- It is.
- How much did you sell it for?
- Considerably more.
- Isn't it true
you sold it for $55 million
to an airline manufacturer
who then happened
to win your business?
- Your Honor,
that's a violation of
the terms of our waiver.
She's using
privileged information.
It would be privileged,
except Mr. Andrews' wife
detailed all of this
in their divorce filing.
- What?
- He hid assets
from their
prenuptial agreement.
He took bribes and hid them
as art transactions--
Hearsay, Your Honor.
Allegations from
a bitter ex-wife.
A woman who knows this man
better than anyone.
Overruled, Mr. Williams.
Divorce filings
are publicly available.
Mr. Andrews, you take
kickbacks from your suppliers.
You cheated your own wife.
Do you really expect a jury
to believe what happened
to the Vermeer was an accident?
- It was an accident.
Well, actions speak
louder than words.
And your actions
aren't just speaking.
They are screaming that you're
guilty
and all of these people
can hear it.
God damn it,
we had an agreement,
and you broke it.
- I didn't break anything.
Don't give me that shit.
There's no public record
of that divorce filing,
and there's no way his wife
knew about that $55 million.
Then go check
the filing yourself.
I think you'll find that
it's been recently amended
and placed in
the public record,
which means I didn't
violate anything.
All right, Samantha.
You want public record.
I'll give you public record.
Ms. Horford, instead
of looking at the whole chain
of custody, you only
focused on Starboard Airlines.
Why is that?
We looked at the whole chain
of custody, Mr. Williams.
For how long?
Ten minutes?
An hour?
Or just long enough to figure
that of all the people
you could sue, Gavin Andrews
had the deepest pockets?
That's insulting.
We don't do business that way.
I think you do,
which is why you lost
Starboard Airlines as a client
when Gavin Andrews took
his business elsewhere.
- That has nothing
to do with this.
- It has to do with you
missing out on your bonus
that year.
If you're implying that
I would use my company
for personal reasons--
Isn't that what you're
accusing my client of doing?
And when an analyst at Goldman
asked you why you lost
Starboard Airlines,
you said,
"The way Gavin Andrews does
business will come back
to haunt him,"
meaning you would come back
to haunt him.
- That's not what I meant.
It sure sounds
like what it meant.
What I meant was that our
biggest rival gave him
a kickback to drop--
- You have proof of that?
No, you don't, just like you
don't have proof that my client
damaged that painting.
All you have is a bunch
of smear tactics and a grudge.
- Objection, testifying--
- Then I'll wrap it up.
Because you were right: actions
do speak louder than words.
And all this is is a good old
fashioned case of payback.
I came home as soon
as I got the voicemail.
I got the job.
Sheila, that is fantastic.
I am so proud of you.
And not only that,
they said if I do well,
I can have it permanently.
- Permanently?
- Yes.
They were discussing it,
and the head of the search
committee said...
Louis, what's wrong?
- Nothing, it's just we agreed
after the baby, I'd do the
heavy lifting in the fall,
and you would take over after
recruiting season ended.
The dean of a law school,
Sheila,
that's a year-round job.
There's no way you'll
be able to do both.
Well, we can--we
can make an adjustment.
- What kind of adjustment?
- Well, I don't know.
Don't most couples with
full-time jobs get a nanny?
I don't want a stranger
raising my child.
So you want me to turn down
an opportunity
that may never come again?
- Not the interim part,
but the permanent part, yes.
Louis, if I did that
and we have a daughter,
how would I ever look
her in the eye?
You look at her in the eye
and you tell her,
"I chose you."
If you don't, you'll never be
able to look her in the eye
at all because
you'll be working.
Okay, that's not fair, Louis.
And if we worked out
the Jewish thing,
we can work this out.
Well, we haven't figured
that out yet.
And that was something
we hadn't discussed.
This is something we agreed on.
Like when we agreed you'd
give up mudding,
and then you didn't.
- Don't throw that back on me.
I lived up to it in the end.
- Okay, well this is a little
bit bigger than mudding, Louis.
This is my life.
And I want this job
and I want a baby
and I don't see why
I can't have both.
Well, I don't know
what to say to all that.
How about,
"I support your choices?"
Because I'm gonna have surgery
in three days to help us
have this baby.
And I'd feel a lot better
about it knowing we were
both on the same team.
Robert.
Samantha.
What are you doing down here?
There was an error
with a client's billing.
I'm trying to fix it
before it gets noticed.
Which client?
Maybe I can help.
I appreciate that.
I just took care of it.
- Have a nice night.
- Samantha.
There's only two reasons
someone who's not an accountant
would be here
on a Friday night.
Either they can't get a date,
or...
they want to be here
when no one's around.
What are you saying?
You're not here
to fix something.
You're here to find something.
- That's not what I'm do--
- It's okay.
I'm here for the same thing.
There's something shady going
on here with the money.
I just can't prove it.
Let's say I trust you.
What have you found so far?
- There's two issues.
- Bonus payments
and retainer fees.
- Exactly.
So I tell you what.
You take the retainers.
I'll take the bonuses.
A week from now, we meet up
and see what's what.
Sounds like a plan.
Robert, why are you doing this?
Because I don't mind
defending criminals,
but I didn't put myself through
law school to work for them.
All right, you wanted help.
Well, here it is.
What I wanted
was help yesterday.
You said no,
and now it's too late.
- The trial's already started.
- Well, I was wrong.
So you can hold a grudge,
or you can think
of something else.
All right.
There is one thing.
After Alex tore Nina
to pieces on the stand,
I told her we needed
to shore up the investigation
into the packing company.
- She got a look on her face.
- What kind of look?
- The kind of look that said
I'm not gonna be able
to shore up anything.
So I said, "Forget I asked."
Let me guess.
She already sent
the files over.
I'm pretty sure they
got here after I got back.
But I don't know
since I didn't look.
Which means you need me
to make that box disappear.
- Yes, I do.
- Samantha...
let me ask you one question:
are you sure
Gavin Andrews is guilty?
Robert, I represented
the man for years.
He is always guilty.
Then consider it gone.
- 10:00, right on schedule.
- I'm nothing if not prompt.
- So, what'd you come up with?
- Not a thing.
- The retainers all checked out.
- Shit.
Why shit?
Well, I dug into the bonuses
and struck out, too.
Maybe there's nothing to find.
I didn't say I didn't
find anything, Robert.
I said the retainers
all checked out.
After I went down my path,
I went down yours,
and wouldn't you know?
It led right back to you.
So tell me, Robert.
Why am I holding a $100,000
off-the-books wire transfer
with your name on it?
Six months ago I found out
all three named partners
were laundering money.
They offered to cut me in.
I said no.
They put that money in there
to make me look complicit.
- Bullshit.
- It's not bullshit.
They wouldn't take the money
back no matter what I said.
So I did the next best thing
and gave it to charity.
If you don't believe me,
I'll show you the check.
So you can cut a check
but you can't blow the whistle?
How noble.
It's more
complicated than that.
Seems pretty simple to me.
You witness a crime,
you tell the authorities.
Which is what I'm
gonna do right now.
Why don't you try telling me
that after you have a daughter?
Her name is Rachel.
She wants to be a lawyer.
But how is that gonna go when
she applies to the bar
and they say, "Isn't
your father a criminal?"
You show them the check
and make them believe
you're not a criminal.
If this comes out,
my name is tainted forever.
They'll never believe me.
And if it was just me,
I'd take that chance.
I'm sorry, Robert.
It's...
- It's not my call.
- Please.
Now, you came in here because
you wanted to hear my side
of the story.
My story...
is I'm a father
with a daughter.
And I need your help.
Samantha.
I was wondering when
this visit was coming.
- What visit is that?
- The one where
you threaten me.
- I'm not here to threaten you.
I'm here to offer you a way out
before publicly humiliating you
because you're still
a client of my firm.
Get off my property.
And I do that,
the jury's gonna hear
from Phillip Jones.
You thought you could
hide him from me.
I don't know anyone
by that name.
Funny, because he has
security footage showing you
meeting with him two weeks
before
you destroyed that painting.
- He'll never testify.
- He already has.
I have him under oath saying
you specifically asked him
how much your Vermeer
would go up
if another one got destroyed.
I've got you, Gavin,
and I am not letting go.
This is illegal
and inadmissible.
- You hacked my shit.
- What I did was do to you
what I used to do for you.
And you can threaten me
or throw me off your property
but once we're
in that courtroom,
I am not going anywhere.
Give me a day.
Excuse me?
I'll pay what we owe.
I just--I need a day
to get the board's approval.
No, I don't trust you.
You don't need to trust me.
You got me.
Like you just said.
I'm still a client of the firm.
That's gotta count
for something.
- It doesn't.
- Samantha, please.
I know you once told me
about your family.
Well, I have a family and...
If this comes out,
think about what it's gonna do
to my kids.
One day.
I'll give you one day.
And then I'm putting you
on the stand.
Louis, what's going on?
What do you mean?
I just found a bouquet
of pink carnations on my desk.
And since we both know that's
the widely accepted bouquet
of apology I thought I'd ask
what you're apologizing for.
I wasn't apologizing to you.
I was apologizing to Sheila.
It turns out, she didn't
want an apology.
She wanted a change of heart.
And you just made
senior partner,
so I thought rather
than throw them away...
Thank you, Louis.
But I thought you and Sheila
were doing great.
Yeah, we were until she got
offered to be the dean
of Columbia Law School.
And you're afraid
if she takes it,
she won't have time
for the baby.
Exactly, and with this added
responsibility, Katrina,
I...
I don't know how
it's gonna work.
I know it's not my place.
But did you consider that
if Sheila has less time,
you might be able
to make more time?
Katrina, I can't
just leave the firm.
I know that, Louis,
but three nights ago,
you came into my office
and said you saw a look
on my face that you had
seen on yours before.
Yes, the look of wishing
for someone to share
your life with.
You don't have
that look anymore.
What you do have
is two name partners
and a new senior partner who
have your back.
Which means that when
the time comes,
you'll be able to step back
a little and trust
that the firm is in good hands.
Speaking of keeping
the firm in good hands,
Katrina, I need
to tell you something.
Gavin, what are
you doing here?
We're due in court in an hour.
No we're not,
because Samantha asked
for a recess and she got it.
- What does she have now?
Doesn't matter what she has.
It matters what I have.
- What is that?
- A list of ethical violations
Samantha Wheeler engaged in
over the course of six years
as my attorney.
- No, I'm not ruining
Samantha's career.
- Look, you don't have to
ruin anything.
You threaten to take this
to the bar and she'll cave.
I'm not gonna
take that chance.
And we don't need to.
We're winning.
No, Alex, we're not.
What are you talking about?
Samantha came
to my house this morning.
She has proof that I asked
an appraiser what would happen
to the value of my Vermeer if
that painting got destroyed.
- Now, if he gets on the stand--
- Let me get this straight.
There's a goddamn smoking gun,
and you kept it from me?
'Cause you're a Boy Scout,
and you would've
given it to her.
- All right, look.
It's bad, but it's not proof.
We can cross examine
this guy and--
- Let me make myself clear!
This is not a suggestion.
It is an order.
If you don't use this, I will.
And if I do it, Alex,
we're gonna skip the part
where she gets the chance
to walk away because I'll
be going straight to the bar.
I don't like that
look on your face.
- What look?
- The look that says
you're about to tell me
some serious shit.
Samantha's got Gavin
by the balls.
But I think I got a way out.
- How?
- I did some digging.
Dexhart has 80%
of the reinsurance
for the packing company
that should have protected
that painting.
- Which means
they'd have incentive
to clear them of any fault.
Which I believe they did
with a false report.
And you think Samantha's
hiding the real report?
I think she's too smart
to look at the real report
in the first place.
And I know if we ask for it
with a subpoena,
it'll never see
the light of day.
What exactly are you
here to ask me, Alex?
I want you to get Katrina
Bennett to go over there
and ask for the unredacted
version of that report.
- No way.
- Harvey.
You're asking to have
one of our lawyers
commit a crime.
- It's not a crime.
She's a senior partner
at this firm.
All she has to do is say that,
ask for the files,
and get the hell out.
- And if it's so innocent,
why don't you go over there
and do it yourself?
Because I'm not blonde
and no one's gonna
mistake me
for Samantha Wheeler.
Damn it, Alex,
you said you could beat her.
I can beat her.
This is what it's gonna take.
And I wouldn't be
in this position
if you didn't break your
promise to me.
And that's bullshit
because you said
you were good with fighting
to get your name up.
What the hell
was I supposed to say?
Alex, helping to speed up
the trial is one thing.
Putting Katrina at risk?
- I'm not doing it.
- Then you should know,
I don't do this,
Gavin Andrews goes to the bar
tomorrow with a list
of shady things Samantha's
done over the years.
So you can help me
with this or not.
Either way, her name's
not going on that wall.
Katrina, if you're here
to go out for drinks tonight,
I can only say that the answer
is a big, fat, "Yes, please."
As much as I would love
to say that's why I'm here,
what I need is a big,
fat piece of advice.
- What is it?
- Harvey...
basically asked me to
impersonate Samantha Wheeler.
What?
It's the only way to get what
they need to help Alex win.
- What'd you tell him?
- I told him I didn't know.
Well, if Harvey wants you to
do this, why not do it?
Other than not wanting to get
on Samantha's bad side,
Louis specifically told me not
to help either one of them.
Did he say why?
He said that if too many
people got involved,
their fight could tear
the firm apart.
Then I say...too many people
are already involved.
You might as well go ahead.
Help Harvey.
Thanks, Donna.
- What's this?
- A settlement agreement.
You're dropping that lawsuit,
paying Gavin's legal fees,
and issuing a public apology.
The hell we are.
Samantha, you can kick
and scream all you want,
but I got proof the packing
company skimped on materials
and your client knew about it.
How the ----
did you get these?
The same way I got
everything else.
You shared it with
me in discovery.
I didn't share shit with you.
I never even saw
these documents.
You never saw them because
you never wanted to see them.
But Dexhart Insurance has
records proving it was sent.
You son of a bitch.
You cheated.
No, I just played
by your rules.
- So don't start crying now.
- Oh, I'm not crying.
And I as sure as hell
am not signing this.
And let me tell you what
happens if you don't.
Gavin Andrews
gets you disbarred.
- What?
- He's got information
that could end your career
and he told me to use it,
but I didn't because I didn't
wanna do that to you.
So, what?
I'm supposed to thank you now?
I don't expect
you to thank me,
but I do expect you
to accept that it's over.
- I'm not accepting anything.
- I get it.
You're not used to losing.
But whether you wanna
admit it or not,
I won, you lost.
And come tomorrow, my name's
going up on that wall.
Louis, what are
you doing here?
Not bringing
you more flowers,
if that's what
you're wondering.
Sheila, the reason I was so
thrown with you taking on
more responsibility
was because...
I was afraid that I wouldn't
be able to take on less.
And whether you are offered
the permanent position or not,
when the time comes,
I wanna take time
for our family.
Well, I'm--I'm glad
to hear you say that.
Because the time has come.
You mean you were offered
the permanent position?
No, not that time, Louis.
The other time.
Oh, my God.
Are you saying what
I think you're saying?
I saw Chaz this afternoon.
And we're not gonna need
that surgery because...
we're gonna have a baby.
I don't believe this.
Are you sure?
I mean...
are you absolutely sure?
Yes, I'm positive.
And I'm sorry we fought.
I just--I'm stressed,
and I've got hormones
running through me
and I'm not even sure if I
want that permanent position.
Hey, it's okay.
It's all gonna be okay.
I am right here by your side.
I'm not going anywhere.
How are you so calm?
Because I know what's important now.
And it's this.
Everything's gonna be okay.
Okay.
I got your message.
You're late.
- I had some thinking to do.
- Well, I'm glad you showed up.
Because I was beginning to
wonder if I was meeting you
or the feds in here tonight.
I think I have a way
to get you out of this.
You mind if I ask you
what changed your mind?
Because I believe you.
I also know if
I do this for you,
you'll always have my back.
- You're saying I owe you?
I'm saying you'll
feel grateful.
- It isn't the same thing.
- No, it's not.
So, what's your plan?
Who here do you trust
more than anyone else?
After tonight, that's easy.
- You.
- No, it can't be me.
It raises too many red flags.
Besides, I'm not old enough.
It's not my time.
Well, what are you
talking about?
Just answer the question.
You need somebody here
to have your back.
It isn't me.
Who is it?
Two people.
- Ellen Rand and Eric Kaldor.
- Then get them.
'Cause we're not out
of the woods yet.
It's good that you reached
out to me when you did.
I was starting to think
you made a wrong choice.
I've made enough wrong
choices in my life, Tom.
I'm not gonna make
a wrong one on this.
- So, what'd you find?
- Nothing.
All I found was a glitch
in the billing system.
Bullshit, we've got
information that your firm--
I don't care what you've got.
Clients were overcharged
then reimbursed.
That's all there was to it.
And when I subpoena
every billing record
from the last five years,
that's never gonna hold up.
And if you could have
subpoenaed those records,
you wouldn't have come to me
in the first place.
I get it.
They paid you off,
and now you're as guilty
as they are, huh?
Don't you say that to me.
You tried to used my history
to get me to turn on my family.
And if you unseal my records,
I guarantee you the firm
of Rand Kaldor Zane will use
every resource they have
to come after you
for malicious prosecution.
- Rand Kaldor Zane?
- That's right.
Jarvis, Ellis, and Green
are all stepping down,
so if you're convinced
they really did something,
think of it as a little
punishment getting served
after all.
- That's not punishment.
That's getting away Scot-free.
And if you think having your
name ripped off the wall
when you've worked your entire
life to get up there
isn't punishment, you don't
know what it is to be a lawyer.
Because trust me,
it's all any of us ever want.
Then why didn't you put
your own name up there?
Because it's not my time,
Tom.
But you can bet your ass
someday it will be.
Samantha.
Are you here
to tell me you won?
I'm here to tell you Alex
Williams has a smoking gun.
- And he's got me dead to rights.
- What?
I lost, Robert.
It's over.
How the hell did that happen?
I had him.
I had my foot on Gavin's neck.
I gave him extra time.
And I'm not gonna lose what's
mine because Alex
used that time to win.
- What are you saying?
I don't give a shit
what the agreement was.
My name's going up on that
wall,
and you're gonna
make it happen.
- I can't do that.
- Why not?
- Samantha--
- God damn it, Robert!
They found those files,
which means you didn't tip
the scales at all.
What is it gonna take for you
to get off the sidelines?
I wouldn't have to get off
the sidelines if you hadn't
shown Gavin Andrews mercy!
Well, I didn't just do that
because he's still a client.
I did it because he
told me he had a family.
Just like you once did.
You're saying I owe you.
You have owed me for years,
and you know it.
And before you gave them
your word,
you gave your word to me.
So the question is,
which word are you
gonna live up to?
Louis, we need to talk.
It's important.
Yeah, of course.
Come in.
Actually, I'm glad you're here,
'cause I have some big
news of my own.
Well, whatever it is,
it's not as big as this.
Robert's about to tell Harvey
that he's gonna put up
Samantha's name
instead of Alex's.
No, no, Alex won.
Robert can't break
his word like that.
Well, he's going to,
and if we don't do something,
we're not gonna have
a firm tomorrow.
We're gonna have
a war on our hands.
Okay, I hear you.
First thing tomorrow we'll get
into a conference room
and we'll talk
this thing through.
Louis, it's too late
for that.
The time for talking is over.
We need to do something.
- And that something is--
- I'll step down.
What?
Donna, Sheila's pregnant.
I'm gonna be a father.
- Oh, my God.
- I was gonna ratchet down
anyway.
This way they can both
put their names up.
Louis, I am so happy for you.
- But that's not gonna work.
- What are you saying?
I'm saying you need to step
in as managing partner.
- What?
- Louis,
Robert can't run
this firm right now
and neither can Harvey.
You're the only one who can.
Sorry, Donna.
I can't.
- Why not?
- Because I'm not a leader.
They won't follow me.
Louis.
I know you went to Katrina
to protect the firm.
And you just offered to step
down to do the same thing.
If that's not the leadership
we need right now,
I don't know what is.
- Why does it have to be now?
I just wanna be a father.
And the last thing I'd
ever wanna do is take that
away from you.
But your baby's not due
for another nine months.
And this firm
is your baby too,
and it needs you right now.
I can't make that
decision without talking
to Sheila first.
- Then hurry.
Because we don't have
a lot of time.
Donna, even if I said yes...
Harvey and Robert
would never vote
to make me managing partner.
You leave that to me.
I take it you're celebrating.
It's a drink, Robert.
I'm not rubbing it
in anybody's face,
but yeah,
I'm happy for my guy.
Well, I'm here
to say something
that's gonna make
you less happy.
What's that?
I'm putting Samantha's name
on the wall, not Alex's.
I must be getting
old because...
I'm pretty sure
I just heard you say
you're breaking your word.
Harvey, I know.
I made a promise.
You didn't just
make a promise.
You looked me in the
eye and you said,
"Let's settle this
in the ring."
And I don't care.
I owe her.
Then you should have put
her name up years ago.
- Not when it costs someone else.
- God damn it, I am
the managing partner
of this firm.
And we can change that right
now because I was here
before you and I'm gonna be
here long after you're gone.
- Are you threatening me?
- I'm giving you a choice.
You and Samantha can accept
Alex or you can pack up
your shit right now.
- I'm not going anywhere
and neither is Samantha,
because you're the past,
and she's the future.
Not here, she's not.
Now get the ----
out of my office.
That's enough.
No one's going anywhere,
and neither one of you
is managing partner anymore.
- Donna, stay out of this.
No, I am putting
a stop to this,
and I'm putting
a stop to it right now.
'Cause this isn't just
a friendly gathering.
This is a formal
partner meeting.
And here's how it's gonna go.
I'm voting for Louis
for managing partner.
And he's voting for himself.
And since there is no way that
either one of you is voting
for the other,
you might as well both vote
for him and keep this
a united front.
Because make no mistake.
Louis is managing partner.
Bullshit.
There's no way you're
pulling this off.
She's not pulling this off,
Robert.
I am.
This is happening whether
you like it or not.
So you think you have what
it takes to run this firm?
I know I do.
And my first order of business
is promoting Alex and Samantha
at the same time.
And any managing partner
worth his salt can see
they'll never go for it.
- No.
They're either both gonna
accept this or they're both
gonna walk the ---- out
the door because I am sick
of this shit.
And I'll tell you
something else.
You two are gonna goddamn
sell it to them.
So, what's it gonna be?
Me and Louis and
a split decision?
Or are we gonna make
this thing unanimous?
How'd they take it?
Kicking and screaming.
Bet you wouldn't
have it any other way.
Nope, I wouldn't.
What'd you tell
Rand and Kaldor?
That all they had to do was
be ready to act in charge,
and I could get them the firm.
And let me guess.
They knew not to ask any
more questions than that.
Isn't that what being
a great lawyer is all about?
Sometimes.
Sometimes it's about asking
the right questions.
Okay, then.
- Why'd you do it?
- Do what?
Help me.
And don't give me that line
about always having your back,
because it's gotta be
about something more.
I didn't have a father.
What?
I have no idea
who my parents were.
Didn't even know their names.
I bounced around
the foster care system.
Never lived in the same place
for more than two years.
What does that
have to do with--
Your daughter.
I helped you because I would
have given anything to have
someone like you
looking out for me.
And I didn't wanna
take it away from her.
I don't know what to say.
Say that from now on I'll
always have someone
looking out for me.
- Robert.
- Samantha, have a seat.
I don't want one.
Unless you're saying
it's a seat at the table.
It is.
But you're not alone.
Alex is getting
a promotion too.
Are you kidding me?
The whole point
of there being only one
is to have it mean something.
I know what the point is,
Samantha.
- So you sold me out.
- I didn't sell anyone out!
I once told you
I'd look out for you.
And I let that get in my head
and it almost cost us
what we have here.
So now I'm gonna look out for
you in a way that I should have
in the first place.
- How's that?
By telling you the truth.
They beat us at our own game,
Samantha.
Whether we like it or not.
But you know what that means?
We are surrounded by
some badass people.
So let's stop fighting in here
and start fighting
everyone else out there.
Because it's time
to make peace.
Am I interrupting?
Because I wanted to say
Harvey gave me the news,
and I'm good with
it if you are.
Of course I am, partner.
Then I guess there's only
one thing to figure out.
Williams-Wheeler
or Wheeler-Williams.
You won, Alex.
It's your choice.
So what do you say we have
ourselves
a good old-fashioned
group hug?
♪ I can feel it coming
in the air tonight ♪
♪ Oh, Lord ♪
♪ And I've been waiting for
this moment for all my life ♪
♪ Oh, Lord ♪
Harvey, it's been a long day,
so if you're here
to yell at me--
Relax, Louis.
I'm here to say thank you.
We lost ourselves
and you brought us back.
Thanks, Harvey.
Appreciate that.
It takes a lot
of balls to come at me
and Robert like that.
- No, Harvey, it didn't.
Because for the first time,
I didn't care how either one
of you saw me because...
I didn't even care to
be managing partner
in the first place.
- What do you mean?
I'm gonna have
a baby, Harvey.
I'm gonna be a dad.
And once that hit me, dealing
with this felt so simple.
Congratulations, Louis.
I think you're gonna make
a great managing partner,
and I know you're gonna make
an outstanding father.
You two need to get a room?
Or does anybody wanna go out
and celebrate?
Actually I think I'm just
gonna stay here for a bit
and take it all in.
I understand.
- Good night, Louis.
- Good night.
Level with me.
You really think
he can handle this?
I think desperate times
require desperate measures.
And I think
something else too.
What's that?
I'm going to enjoy watching
you and Robert take orders
from Louis.
We're not gonna be the only
ones he's in charge of.
He'll be giving you
plenty of orders, too.
No, he won't.
You're forgetting.
I'm the Louis Whisperer.
Are you sure about that?
When he walked in, he said you
weren't pulling it off.
- He was.
- And who do you think
told him to say that?
Holy shit,
are you saying you're
the real managing partner?
- I'm not saying that.
But I'm also not
not saying that.
Come on, pretty.
Drinks are on you.
♪ When times get hard ♪
♪ That's when I get going ♪
♪ 'Cause I can't stop,
I won't stop ♪
♪ And once I get rolling, then
there ain't no holding me ♪
♪ I can't stop,
I won't stop ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
www.tvsubtitles.net