Previously, on "Suits..."
There's a whole life
going on here
that you're not even a part of.
You think I don't know
what I've missed?
I'm not just talking about
birthdays, Harvey.
I got sick again.
- What?
Why didn't you tell me?
- Did you know?
- Know what?
That Gavin Andrews
was gonna ask me
to launder money
for him?
Help me get out of this.
Please, Samantha.
I should have listened to you,
but I have a family.
I want to make a perfect baby
with you.
- Are you sure?
- Absolutely.
And I don't want to just be
pulling the goalie.
I want to start trying, and I
want to start trying right now.
I know you think we're in
competition for the same thing,
but we're not.
Robert Zane made me a promise:
the next name that goes up on
the wall is mine.
Why are you telling me this?
Because we're never gonna
trust each other
if you think I'm trying to get
ahead of you.
I'm not, because I already am.
Sheila.
It's after 9:00.
You're gonna be late.
Then I'll be late,
because there's something
I need to ask you.
- Yeah, of course.
- You can ask me anything.
- Louis, have you ever gotten
a woman pregnant before?
Okay, uh...
[laughs]
Where is this going?
I'm asking because
you haven't gotten this woman
pregnant yet either.
Sheila,
we just started trying,
and I think
what I've been doing
is more than meeting
the standards.
Louis, you are
an A/A-plus lover.
Everyone knows that.
- There's a slash?
That's not the point.
The point is,
have you ever considered
the possibility
that you're shooting blanks?
- No more than I would consider
the possibility
that I don't have a face.
I get that, Louis,
and you probably have the sperm
of a thoroughbred,
but I'd like you
to get yourself checked.
- Sheila, if you're asking
what I think you are,
I don't want to go to a place
where people do...
that...
unless it's
absolutely necessary.
I get that, too,
but the fact is,
I'm not getting any younger
and we don't have time
to waste, so I'm getting
myself checked,
and I'm asking you
to do the same.
So here's the address.
You have an appointment today.
Okay, Sheila,
I'll get it done.
Thank you.
Harvey, do you have a second?
- Sure, Louis, what is it?
- Did you ever have
to test your sperm?
- What?
- Sheila wants me to,
but I don't think I can do it
in one of those places.
Louis, I don't want
to have this conversation.
It's bad enough
that we share the same dentist.
Harvey, come on.
We're trying to have a baby,
and I don't have anyone else
to talk to about this.
Okay, what--
what's your problem?
Problem is, I've never had
to do it under duress before.
I don't know how.
- Well, why don't you do it
like everyone else does?
Use pictures.
- I don't use pictures.
I only think of Sheila,
and I can't do that
with a bunch
of strangers there.
Well, what did you do
before Sheila?
- I don't wanna talk about it.
- Well, I don't want
to talk about any of this.
- Harvey, come on.
[sighs]
All right, look...
you can't use pictures;
you don't want
to think about Sheila.
Well, then, you'll have
to think of something
that turns you on
that isn't Sheila.
You mean think about
an inanimate object.
Yes, Louis,
that's what I mean.
- Have you done that before?
- Of course I have.
- What do you use?
- No, I'm not telling you that.
Harvey, please.
All right.
You want the truth?
Sometimes...
I think about...
tomatoes.
- Really?
- Well, if you think about it,
they're the most sensual fruit.
- I thought they were
a vegetable?
- I am opening my soul
to you here;
don't criticize me.
I'm sorry, you're right.
Thank you, Harvey.
Good luck in there, buddy.
Yeah.
Tomatoes, holy shit.
Never thought of that.
You wanna tell me
what that was all about?
No, because I'm guessing
you listened
to the entire conversation,
which means you know
what it's about.
- In that case,
what I really want to know is:
is it true about the tomatoes?
I think we both know
it's not.
Just like we both know
it's really strawberries
and whipped cream.
What, too soon?
- No.
But this is an office,
and someone could overhear
and misunderstand that
that was 13 years ago.
Really?
'Cause it feels like
12 and 1/2 to me.
- You're an idiot.
- No, Louis is an idiot.
because he believed
I think about tomatoes.
And if Sheila wants him
to get his swimmers checked,
we shouldn't mock
that he has to do that...
in a cup...
thinking about tomatoes.
- You're absolutely right.
We should take it
very seriously.
Tomatoes.
- Okay, you know what?
As much as I would love
to do this all day,
I came in here to tell you
you need to call Marcus.
Marcus?
About what?
I don't know,
but he left me a message
that he wants you to call him.
- Well, if he wants me to call,
why would he be leaving
a message for you?
Because when Marcus
really needs you, he calls me.
He's only ever done that twice,
which means whatever it is
he needs, it's important.
All right, Donna,
I'll call him.
Today, Harvey.
Today.
Hey, Harvey.
I'm glad you called.
I take it Donna
gave you my message?
She did.
What's going on?
- I'm getting a divorce.
- What?
I know.
And I know it is a big ask,
but I was hoping
that you could represent me.
Marcus, hold on.
When did this happen?
The last time I was up there
everything seemed fine.
Yeah, well, it's not fine,
and as much as I hate it,
this is what she wants.
- If you want me to help you,
I'm gonna need
to know more than that.
What do you want me
to tell you, Harvey?
That we grew apart?
Well, we did.
- Bullshit, I know you.
It's not the full story.
- You're right, it's not,
and I will tell you everything
when you get up here.
I didn't say
I was coming up there,
and I'm not going to
unless you tell me
what's going on, right now.
I slept with someone,
all right?
- You did what?
- I was stupid,
and I had an affair,
and I know you want
to rip my head off right now--
- You're damn right, I do!
'Cause you know better
than anyone
what that does to a family.
- Right now, I don't care.
What the hell
did you just say to me?
Harvey, you're always
telling your clients
that your issues
are your issues
and that you don't judge people
for what they do.
So right now I don't need
to hear how I screwed up.
What I need to hear is that
you're on your way up here
to help make sure
that I don't lose my kids.
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about custody,
Harvey,
because Katie hired a shark
to represent her.
Which means even if
you didn't want this
to turn into a fight...
- I can't risk
not treating it like one,
and the best way I know
to avoid a fight is to show up
with a howitzer--
and, Harvey...
the biggest howitzer I know
is you.
All right, Marcus,
I'll come up.
♪ Suits 8x05 ♪
Good Mudding
Original Air Date on August 15, 2018
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ I'll even eat a bean pie,
I don't mind ♪
♪ Me and Missy is so busy,
busy making money ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ All step back,
I'm 'bout to dance ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
♪ The greenback boogie ♪
All right, you have your tea.
Now let's get you set up
in the library.
- You mean the room
with the books
I can literally see from here?
Joy, I don't need
to have any attitude.
I can set myself up, Dad,
thanks.
- [sighs]
- These associates get younger
and angrier, don't they?
- That's not an associate;
that's my daughter.
- And you think
I didn't know that?
I can spot
a ninth-grade pushback
from a mile away.
Let me ask you something:
how'd you manage your kids?
- What do you mean, manage 'em?
- I mean, Joy got in trouble
at school,
that's why she's here.
And she may be a pain
in the ass,
but she finishes her homework
in 18 seconds
and all I have today
is paperwork.
I got it.
Your daughter won't listen
and you don't want
to talk to her, anyway.
- No, I just don't know
what to say to her
to get her to hear me.
That's because sometimes
there is no way
to get them to hear you.
But they might
hear someone else.
Someone--someone cool.
- Someone like you?
- No, no, no.
Not me.
- Come on, Gretchen,
what's it gonna take?
- I'm not saying I won't do it.
I'm saying it won't work.
- Why not?
Because it can't be someone
you think is cool...
It has to be someone
she thinks is cool.
Well, look at that.
Maybe you're not doomed
after all.
Now, move out of the way.
I gotta get me some
of that almond milk.
[funky music]
♪ ♪
Hello.
My name is Louis Litt,
I'm here to, uh...
[laughs jauntily]
You know, make a deposit.
Ah, of course.
11:00, right on the dot.
- Well, punctuality helps me
get in the right head space.
- Then why don't you
take a look
at our preparatory materials--
and before you ask,
I promise, whatever you need,
we've got you covered.
- Oh, that's great.
Then I'll just
take a quick look
at "The Wall Street Journal."
- The what?
"The Wall Street Journal."
America's paper of record.
What do you need
"The Wall Street Journal" for?
What do you mean,
what do I need it for?
I need it
to conduct my business.
But we don't
conduct business here.
No, not that kind
of business.
This kind of business.
- Are you telling me...
Yes.
I need a "Wall Street Journal,"
a "Forbes,"
"Investor's Weekly"--
anything of a fiscal
and fiduciary nature.
Well, we don't have
those things.
Who are you?
You just said anything I need
you got me covered.
What is your problem?
Well, it's not
the clinic's, but...
I have the real estate section
of the newspaper.
Give me that shit.
Standard, standard, standard,
blah, blah, blah...
Holy shit, they want how much
for a two bedroom--
Mm, Chubby Checker.
That'll work.
- Really?
- Yes, really.
I need a room.
I need one now.
I'll even share it
with somebody.
Come on, get the cup.
- All right...
- Get the cup!
- This way.
♪ ♪
Samantha, you got a second?
What I have
is less than four hours
to find proof Insight Drugs
has ripped off
our client's heart medication.
- That's too bad,
because I need help
with something,
and you're the perfect person.
- You're asking for my help?
- Yes, I am.
- What's the case?
- Williams versus Williams,
and I'm losing big time.
- What, now?
My daughter.
She's here for two days
because she got suspended,
and worse, when I asked her
what happened,
she lied to me about it.
So you're coming to me
because you don't think
she'll listen to you
or your wife right now.
She's a smart kid,
but right now
all she cares about
is being cool,
so I need someone like you
to show her
that being smart is cool.
- So you're saying I'm cool.
To a 15-year-old
who won't listen
to a word her father says, yes.
Well, maybe that's because
she doesn't need
to listen right now,
she needs to be heard.
Because I can tell you
from experience,
being a teenage girl
is pretty damn hard.
Does that mean you'll do it?
I guess it does.
Just don't make me
regret this.
Alex, if you don't know
by now,
making people regret things
is kind of what I do.
Then you and Joy
are gonna get along just fine.
Thanks, Samantha.
- What is this?
- Sanitizer.
I heard you had
a particularly dirty case
on your hands.
- Harvey told you.
- You mean that this
was the hardest case
you ever had?
That the client was really
jerking you around?
- That...
- Are you finished?
- Donna!
I'm just asking as a friend.
Did you slay the dragon?
Did you bop the potato?
Did you wallop the badinger?
- [stammering]
"Wallop the badinger"?
- Yeah, I was on a roll.
Whatever--no...
Louis, what's wrong?
I was just joking around.
Did it not go okay?
- It's not that, Donna.
- Then what is it?
- What if I can't have kids?
- Louis...
It is all I've ever wanted,
but it has never once
occurred to me
that I might not be able
to do it.
Well, has it occurred to you
that the reason
you were never worried
is that there's no reason
to be worried?
- Except Sheila is worried,
and now it's in my head.
Donna, what if it is me?
- Louis, right now
we don't even know
if there's a problem at all,
so I suggest
you cross that bridge
when you come to it.
And if you do,
and you need someone
to talk about it with,
I'll be here.
Thank you, Donna.
Hey.
Did you get a hold of Marcus?
- I did.
- Then what's going on?
He's not sick again, is he?
- No, nothing like that,
but it's still not good.
- Then what is it?
He cheated on Katie.
She found out
and now she wants a divorce.
Oh, my God.
Are you kidding me?
- No.
And that's not all;
he wants me to come up there
and represent him.
- So what are you gonna do?
What do you think
I'm gonna do?
I'm gonna help him.
- Okay, look, I have to ask--
are you sure
that you want to do this?
I appreciate your concern,
Donna, but it's my brother.
What am I supposed to do?
- All I'm saying
is that this could bring up
a lot of shit for you.
And I don't disagree,
but like I said,
it's my brother.
What am I supposed to do?
- Okay.
But before you go,
after what just happened
I think you should tell Robert.
- I already did.
How did he take it?
I have to give him credit,
he--
he didn't hesitate
for a second.
He said,
"Family comes first.
Always does, always will."
You must be Joy.
That's the name they gave me.
I'm Samantha.
Your dad's gonna be stuck
in meetings all day,
so he asked me
to check in on you.
Samantha, is it?
He didn't ask you
to check in on me.
He asked you
to keep an eye on me
because you're the cool one.
Well, you might be cool to him,
but you're not cool to me.
Okay.
I see what this is.
I'll tell you mine
if you tell me yours.
- Your what?
- My "why I got suspended."
- You got suspended?
- Just once.
But from three
different schools.
That's the football field.
I used industrial bleach.
That shit's not coming out
for months.
Wow, that is
some colorful language.
So what'd you do?
The worst one?
I boosted a car
from the school parking lot.
- You stole somebody's car.
- Not somebody's,
the principal's.
Turns out that is not
a good idea.
Got it.
Don't steal
the principal's car.
I'm not saying
breaking the rules
is a bad thing.
I'm saying you just need
to know which ones to break.
I don't think you're supposed
to tell me that.
Maybe not,
but if you're gonna help me
the next couple of days,
you should know how I work.
- Help you?
- Yeah.
I've got a deposition
this afternoon
and nothing to force
the other guy's hand.
You in?
- I'm in.
- Well, then, Joy,
you and I
are gonna need some coffee.
[door bell chiming]
Harvey,
what are you doing here?
I'm here because Marcus
asked me to represent him.
Then you shouldn't
be contacting me
without my lawyer.
- No, I shouldn't.
But I'm not here as a lawyer.
I'm here
as your brother-in-law.
- What does that mean?
- It means I know Marcus
still loves you, and...
I need to know
if there isn't still a way
that you guys
can work this out.
And as much as I wish
that could happen,
it's too late for that.
Look, Marcus told me
what happened...
And you're still
standing here
trying to defend him.
- No, I'm not.
When he told me, believe me,
I wanted to lay him out myself,
but I also know
what it feels like
to have your family
ripped apart, and I don't want
to see that happen.
- You think I do?
No, I don't,
but I'm telling you,
the second
lawyers get involved...
it's gonna get messy.
It's already messy, Harvey.
And my lawyer's
already involved,
so be Marcus' lawyer or don't,
but either way
I can't talk to you anymore.
No, no, you sit here.
- Why?
- Those two over there
are opposing council
and his client.
What does that have to do
with where I sit?
It has to do
with where I sit.
- I don't understand.
- Let me explain.
I have nothing on this asshole,
but I know he's lying.
So I'm going to bluff him
in an hour,
and this is where
that bluff starts.
So you're just gonna
stare at him?
No, I'm also going to laugh
and drink my coffee
and show him
how incredibly confident I am.
I get it.
You're trying
to get in their heads.
- Not trying, doing.
- Awesome.
I'll get us some drinks.
- You're buying?
- My dad's buying.
- In that case,
I will take a dozen bagels,
seven donuts, and...
one of those fancy
espresso machines over there.
Don't tell me--
the results are in.
- They are.
- And?
They want me to meet
with the doctor in person.
- And?
- And I want you
to come with me.
- Louis, I--
I don't mean
to sound insensitive,
but I really think
that you should do this
on your own.
- Donna...
they said "in person."
That can't be good.
- But don't they do that
for everyone?
- Maybe they do,
but I just don't want
to be alone.
And I understand that,
but I'm not the woman
you should be asking.
- Sheila.
- She's your partner in this.
I know that, but what if...
- What if what?
- Donna, if I'm the reason
we can't have kids,
I wanna be the one to tell her.
Not some guy in a lab coat.
And if you really want me
to go with you, I will, but...
if I were Sheila,
I wouldn't want
to be the second woman
in your life to find that out.
You're right, Donna.
Don't tell me
they ran out of coffee.
No, I got something better
than coffee.
I didn't know what to do,
so I just hit "record."
Does it help?
- It sure as shit doesn't hurt.
Huh.
- Does that mean you don't have
to sit here and smile at them?
No, it just means
it's gonna be
a hell of a lot more fun.
[laughs]
Harvey.
You were supposed to be here
an hour ago.
There was something
I had to do first.
Yeah, I know
what you had to do,
and I wish you hadn't done it.
- Listen to me...
Harvey, you said
you were gonna come up here
and help me, not stir things up
with Katie.
Marcus, you said
you wanted peace, so I tried
to make peace.
- Yeah, well, what you did
was make it worse.
- Shit.
- What does that mean,
"You've been sanctioned"?
Look, it's a fine
for contacting her
without her lawyer.
It's nothing.
- No, I know you,
and there's something else.
[sighs]
If I file some kind of motion
and it's a coin toss,
the judge probably rules
in their favor.
- Are you fucking kidding me?
- Marcus, I am sorry.
You asked me to come up here,
and like it or not...
This is tough for me too,
so I tried with Katie.
Okay, Harvey, I get it.
I just wish
there was a chance in hell
that it would've worked.
So what are we gonna do now?
I'll tell you
what we're gonna do.
You want a peaceful settlement,
we're gonna get you
a peaceful settlement.
- Mr. Litt.
- Yes.
- Please, have a seat.
- Oh, my God,
it's worse than I thought.
I have no sperm at all.
[laughs]
Of course not.
In fact, I'm happy
to inform you
that your sperm count
is perfectly fine.
I see no reason
why you can't make
any healthy woman pregnant.
- Great, fantastic.
There is one thing, however.
- One thing.
- I noticed
on the lifestyle section
of our form,
you put down "mudding."
- Yeah.
[laughs]
Yes, it relaxes and soothes me.
Come to think of it, doc,
I think that's the reason
why my count is so robust.
- You'll have to give it up.
- What now?
- Well, your count is fine,
but due to your partner's age--
if you give up mudding,
your chances of conceiving
go up significantly.
- Define significantly.
- 80%.
Holy shit, 80%?
There's gotta be another way!
- There isn't.
What if I put everything in
but my balls?
- I don't...
- Scratch that,
defeats the purpose.
- Mr. Litt...
What if I cut down
on my sessions?
I cut it down in half,
it improves our chances 40%.
I'm afraid
it doesn't work that way.
Well, then what are you
telling me?
I'm telling you
that if you want to have
the best chance
at having a child,
you'll give up mudding
for the foreseeable future.
Excuse me.
Who is she,
and what's she doing here?
It's "go to work
with your parent" day.
She's your daughter?
Something like that.
But of course, if you're too
afraid to have her here,
she doesn't have to be here.
- Fine with me if she stays,
since this is gonna be
the world's
shortest deposition
Because you're ready
to admit you infringed
on my client's patent to create
your generic knock-off?
Because, my company
developed that drug
from scratch, and your client
has no proof we didn't.
Actually, we do have proof,
we're just not gonna use it.
[laughs]
You're not gonna use it
because it doesn't exist.
- I'm not gonna use it
because I'd like you
to lie to my face
in this deposition.
And why is that?
- So when I reveal what we know
in open court,
you not only lose this case,
you get charged with perjury.
Can't you get sent
to jail for that?
Why, yes, Joy, you can.
But you'd probably
go bankrupt, first,
trying to fight it.
both: Hmm.
You're bluffing.
You don't have shit on him.
I guess there's only one way
to find out.
So, Mr. Coleman, did you
or did you not
rip off our patent to create
your bullshit new drug?
And before you answer,
I'd like you to think back
to that decaf latte
you were drinking
before coming up here.
And, more specifically,
to the person waiting in line
by your table...
while you were trying so hard
not to look at me.
That's what she's doing here.
You set us up.
- You set yourself up
because you went
to a public place
and discussed a case
loud enough
for a 15-year-old girl
who just happened
to be recording the coffee shop
to pick you up on tape.
Now, for the last time...
Where'd your new drug
come from?
All right.
How much do you want?
Gentlemen,
sorry to keep you waiting.
My client and I
were just discussing
a few last matters.
- Not a problem.
Now that you're ready,
I suggest we start
with division of property.
- Actually, we'd like to start
with the most
important issue...
- Our kids.
- Exactly.
Because we're seeking
sole custody.
What?
We--we didn't talk about that.
And what was
or wasn't previously discussed
is irrelevant.
- That's bull--
Marcus, let me handle this.
Because they don't really want
sole custody, they just want
to start on one end
because they're expecting us
to start on the other.
But we don't want a fight,
so why don't we just all start
in the middle?
- I'll tell you why--
because we're not moving
on this at all.
- Excuse me?
- Katie, don't do this.
You did this
to yourself, Marcus.
No, he didn't.
He may have screwed up,
but you don't have the grounds
to take the kids.
- Actually, we do.
- Bullshit.
And I'm not gonna let you
play games like you did
with those sanctions.
- What sanctions?
You know what sanctions.
The ones you had your lawyer
slap me with
for coming to talk to you.
- I didn't authorize
anything like that.
- You didn't need to.
After you told me
he approached you improperly...
You thought it was
a good idea to use that
to bias the judge.
- I thought it would be
a good idea to protect
my client's interests.
Well, those kids aren't just
your client's interests.
They're my brother's children--
Well, then maybe
he should have cared enough
to put their needs
ahead of his own.
Katie, he may not have been
a perfect husband,
but I am not gonna let you say
he's not a good father.
How would you know
what kind of a father he is?
I'll tell you how.
Every time I have seen them
with him, every time
he has told me about them...
And what about
what he told you
about why we're splitting up?
- Just because he slept
with someone else doesn't mean
he's not a good father.
Slept with someone else?
Oh, my God.
He didn't tell you
what happened, did he?
Katie...
Marcus,
what's she talking about?
You know what?
You can have that conversation
on your own time,
'cause I'm not gonna
let you tell me
this is all my fault
when you don't even know
the whole story.
Let me be clear:
I'm taking the kids
because that is what is best
for them.
And if you have a problem
with that, Harvey,
you can take it up with
the man sitting next to you,
'cause I'm done
defending myself.
Katie!
Okay, you tell me
and you tell me now.
What was that all about?
- I was gambling again.
- I don't believe this...
It was just for a few weeks.
It was almost a year ago,
and I've been in a program
ever since.
- Let me guess:
you didn't tell Katie,
just like you didn't tell me.
- I was going to tell you.
- When?
After the judge took your kids?
Because they're right, Marcus.
They do have the grounds
to do that,
and you gave it to them.
- Harvey,
there's gotta be something
you can do here.
Not when I don't have
all the facts!
I point-blank asked you
what happened, and you said
it was because of an affair.
Look, I know
I should have told you,
but I'm telling you now.
Well, then you tell me,
right now, anything else
I should know,
and I mean anything.
Haley caught me
making a bet.
and I told her that I was just
playing a game,
and that it could be
our little secret.
- Are you kidding me?
- Hey, hey--where you going?
- Back to New York.
- No, please, you can't--
These are my kids!
Your kids that you asked
to lie for you.
which makes you no different
than Mom was.
No, that is not fair.
What Mom did
is nothing like this.
You asked your kids
to keep your secrets.
How is that different?
- Because it was one time
and Haley had no idea
what I was doing was wrong.
You know what?
Tell yourself
whatever you want
about what kind of man you are.
You're not just
a shitty husband;
you're a shitty brother,
and I'm done here.
[laughs]
What's this for?
Well, I know it was
a stressful day, and I thought
you deserved something
with a little umbrella.
- [laughs]
You have no idea.
- Mm.
So how did it go?
- It was great.
- Really?
What did he say?
- Mm.
He said I should have no issue
getting you pregnant,
and nothing else.
- Nothing else?
- [swallows]
Absolutely not one thing else.
That's funny,
because I was told
you have to give up mudding.
- What?
How'd you know that?
- They called me
right after they saw you.
- I don't believe this.
This is a total violation
of the doctor-patient...
Cut the bullshit, Louis.
You signed the form.
The question is,
can you do this?
- Of course I can do it.
- Are you sure?
Because you couldn't even
admit it to me.
I didn't wanna talk about it
because it was
a difficult thing,
but I can handle it.
You know nothing means more
to me than having a family.
I do know that, Louis,
but I also know
how your brain works,
and you're gonna try
to figure out a way
to convince yourself
that you can have both.
- [scoffs]
I am a grown man,
and I am telling you,
if a doctor tells me
I have to give up mudding,
then I will give it up.
- Promise me.
I promise.
[knocking on door]
[sighs]
Mom, if you're here
to talk about Marcus...
- Of course I'm here
to talk about Marcus.
Question is, are you going
to let me in or not?
Then go ahead
and say your piece,
but it's not
gonna change my mind.
Well, I don't know
if it will or it won't...
but I came to tell you
you're right.
What Marcus did was horrible,
and I understand
you being furious,
but Haley's in fifth grade.
She barely knows
what gambling is.
She knows what lying is.
She knows that her father
asked her to do it.
And Marcus feels terrible
about that.
Yeah, that's what
all addicts say.
And your brother has never
been as strong as you are,
but that doesn't mean...
- This isn't about strength.
No, it's about forgiveness.
And Marcus forgave me,
even when I failed you both,
and then he forgave you
when you walked away.
Are you saying I owe him?
I'm saying
people make mistakes.
Harvey, I know
how angry you are...
but you can't let him lose
his children.
Because I can tell you
from personal experience
there is nothing worse
for the parent or the child.
What am I supposed
to say to that?
How about if I say
what we both know is true?
This is all my fault.
I modeled
all of this behavior
for both of you,
but please, Harvey,
don't make him pay
for my mistakes.
Okay, I'll see what I can do.
But I'm gonna need
to ask you some questions.
So make yourself comfortable,
because we're gonna be here
for a while.
Thought you were done
with me.
I'm your brother.
I'm never gonna be done
with you.
- You talked to Mom.
- I did.
She basically said
it was all her fault.
- Well, it wasn't.
- I know.
But if I can forgive her,
I should be able
to forgive you too.
I figured out a way
to get you shared custody.
But I am putting
in the agreement,
you ever gamble again,
she gets the kids.
You don't live up to that,
I don't care what the law says,
I'll represent her to make sure
that's what happens.
- Okay.
Um...
this claims that Katie's
an unfit mother.
You were traveling for work,
and Haley broke her arm
at the playground.
Where was Katie?
- She was in a meeting.
Her phone was off.
- So you'd think
she'd be more mindful
in the future,
but when her son wandered off
from camp two years later,
she didn't even bother
calling them back
for three hours.
- She didn't get the message!
Well, when you got
the message, you drove up there
like a rocket to go find him.
- Harvey, you're twisting
the facts here.
- No.
I am getting your children.
- Not this way, you're not.
I know this
doesn't feel good,
but you said it:
we need a howitzer.
This is it.
- I don't care.
- Marcus...
- Katie is a good mother.
She loves those kids.
I'm not gonna let you
say these things about her.
Damn it, Marcus,
there's no other way.
You're the best goddamn
closer in New York.
Isn't that what you always say?
Well, the best goddamn closer
would find another way.
Hey, Dad.
Got you some churros.
Thanks, but I gotta say,
I thought you'd be here
an hour ago begging to go home.
Well, Samantha and I went
to Otto's Tacos to celebrate.
- Celebrate what?
- Her destroying this dude
in a deposition all because
of what I gave her.
She said I did great.
- What do you mean,
"what you gave her"?
- Well, I overheard this guy
telling his lawyer that
they stole our drug formula,
and then I just...
- Wait a second,
you overheard this?
- I didn't just overhear it,
I recorded it.
And then Samantha used it
in a deposition.
Well, she didn't
really use it,
she just threatened to use it,
which I thought
was pretty badass...
- I want you to stay
the hell away from that woman.
- What?
- You heard me.
- Wait, aren't you the one
who wanted us to work together
in the first place?
Not to work together,
keep an eye on you,
and definitely not use you.
- She didn't use me.
I volunteered.
- You don't know what she did
because you're 15 years old.
- Well, I may only be 15,
but I actually came in here
to admit that I was wrong
for not wanting to come
into work with you,
and that now I can't wait
until tomorrow.
Well, tomorrow's not gonna
be like today,
because you're gonna stay away
from that woman.
- You can't make me do that!
- You'd better believe I can.
You really are a piece of work,
aren't you?
I'm sorry, shouldn't you
be coming in here
to thank me for taking care
of your daughter?
If you think what you did
is what "taking care of" means,
I hope you never get
a goddamn house plant,
let alone a child.
- Excuse me?
Joy told me about
the stunt you pulled,
and how you told her
she did a great job.
Well, did you also tell her
it's illegal to record
someone else's conversation?
- It is not illegal
to record sound
in a public space.
That's not what happened
and you know it.
Well, it doesn't matter,
because I didn't use
the recording
because I didn't need to.
Oh, I know that,
because if you had,
we'd have a whole other set
of problems right now.
And what would those be?
Because was I did
was completely within
the bounds of the law.
- You don't get it, do you?
I trusted you with my daughter
who's been getting in trouble
and lying,
and then she does something
like this.
And instead of you telling her
it was wrong, you gave her
a goddamn cookie.
- What I did was treat her
like an adult and show her
how the world works.
Well, she's not an adult,
and she can learn
how the world works
when you and I did,
and that's not 15.
- Some of us learned
a hell of a lot younger
than that.
Well, you must have had
a shitty upbringing,
because a parent's job
isn't to teach their kids
how the world is.
A parent's job is to teach them
how the world should be.
Well, her parent asked me
to get through to her
in the first place
because he couldn't
do it himself.
- Well...
that's on me to grapple with.
In the meantime,
stay the hell away
from my daughter.
[elevator dings]
Good morning, Gretchen.
How are you this...
I'm busy, Louis,
just like you'd better get.
Which is what I'm doing here.
- Wait, slow it down.
What are you talking about?
- The Nielson depo
got moved up to tomorrow.
- Tomorrow?
Yes, and Joan Walsh wants
her quarterly update yesterday.
There are 16 other things
waiting for you in your office.
You got lunch with Sheila
at 1:00, and I don't know
what the hell...
- Stop right there.
You need to reschedule half
of those things.
That brings me
to the last thing:
I gotta go to the dentist.
- What?
Gretchen, no,
you can't leave me like this.
Did you hear me?
I got a hole in my tooth
the size of Colorado.
And before you ask me
to call Lipschitz
because you can't handle
the pressure,
he's out of town
till next week.
Good luck.
Good mudding, Louis.
- Good mudding, Louis.
- Hey, Louis, good mudding.
And good mudding to you.
- Top of the mudding to you.
- Good mudding.
[echoing]
Hey, Louis, good mudding.
Mudding...mudding...
So what's on the agenda
for today?
Nothing.
After last night's lecture,
I didn't think
I'd be seeing you today.
- Yeah, well, my dad told me
to stay away from you,
but he doesn't know anything.
- That's not true.
- Yes, it is.
He's an asshole.
- Don't say that.
Why not?
It's the truth.
I learned more from you
than any adult ever,
so if he wants me
to stay away from you,
he's wrong.
- No...
Joy, he's not.
I'm the one who was wrong.
That car I boosted
when I was 14?
I didn't tell you
the other half of it.
I didn't just get suspended;
I got expelled.
- Holy shit.
- Yeah.
And after that, I had a choice:
either get my shit together
or get nowhere in life.
So by the time I was a senior,
I got a scholarship and...
that's how I was able
to go to college
in the first place.
Well, I don't need
a scholarship. My dad's rich.
And if you think that's
your father's value,
you don't know anything.
Whether you see it or not,
he is looking out for you.
He doesn't look out
for me, okay?
He just tells me what to do.
- Telling you what to do
is looking out for you.
As someone who didn't
have anyone telling me
what to do when I could have
really used it...
you have no idea
how lucky you are.
So whether you want
to listen to him or not, I do,
and we're not
working together anymore.
I didn't think
you'd take his side.
What can I say, turns out
your father's pretty smart.
You should listen to him
sometime.
Maybe I will.
I mean, he was right
about one thing this week...
Yeah? What's that?
You are the cool one.
Joy, what I'm trying
to tell you...
is I think maybe your dad
is the cool one.
- Mind if I sit?
- Harvey, I told you,
I'm not talking to you
without my lawyer.
And I tried to tell you
that lawyers
only make things ugly.
Here's proof.
- What is this?
- It's a list of all the times
you put those kids at risk.
- This is bullshit.
- Maybe, but it's the kind
of bullshit that works
in court.
- You wouldn't do this to me.
- You'd better believe I would,
because I care
about those kids,
and I know they both need you
and Marcus in their lives.
Well, then maybe Marcus
should have thought about that
before he did what he did.
- Yeah, he should have.
But he's thinking about it now,
which is why as much
as I'd like to use this...
He won't let me.
- What?
I told him this
was the only way.
He told me to find another one
because he doesn't want
to hurt you any more
than he already has.
Katie...
he loves you...
and whether or not
you're willing
to give the marriage
another chance...
he deserves another chance
as a father.
I never thought I'd hear
something like that
from Harvey Specter.
Well, if there's one thing
I've come around on,
when it comes to family,
forgiveness
is a hell of a lot better
than anger.
I'll think about it.
That's the most I can ask.
- Hey.
- Louis, it's past 3:00.
We were supposed to go to lunch
two hours ago.
I know.
Work was a shit-show
so I--I got you these
to say I'm sorry.
- Oh...
they're beautiful.
And I have a gift for you too.
- Oh, yeah?
What kind of gift?
- The best kind.
You don't have
to give up mudding
because I've decided
to get my tubes tied.
What?
Why would you...?
Because clearly mudding
is more important to you
than having a baby,
so I thought,
"Why not make it easier
for both of us?"
- Sheila, that's not...
- You're gonna tell me
that's not mud
under your fingernails?
All right, it is--
but it was just one last time.
And how can I trust
that that's true?
Because I just told you,
work was fucking crazy.
Gretchen was coming at me
with 1,000 things.
You don't understand.
- I do understand,
because I'm the one
who asked her to come at you.
So let me just
get this straight:
you didn't trust me,
so you did this to me.
No, I didn't do anything
to you.
You made me a promise.
All you had to do was let go
of one thing,
and you couldn't do it.
- Well, it was a big thing,
and I don't even know
if it's the only thing.
Now, let me
get this straight:
you can't put the needs
of our child...
above your own.
- I'm not saying that.
Okay, then what
are you saying?
Because I may not be
a mother yet, but I know
that's what parenthood means--
- So do I.
Then what happens
the first time he's sick
when we have tickets
to the ballet?
Or there's a deposition
at the same time
as a parent-teacher conference?
- Those are different.
- How?
Because I would be
giving those things up for him,
not for...
For me.
No, you're not giving
any of it up for me.
You're giving these things up
to have a child.
Do you want to know
what I'm giving up?
Coffee...
and drinking...
and cheese,
and my hair color--
not to mention the pain
of pushing another human being
out of my body.
So if you're not ready to make
this one little sacrifice,
then you're not ready...
to have a child.
Sheila, I'm sorry.
I wasn't thinking,
and I won't--I won't--
I'll just get rid
of my membership today.
No, you don't have to give up
your membership, Louis.
You just have to stop
till we get pregnant.
Don't you see?
If I keep it...
I'll be tempted.
Sheila, having a family
is far more important to me
than going mudding.
Okay, good.
[phone vibrating]
Let me guess:
you fixed everything,
and you're calling me
to tell Robert
that you'll be back
in the morning.
Okay, mind reader.
What do I have to say to that?
I don't know, Harvey, but...
I'm glad you went.
To tell you the truth...
it was one
of the hardest things
I've ever had to do.
I swear it took
a piece of me, Donna.
Well, you could look at it
that way,
or you could look at it
like you chose
to give a piece of yourself.
That's pretty good.
You should be a philosopher.
And who's to say I'm not?
Oh, now, if you'll excuse me,
I need to give a piece
of something to someone else.
Thank you, Donna.
Donna, no offense,
but a cup of coffee
is the last thing
I need right now.
Among other things,
I'm trying to give up caffeine.
I know that, Louis...
and that's not coffee.
Oh, my God,
don't tell me it's...
Iron-rich Peruvian
ground silt heated
to the recommended temperature
of 102.68 degrees Fahrenheit.
- Sheila told you
I sold my membership,
didn't she?
She did, and I have to say
I think that's
the most romantic thing
I've ever heard.
Thanks, Donna.
And thanks for this.
One more thing.
Something tells me
that you're gonna need this
for coffee
sooner than you think.
Good night, Louis.
[soft music]
♪ ♪
You have a minute?
- Depends on what it's for.
- I shouldn't have said
what I said
about your upbringing.
- And?
- Whatever you said to Joy...
I appreciate it.
- I'm glad.
Is it true, what you told her
about family?
I don't want to talk to you
about my childhood, Alex.
What is true
is you're a good father.
I overstepped my bounds.
I'm sorry.
Aww, shit...
- What?
- I told you I'm trying
to teach Joy
to do the right thing,
but I haven't done right
by you.
You told me Zane promised
your name would be next
on that wall,
but I didn't tell you
that Harvey promised me
the exact same thing.
[scoffs]
Well...
now that you have,
you wanna give it up?
No.
- You?
- No.
- You wanna share it together?
Me either.
I guess there's only one thing
left to say.
I guess there is.
- When the time comes...
- May the best woman win.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
www.tvsubtitles.net