Previously, on
"SUITS"...
Two conflict of interest
waivers giving you
the green light to take off
the gloves, get in the ring.
You gonna let him
push us around like that?
We go to court,
I will clean your clock.
Bring it on.
And this is between you and me,
not Jessica.
She admitted to being
a party to fraud
- in front of the State Bar.
- Son of a bitch.
Ah, that's the look
I came here to see.
Only thing better would be
if I were there
when you have
to tell Jessica Pearson
that you cost her
her license to practice off.
Harvey basically asked me to
impersonate Samantha Wheeler.
If Harvey wants you to do that,
why not do it?
Other than not wanting to get
on Samantha's bad side,
Louis said if too many
people got involved,
their fight could tear
the firm apart.
I got proof the packing company
skimped on materials
- and your client knew about it.
- God damn it! Robert.
What is it gonna take for you
to get off the sidelines?
Robert's about to tell Harvey
he'll put up Samantha's name
instead of Alex.
We don't do something,
we won't have a firm.
We'll have a war.
Harvey and Robert
would never vote
to make me
Managing Partner.
You leave that to me.
Think you have what it takes
to run this firm?
I know I do.
My first order of business
is promoting Alex and Samantha
at the same time.
So, what's it gonna be?
A split decision,
or are we gonna make
this unanimous?
Good morning, Harvey.
Coffee?
Don't mind if I do.
Donna,
this coffee's cold.
Well, it was hot
two hours ago.
Harvey, how could you oversleep
today of all days?
I'll tell you how.
I had a nightmare last night
that we made Louis
Managing Partner,
and I couldn't
get back to sleep.
Wasn't a nightmare.
You know it.
Instead of showing up late,
what you should be doing
is ask Louis how you can
make life easier.
Well. What I'm gonna be doing
is kicking the shit
out of Andy Malik.
- What?
- I didn't oversleep.
I spent the morning
digging into an article
about Malik's
newest client.
So you're gonna represent
the guy he's going after
to make him pay
for Jessica.
- Exactly.
- Harvey...
No one would
appreciate you
knocking down Andrew Malik
more than me,
but is day one of Louis' reign
the best time?
It's the perfect time.
In fact, I'm doing him a favor
by letting him figure out
how he wants to run
this place
in his own unique way.
- In other words, you're ducking him.
- Yup, that's what I said.
So, what do you say
you help me out with Malik?
Let me guess, by getting you
a hot cup of coffee?
It's like you never left.
Do you mind?
Of course not.
There's this little thing
called a kitchen.
Just walk down the hall
past reception
and take a left at
"I've never heated up your coffee"
and I'm not about
to start now."
So that's a no.
Excuse me, handsome.
Have you heard the news?
Why, no, Louis, I haven't.
What news?
Helo! No biggie,
you're just looking at
the newest Managing Partner
in the city.
Get out of town!
Saul and Naomi's kid?
That's right, baby girl.
The very one.
Ooh-ha!
Look at the newest
Managing Partner in the city!
You talkin' to me?
I'm the only one here.
Then all I gotta say is...
Let's go.
♪ Ooh, I'm a rebel
Just for kicks, now ♪
♪ I been feeling it
Since 1966, now ♪
♪ Might be over now
But I feel it still ♪
♪ Ooh, I'm a rebel
Just for kicks, now ♪
♪ Let me kick it
Like it's 1986, now ♪
♪ Might be over now
But I feel it still ♪
♪ Might've had your fill
- Gretchen.
- Louis.
Don't tell me you've been
walking through the place
like you own it,
doing God knows what
- to everybody you see.
- Not walking, strutting,
and high-fiving,
fist-bumping,
and a bit of this:
As you should,
Mr. Managing-Partner.
That's what I'm say...
Don't even think about it.
- Think about what?
- All right, Louis, two things.
Congratulations
and I'm proud of you,
- and I'm gonna need a raise.
- That's three things.
"Congratulations, I'm proud of
you" is the same thing.
Another thing, I will no
longer be getting your coffee,
get your car washed,
or trim your neck hair.
Gretchen! You've never done
any of those things.
And I never will.
You're just giving me shit,
aren't you?
Mm-hmm.
Louis, I don't need
a plug nickel.
I was here for you before.
I'm here with you now,
whatever you need.
Thank you, Gretchen,
and all I need
is for people to know
that there may be
a new person at the top,
but I want this firm to be
the same as it ever was.
Now, move those feet.
Come on, now!
Jim Allen.
Yeah, that's right.
Who are you?
I'm the guy
that's gonna win your case
against Andrew Malik.
That's funny, 'cause I
already got a guy to do that.
You have a guy who says he can,
but you should know
that just because a guy
talks a big game
doesn't mean
he won't get knocked out.
Why should I believe you can
handle this if my guy can't?
- You seen Rocky IV?
- Only about 30 times.
Well, Malik's Ivan Drago,
and my old mentor
is Apollo Creed.
Let me guess,
you're Rocky.
I'm Rocky, Clubber Lang,
and Apollo all rolled into one
because Malik took a swing
at people I care about.
- He knocked one out.
- And nobody fights harder
than someone looking
for payback.
And on top of all of that,
I'm the best there is
on a bad day.
So are you in?
I'm in.
Then the only thing left
for me to ask is,
is there anything
you need to tell me?
You mean did I
throw that fight?
You listen to me.
I love this sport.
I'd never do anything
to hurt it,
and if you don't believe me,
you can march
that fancy suit out right now.
I just needed
to hear you say it.
For the record,
I saw the fight.
Alonzo caught him dead-on.
Might be
a once-in-a-lifetime shot,
but there's no way Ricky
faked going down.
Then why don't you
stop telling me
something I already know
and go out there
and prove it?
'Cause I gotta go fire
my old lawyer.
Trust me, it'll go a lot
smoother once you told him
that the man
who's taking his place
is Harvey Specter.
♪ See the money
Wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
For your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
How it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
What it's like ♪
♪ I'll even eat a bean pie
I don't mind ♪
♪ Me and Missy is so busy
Busy making money ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ All step back I'm 'bout to dance ♪
*SUITS*
Season 08  Episode 11
♪ The greenback boogie ♪
Episode Title: "Rocky 8"
Robert.
Well, it's official.
I just signed over
the management of the firm
- to Louis this morning.
- And?
Well, I gotta say,
it's a weight lifted off
my shoulders.
Doesn't look like
a weight off.
Oh! You seriously gonna
say that to me today or all days?
Yeah. That's how strong
I think our bond is.
Are you sure?
Because I can make fun
of your
physical appearance too.
Really?
Huh, what would you say?
Never mind.
Listen, I heard
that you're taking on
that, uh,
fixed fight case.
I want in.
Robert...
Ah, no buts, Harvey.
I know.
Jessica was your mentor,
but she was also my friend.
And not to mention, after
15 years as Managing Partner,
I'm dying to step back
in that ring.
I get it, you don't want to be
ordered around by Louis, either.
The man walks into
my office this morning
and asks me about turning
the bathrooms coed.
Look at me. Do I look like
I want coed bathrooms?
All right, you're in.
But let's be clear.
This isn't about
avoiding Louis.
This is about handing
Andrew Malik
a big, fat public knockout.
What do you think?
I think that is something
I've waited
a long time to see.
You have no idea.
And what with
you overcoming
the difficulties
of being white,
you must've thought
you'd never make it.
And you having to deal with
the struggles of being a man.
It's a triumph
of the human spirit.
Mm.
I have to say,
I'm surprised
you went with
Wheeler Williams.
Well, I thought about it,
and a name in the middle
might get lost,
but a last name
sticks with people.
Has more power to it.
Sure.
Like Tonto,
Robin,
Garfunkel.
Shit, I may need
to rethink this.
While you're thinking about it,
how'd you do it?
- Do what?
- You know what.
Get that evidence.
Samantha,
you made name partner.
I made name partner.
Don't let something
eat you up
that doesn't
even matter anymore.
Let it go.
Thomas, Gretchen said
you were here.
- You hear the news?
- I certainly did.
Wish I was here
to congratulate you,
but I've got a problem,
Louis.
I had to fire Larry.
What?
- Why? He's been with you forever.
- Oh, I know that.
We signed this deal with
Winthrop Hotels. He let them
slip something into the fine
print about volume discounts.
I fulfill this order,
I go out of business.
And if you don't, they sue you
for breach of contract.
Sure, that is
a fireable offense.
I need you to get me
out of that contract.
Of course.
I'll take care of it.
One more thing,
I'm, uh...
I'm gonna need
an interim General Counsel.
Well, look, you know
I want to say yes, but...
Louis, I need this,
just until
I find somebody else.
Okay, I will handle things
for you in the interim,
and we'll find you
a new General Counsel.
Thank you, my friend.
Knew I could count on you.
Nina,
what are you doing here?
I came by to say
it's not gonna look very good
if the same day your name
gets on the wall,
you lose
a billion-dollar client.
- What?
- Don't "what" me.
We lost $80 million,
and I want my money back.
I'm a lawyer,
not a miracle worker.
Unless you want the ethics board
looking into what you did,
I suggest you
become a miracle worker.
What do you mean,
what I did?
You know what.
You went to my Records
Department, asked for
copy of that report, and leaked it
to Alex Williams.
Listen to me.
I never did that.
Well, if it wasn't you, it was
someone else from your firm.
Either way, you're gonna get me
my money back.
There's no legal way
to do that.
You didn't have a problem
breaking the law
to lose me 80 million.
Don't tell me
you have a problem
breaking the law
to get it back.
Harvey Specter.
What are you doing in a place
where people
with integrity work?
I came to tell you
you should've stayed down
after I knocked you out
last time,
because I'm representing
Jim Allen.
Oh, what a surprise
that you would
step into the ring
with a fraud.
Hey, speaking of frauds, uh,
how's Jessica enjoying
the Windy City?
She's doing just fine,
but you're about to get
what's coming to you.
Then you picked
the wrong case,
because there's no way
a fighter in his prime
loses to
a middle-aged has-been.
And upsets happen
all the time.
Broadway Joe, Miracle on Ice,
Eagles-Patriots last year.
What, you think
they were all crooked?
Team sports, asshole.
The easiest game in the world
to fix is boxing,
and everybody knows it.
So defend him
all you want,
but I'm not backing down.
I don't think
you understand.
I'm not just defending him.
I'm coming after you.
Because you'd rather trump up
a case against a promoter
than go after
a real criminal.
Jim Allen
is a real criminal.
He is staining a sport
that I love.
I'm not gonna
let him get away with it.
You love boxing?
Middleweight champ,
Eastern Long Island
two years in a row.
Then what do you say
we lace 'em up
and settle this in the ring?
Spoken like a lawyer with
a guilty man for a client.
Spoken like someone who's
as afraid of me in the gym
as he should be
in the courtroom.
You finished?
No. But you are.
You just
don't know it yet.
Louis, what are you doing?
Are you hiding in here?
I am working on something.
Is that something doing work
for Thomas Kessler
that should've been farmed out
to someone else?
Donna, he's one
of my oldest clients.
He lost his general counsel.
I'm not hanging him
out to dry.
I'm not saying you should.
I'm saying delegate.
I got a stack of things
you haven't even looked at yet.
You handle them.
You're the COO.
I can't.
The bylaws explicitly state
they're the purview
of the Managing Partner.
Who the hell decided that?
You did, when you
put it in the bylaws.
That the purview
of the managing Partner,
Donna, I cannot let
my clients down.
It is just not in me.
You wouldn't be. You'd be
giving him to someone
who can handle him
more closely.
What about finding
placement in a general counsel?
- Who's gonna do that?
- Louis, I just found us
a new Managing Partner.
I think, I can handle
finding Thomas Kessler
a new general counsel.
Now, the better question is,
can you handle this job
that you agreed to take?
"Great
leadership is when leaders believe
"in the greatness
in those below them
and to the side of them,
delegating greatly... ".
Are you having a stroke?
I'm quoting Churchill.
Really? It sounds like
you're quoting yourself.
Churchill, me,
same difference.
The point is,
is that Thomas Kessler
has a contract that
he needs to get out of that.
And you are
the man for the job.
Donna told you to delegate?
No, not... Maybe.
Yeah, she did.
The truth is,
you are the best man
for the job,
with the exception of me.
If you don't want
to give me the...
The reason I think
I'm better is,
Thomas Kessler is one of my
oldest clients.
We don't get him out of this,
he goes out of business.
If it were me,
there is nothing
I wouldn't do
to keep that from happening.
Louis, I hear you loud and clear.
I don't care what it takes.
This man is not going
out of business.
Thank you, Alex.
Can I help you?
Yes, I'm looking
for Thomas Kessler.
Congratulations,
you found him.
Oh.
I'm Donna Paulsen.
I'm from Zane Specter...
No, I know who you are.
What can
I do for you, Donna?
Actually, I'm here
to do something for you.
I'll find you
a new general counsel.
I appreciate
the offer,
but I've already got
Korn Ferry working on that.
And Louis Litt wants to make sure
you feel taken care of.
It's my job to see
that happens.
No offense,
but they're the best
headhunters
in the world.
What can you do
that they can't?
Tell you what.
I'm gonna get you
the top 10 candidates
by tomorrow.
And trust me. When I'm done,
you're gonna want to hire me.
Bold statement from someone
who doesn't know my business.
Well, I can't design
a lampshade
if that's what you're
getting at, but I do know
40 percent of your business
is commercial
and you passed on
a buyout last year
because you wanted to pursue
this hotel deal,
which is why you are now
looking for
a new general counsel.
I guess you do know
my business.
And for the record,
I can design a lampshade too.
But finding you
the right general counsel
isn't just about
knowing your business.
No, it's about chemistry.
- Yes, it is.
- Mm-hmm.
How do you know my type?
Well, let's see.
You're wearing a suit
that's just nice enough
to hide the fact that
you don't care about the suit,
and you don't care about it
because you don't want
your employees
thinking you're above them,
which means you do
care about the suit.
But what you care about
even more is your people.
You're saying my suit
looks cheap?
I am saying it looks
sharp as hell,
but I'm also saying
that you are a CEO
who needs a GC
who understands your POV.
Yes, I D-O-O.
That didn't come out right.
Points for trying.
So Thomas,
do I have the job or not?
Well, listen, if Louis
wants me to be taken care of,
then who am I to say...
I'll have the candidates
for you by tomorrow.
I would've thought,
given your time at Rand Kaldor,
you would've learned better
than to tangle with me.
I did. I have no intention
of tangling with you.
Then let me
tell you a story.
I just lost a huge case
for my client.
Dexhart. I like to think
of my client as Nina
because that's the woman
I have always been loyal to.
So when Nina accused me
of betraying her,
I knew something was wrong.
Turns out, a blonde woman
came in asking for their files.
She didn't say her name, just
that she was a senior partner.
Samantha...
It was a smart move,
because it didn't
break the law,
but it was also dumb,
because it wasn't hard
to figure out who it was.
I know what
you're thinking.
You didn't do this on your own.
You were given an order.
If you think
I'm going to tell you
who gave me that order...
I don't care who gave it.
What I care about is
now you're going
to take an order
from me.
What are you
talking about?
Your client Kappa Financial
is negotiating
a $70-million settlement
with the SEC
that Dexhart
is on the hook for.
You're gonna get them
off the hook
by getting Kappa
to admit fault.
- They'll never do that.
- I guess someone's
gonna have to slip it into
the deal without them noticing.
You said it,
I didn't break the law.
There's nothing
you can do to me.
You said it yourself,
you didn't want
to tangle with me.
If you think
I can't find something
where you did cross the line,
well, then you haven't
been paying attention.
All right. I understand we're here
because of a motion to dismiss?
That's right, Your Honor.
He has no proof my client
ever defrauded anyone.
Never? What would you call
rigging a scale before a fight?
If you're talking about
the Watkins-Lopez fight,
that was 15 years ago,
and Omar Watkins was a kid
that made a five-pound mistake.
Or Jim Allen's a promoter
who let an overweight fighter
break the rules and then paid
him $50,000 to lie about it.
Alonzo, I'm Robert Zane.
Been a fan for a long time.
Have a seat.
I'll have a seat, but let me
save you some time.
Ricky didn't take a dive.
You sound pretty sure.
I'm sure because I felt
my glove smash his face.
Defense is right,
Mr. Malik.
Circumstantial evidence
from 15 years ago isn't enough.
How about the fact a huge bet
was placed before this fight?
A lot of bets were placed
before this fight.
Not $100,000 on the underdog
at the last second.
You know everybody
counted me out?
Now the only thing
they're counting to is 2: 10
because I dropped that chump,
plain and simple.
$100,000?
That's right, Your Honor.
All in increments
of $9900.
Increments? Then you don't know
it was the same person at all.
Not to mention
the fact that $9900
is under the legal
reporting requirements.
By $100, which is awfully
convenient if you're trying to
break the law and not draw
attention to it, like Jim Allen did.
Jim Allen's not dirty.
I don't care
what that lawyer says.
I didn't take a dive.
I'll tell you
something else.
I get a rematch
with that piece of shit,
I'm gonna drop him
like a stone.
The fact is, you only found
something suspicious
- by doing something suspicious.
- I was doing my job.
Your job isn't to look
at bets under $10,000.
I'll look
at whatever I want.
When I find out
who made those bets,
I'll have your fraudulent
client dead to rights.
That's enough. The evidence
is sufficient to move forward.
Your Honor...
Enough, Mr. Specter.
This case is going to trial.
I'm guessing
by that look,
- we're going to trial.
- We are.
The judge denied our motion
because Malik
made Jim look guilty.
- You think he is?
- No.
He looked me in the eye,
told me he was innocent,
and I believe him.
I feel the same way
about those fighters.
Well, the next thing
we need to do...
Harvey, the next thing
we need to do
is tell Louis
what's going on.
If there's any chance
that we could lose this thing,
he deserves to know.
I tell him that, he's gonna
tell me to drop this thing,
which I am not gonna do.
How is that
gonna make him feel?
I'll tell you how,
like a Managing Partner,
because Louis is
running this firm now.
And we need to respect him
enough to tell him to his face.
So if you're not gonna tell him
what's going on with this...
I will.
All right, I'll tell him.
Louis, can I talk to you
for a second?
Yeah, of course, Harvey.
You know my door's always
open to you.
Good.
Robert and I are taking a case
that you might not like,
and since
you're Managing Partner now.
Harvey, let me stop you
right there.
Already?
Yeah, I don't need
to hear any more.
Good luck with your case.
You don't want
to hear what it is
before saying you're good
with me taking it?
No, I know. Because you're good
with you taking it.
Louis, if this is
some kind of Jedi mind trick
that Lipschitz
taught you...
I don't know
who Jed Mindtrick is,
but I do know I intend to be
the world's best delegator.
If I'm gonna do that,
there's no way I can
- try to tame you.
- In that case...
I definitely can't
put a saddle on you,
much less try
to ride you bareback.
Ride me what, now?
Bareback.
I said, ride you bareback.
Please don't...
don't say "bareback" again.
Why not?
Harvey...
Listen to me.
You are a wild stallion,
and wild stallions
have to run free.
Louis, I'm really
not comfortable
with where this
conversation's going.
No, no.
Shh. Shh...
All I'm saying is that
you're a magnificent steed
that gallops wherever
the wind takes him,
and I'm not gonna
ride you hard
until, you know,
you're able to start
bucking underneath me.
Now, you tell me,
how is that possibly
uncomfortable?
Nothing, Louis.
Nothing is uncomfortable.
Then giddyup, Harvey.
Giddyup.
Hi-ya!
Katrina,
it's after 10.
What are you
doing in here?
I just got promoted,
Donna.
I'm not gonna take
my foot off the gas.
I wouldn't expect you to.
So whose tab
are you running up?
What?
Who's the client?
Kappa Financial.
I thought that settlement was
locked for closing tomorrow.
Just making some
last-minute tweaks.
Katrina,
what's going on?
Why would something
be going on?
If you were just making
last-minute tweaks,
then either Brian
would be doing it,
or some paralegal would.
Samantha wants me
to make good
on what I did for Alex.
You mean what Harvey
asked you to do
and I advised you to do
though you didn't wanna do it?
That's what I mean.
And don't tell me,
it's not exactly ethical.
No, it's not,
but if I do it right,
the worst that'll happen is,
we'll lose a client.
If you do it wrong,
you'll get disbarred.
What difference does it make?
I don't have a choice.
It won't make any difference
if you refuse to do it.
Have you met
Samantha Wheeler?
I'm not going to make
an enemy out of her.
I have met her,
and I can talk to her about...
I don't want you
fighting my battles.
Then fight them yourself,
because you're
a senior partner now.
You need to decide what
kind of lawyer you wanna be.
I want to be the kind of
lawyer who runs her own firm.
And look at the ones who have:
Jessica, Robert, Harvey.
They all do shit
like this.
Maybe they do,
but you know what else
they all have in common?
None of them are pushovers.
Four clean strikes in a row.
Crosby doesn't look swayed.
- Talk to Louis?
- I did.
And?
Evidently,
I'm a wild stallion
who needs to run free.
We're being managed
by a crazy person.
Speaking of being managed,
it's nice
I can count on you
to roll up your sleeves
in my absence.
You think I'm watching this
for my own amusement?
Don't think you're planning
on making a comeback.
I was watching it
to see if I got played.
What are you talking about?
All those last-minute bets
just shy of the limit.
That couldn't have been
just coincidence,
so I called in a favor,
got some specifics.
You mean Samantha
called in a favor for you?
Me, Samantha,
doesn't matter.
I found out
who placed those bets,
and each and every one of those
people are connected to Jim.
Robert, I looked
the man in the eye...
Let me finish.
The total winnings
of those long shots
was $2 million,
and we both know
Jim Allen would be a dumb-ass
if he risked his empire
for a payout that small.
And Jim Allen's no dumb-ass,
which puts us back
to square one.
No, Harvey,
it puts us right back
in the ring.
If all of those people
are in Jim's orbit...
They're in Ricky Crosby's
orbit too.
It only takes one man
to throw a fight.
You think he played you.
I think there's
only one way to find out.
And for the record,
my playbook is a lot deeper
than just Samantha Wheeler.
So she did it for you, then.
That's exactly
what I'm saying.
Alex, where you been?
I've been looking for you all day.
I'll tell you where.
I was getting screwed
by Winthrop Hotels
and figuring out what to do about it.
What do you mean
getting screwed by me?
I went in there with a dozen
win-win offers, and they
shot down every one.
- Did you threaten litigation?
- I threatened them
with everything
but the kitchen sink.
But the fact is, this contract's airtight,
and they know it.
What are you exactly gonna
do about it?
Because Thomas has to honor
that contract,
- he's out of business.
- No, Louis, he's not.
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about
slicing and dicing.
You wanna run that
by me again?
Slicing and dicing is...
I know what
slicing and dicing is, Alex.
You tell me your big idea is to split
his commercial division
from his retail? 'Cause I told you
the survival of his company
- was important to me.
- I know that Louis.
But this is the
only way out.
Cutting someone's arm off
is not a way out.
It is if their life
depends on it.
In this way, we have a chance
to get Winthrop
back to the table
before we cut anything off.
Listen to me. We are not
going back to Thomas
saying, "Congratulations,
now you're a three-legged dog."
And I'm telling you
this is the only play.
You're...
You know what?
This was a mistake.
I take full responsibility.
Things were fine.
I do not want them to change.
Louis, it doesn't matter
whether you handle this or...
Goddamn it, Alex,
it may be
the only play for you,
but it is not for me.
Now, I told you I would do
anything to keep him alive,
and it's gonna start with me
taking back this case.
- Louis...
- Gretchen, whatever it is,
I don't have time
'cause Alex shit the bed
with Thomas
and I need to fix it.
Well, you better make time,
because Andrew Malik
just trashed this firm
in the Journal.
Shit,
so that's what he's up to.
You want me to get
Harvey in here?
No, it's his case.
I don't wanna get involved.
If you ask me,
you need to let Alex
handle his business
and start making sure
Harvey isn't ruining yours.
Gretchen, I appreciate you
bringing me this,
but what I need is
to run my firm
how I feel it should be run,
and now, that means
taking care of Thomas
and trusting that Harvey
will take care of himself.
You're the boss.
Well, that was fast.
Told you,
I'm good at what I do.
These are the top three
candidates in the city.
You are not gonna find a more
qualified lawyer anywhere.
Wow. Okay.
But you should hire this one.
I'm sorry, you want me
to pass on these superheroes
for a guy who graduated middle
of his class from SUNY Buffalo?
Did you check to see whether
my nana's available?
Thomas,
he didn't go to Harvard
and he graduated the middle of
his class for the same reason.
He was working full-time
to put himself through school.
And if you give him a shot,
he will go to the ends
of the Earth for you.
And on top of that,
you're gonna love him.
He's just like you.
- Handsome.
- Stupid.
But is he funny?
Because he can't
be funnier than me.
We can't have that.
Bad for morale.
Not so much other people,
just mine,
but still, it... You know.
Can I go now?
Yes, you can.
And listen,
thank you for this.
Um, I'm gonna meet with Brendon
as soon as I can.
Great.
Would you tell Louis
I'll send those contracts
at the end of the day?
- Louis?
- Yeah.
I gotta say,
I appreciate the fact
that he hasn't handed me off
to somebody else.
I didn't think
that he would keep me,
considering he's got an entire
firm to run, but...
- pretty amazing guy.
- Yes, he is.
Let me know how it goes
with Brendon.
Will do.
Pow-pow!
Pow, pow, pow, pow!
I'm done, baby.
Looking good, champ.
Getting ready
for a rematch?
- You're Jim's lawyer, right?
- I am.
I'll need your help
with his defense.
I got excelled... in boxing for 30 years,
but it's not often
you've to come face-to-face
with the likes of you.
You looking to test yourself,
that's a bad idea.
I'm here to pick your brain.
The guy I spar with,
whenever he throws a hook,
- I never see it coming.
- Here's the thing:
You don't have to see it
as long as you move inside.
- You're saying work the body?
- I'm saying you...
that right kidney enough times,
he ain't throwing that hook.
You go to the body
too often...
- What about the uppercut?
- That's why you gotta
- stick and move.
- But if you stick and move,
you could walk
into that left cross.
That can't hurt as long
as you keep your hands up.
Then let me
ask you something Rickie..
Why didn't you keep
your hands up against Alonzo?
- What?
- You dropped your hands
against Alonzo,
and I know why.
You took a dive.
Yo, what the fuck
you just say to me, man?
'Cause anyone that knows me
knows I would never do that.
Really? Because, I have a whole list
of people that know you.
If I have to put them
on the witness stand,
they'll testify that you
told them to bet against you.
So, unless you're telling me
that Jim was in on it...
Jim had nothing
to do with it.
You better call a lawyer
and call one fast.
Wait, stop.
I would've killed
to be in your shoes.
You had your whole career
ahead of you.
I didn't have shit
ahead of me!
What are you
talking about?
Three months ago,
I went to go pick up
my daughter from kindergarten,
all right?
At a certain point,
I didn't remember
why I was in my car
or where I was going.
Drove around an hour,
trying to remember,
till the school
finally called me.
Yo, I'm 35 years old, man.
You know how messed up that is?
I know how
messed up it is
to let Jim go on trial
for a crime you committed.
Well, Jim hasn't been
getting his head bashed in
since he was 15,
all right?
And-and I need to provide
for my family.
'Cause where am I gonna be
in 10 years, huh?
Am I gonna be able
to hold down a job?
Am I gonna need somebody
to wipe my ass?
I don't know, Ricky.
All I know is
Jim is innocent.
And it's my job to make sure
the world knows it.
Louis? I just talked
to Thomas, and he said
you took the case
back from Alex.
He wanted to mutilate
the man's company.
I'm not gonna let him.
What about your company?
Because, I'm willing to bet
my entire salary you haven't
even looked at
the stack of files I left.
I was working on it, Donna.
Then Gretchen walked in with...
With what?
I don't believe this.
What are you gonna do about that?
- I'm not gonna do anything.
- Malik's making us look like shit
and you're not gonna
at least talk to Harvey about it?
No, I'm not. I'm gonna tell you
exactly what I told Gretchen.
I am managing this firm
as I see fit.
Then I'll tell you
what Gretchen should have.
- You're doing a shitty job.
- Excuse me?
You're doing a shitty job
as Managing Partner.
I'm not gonna let that happen.
You're not gonna...
I'm your goddamn boss!
Yeah, because
I put you there.
No, you didn't put me shit.
You begged me to save
this firm, and I did.
While we're talking
about this firm and bosses,
you're also Harvey's boss
and Robert's boss,
and you haven't been
overseeing them.
You said to delegate.
That is exactly what I did.
You weren't delegating, Louis.
You're abdicating.
And you're using Thomas' case
to stay in your comfort zone
rather than...
I am not giving up
my clients.
I'm sorry to tell you
this, Louis,
but what you want
doesn't matter anymore.
And I'll tell you
something else.
It's not about your clients
anymore, either.
It is about
steering the ship.
And you haven't been
steering it, either.
Katrina.
Funny, I was just coming
to see you.
Well, that won't
be necessary.
I assume that means
you've done what I asked.
No. I did what
Donna asked.
She figured out what was
going on and wanted to step in.
And let me guess, you said
you'd rather handle me yourself.
I did.
And like I said,
this isn't what
you asked me to do.
Then what is it?
I went through
Dexhart's files
and found $10 million
in savings
by closing loopholes
in their policy exclusions.
They lost 80 million.
And if you
can't explain to them
that this is just the tip
of the iceberg
in making them whole,
that's on you.
What's on me is to say
that you will not determine
the type of lawyer
I want to be.
What is that
supposed to mean?
It means I looked into those
details like Louis would.
I found another way
like Harvey would.
And you want me to accept it
like who would?
Because you left out Robert.
And I don't think
if you did to him
what you did to me,
he'd accept it.
And I don't think
Robert would've done
what you did to me
in the first place.
But in addition to this,
I'm willing to say
I owe you one.
So make an enemy
of me or not.
That's the best
you're going to get.
"Well," what?
I got a call from Ricky
telling me what happened
and asking me
what we're gonna do.
What do you think we're going to do?
We'll wait for Malik
to make a fool of himself,
and then show
- he got the wrong guy.
- In other words,
throw Ricky
under the bus.
Not in other words,
in those exact words.
Harvey, the man
has brain damage.
I don't give a shit
what he has.
He was gonna let his mentor
go to prison.
You don't know
what he would've done
- if it had come to that.
- I know that he threw off a fight
in the sport I love, and what
happens to him isn't my problem.
You must live in
a damn nice glass house.
You designed... of the fact that
you threw a fight
on behalf of one
of your own clients.
If you're talking
about Reform Corp...
I'm talking about
William Sutter.
You think Rachel
never told me about that?
That was to get Mike
out of prison.
And Ricky threw a fight
to take care of his family.
Look. if you're so sure of yourself,
what do you think we should do?
We should go to Malik,
tell him he has the wrong guy,
and cut the best deal
we can for Ricky.
Are you out of your mind?
We took this thing
to get payback for Jessica.
Ricky is our trump card.
Now, if you're not okay with
this, the door is right there.
I'm not going anywhere,
and this case
is as much mine
as it is yours.
It's not either one of yours.
It's mine.
Excuse me?
I said, it is mine.
I'm not gonna let you jeopardize
this firm with some vendetta.
What happened to me
being a wild stallion?
What happened is I was afraid
to tell you the truth.
And the truth is,
I am running this place,
and we all need to get
on board with that,
and it starts
with you reading me in.
Okay, Louis.
We'll read you in.
But there is no way I am
letting Malik off the hook.
Look, we've been over this
all night.
It comes down to a choice
between cutting Ricky a deal
and payback with Malik,
and I am not going...
Wait a second.
Payback. That's it.
What's "it," Louis?
Where are you going with this?
How much revenue
has Jim lost
since these charges
were brought?
I don't know. His license is suspended.
He hasn't been able
to book a fight.
What's your point?
My point is, once we show he's innocent,
someone needs to pay back
all the revenue he's lost.
That someone is Andrew Malik.
Louis, I don't wanna take his money.
I want to ruin his reputation.
What Louis is saying
is that Malik won't pay it.
The state will.
Which means the voters will.
You talking about
suing him for compensation
under the Wrongful
Prosecution Act?
You bet your
sweet hindquarters I am.
Which means he either
cuts Ricky a deal,
or any higher-office aspirations
he has, they're done.
You think Jim Allen
will forgo a lawsuit
just to get Ricky
a better deal?
Once he finds out
why Ricky did it, yeah, he will.
Harvey, there's only one problem.
You wanted to ruin
Malik's reputation.
This deal won't do that.
You leave that to me.
And, Louis,
you're a genius.
No, Harvey.
I'm just...
a Managing Partner.
What's that for?
Your wife told me
you were here.
I wanted to pick up the check.
I'm sorry, Alex.
I gave you the case,
and I need to trust
you're gonna bring it home
how you see fit.
Well, I'm sorry too.
- What do you mean?
- I gave up too quickly.
If it weren't for you
pushing me,
I wouldn't have figured
the way out of this thing.
The way out?
Yes, Louis, the way out.
Because, I got to thinking.
Larry didn't just make
one mistake.
He made two.
He never ran
the final contract by you.
Holy shit, he didn't.
He always does
because he knows...
You'll catch any mistake.
He didn't make a mistake.
No, Louis,
it was on purpose.
Isn't it a coincidence
that Larry just signed
a contract to work
at a subsidiary of Winthrop?
Alex, this is brilliant.
We need to get them
on the phone right now.
Already taken care of,
Louis.
Contract is back
exactly the way it was.
Well, with
a 25 percent increase,
and by 25, I mean 40.
Nice work, Alex.
Right back at you, Louis.
Let me get this straight.
You'll come at me
for Jim Allen's losses
if I prosecute Ricky Crosby,
who you know is guilty
and wasn't even your client
until today?
What he was
isn't important.
What he is,
is getting a deal.
So. take your medicine
and count yourself lucky
that we're willing
to horse-trade.
If we weren't, you'd be
fucked right now.
Which you are anyway
because you're gonna be issuing
a public apology for going
after an innocent man.
No way. I admit that,
it ruins me for higher office.
What do you think
I'm here for?
You wouldn't be in this position
if you didn't
go after an innocent man
in the first place.
I will issue an apology
first thing tomorrow.
No, you will issue one now.
We're not giving you a chance
to weasel out of this.
We even did you a solid
and wrote one up for you.
Robert,
did you know there are
12 different synonyms
for the word "incompetent"?
After he signs this,
there's gonna be a 13th:
"Malik."
You know, you think
this is funny.
But sob story or not,
a crime was committed here,
and you are using it
to ruin my career.
So you...
You better
watch your backs.
Tomorrow's gonna be
what tomorrow's gonna be, Andy.
But for today,
Jessica Pearson
sends her regards.
Katrina. I was on my way out
to meet my wife for dinner.
You're gonna have
to push that reservation.
I'm not going to sit on this
another minute.
- Sit on what?
- The fact that you sold me out.
- I did no such thing.
- Yes, you did.
Because when you signed
Gavin Andrews,
I specifically asked you
to make sure Samantha
never found out
I gave you his name.
She never did.
I never told her.
You might as well have.
Because, two days ago,
she came at me
saying she knew
I was the one
who got those
files for you,
and unless I did
some shady
- shit for...
- Shit.
Katrina, I'm gonna
go tell her right now
- to back the hell off.
- You're not gonna tell her anything.
I handled it.
Then why are you
coming to me?
Because, the silver lining
of this whole thing
is it gave me a chance
to figure out
what kind of lawyer
I wanna be.
And the kind of lawyer
I want to be is one
who tells you to never put me
in this position again.
- Fair enough.
- Good.
- Is that all?
- No.
It's not.
Because I also want to be
the kind who tells you...
you owe me one.
Hello, stupid.
You calling to tell me
how a certain interview went?
I am.
Met with Brendon.
It went great.
Hired him on the spot.
- In other words, I'm amazing.
- You are.
Which brings me to why
I'm really calling.
I don't think Brendon's the
only one I have chemistry with.
- Thomas...
- Have dinner with me.
Thomas, I'm flattered,
but you're a client, and...
Before you finish,
let me ask you this:
If I wasn't a client,
what would you say?
- I'd say yes.
- Okay, then.
Here's what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna give you
a bit of time,
I'm gonna ask you once more,
and if you still feel
the same way,
then I promise
I will never ask again.
Fair?
Fair.
Good.
And listen, Donna, either way,
thank you for keeping
my business going.
Donna?
Can I talk to you
for a minute?
About what?
About Katrina.
Samantha, before you jump
all over me...
I'm here to say I shouldn't
have done what I did.
- But?
- But...
you could have come
and told me that yourself.
Maybe.
But the more I do this,
the more I realize
that sometimes
people just need to learn
things on their own.
I guess I did need
to learn that on my own.
No, I was talking
about Katrina.
What about me?
We were just saying what
a great lawyer you're gonna be.
That's funny,
because I was just coming by
to tell Donna
what a great COO she is.
Since we're passing out
compliments,
what do you say we do it
over drinks?
- Fine by me.
- Me too.
How about we meet
in the lobby in 20 minutes?
I've got something
I need to take care of.
If you run into Gretchen,
I guarantee you we'll have
a much better time.
Hey.
- Do you have a minute?
- Of course.
I was actually just about
to get to the...
stack of things you left.
- Listen, Louis...
- Donna, I am sorry.
Everything you said
was right.
I was avoiding the job.
And if it hadn't been for you,
I would've gone
right on avoiding it.
I take it this means
you and Alex worked it out.
- We did.
- Well, I'm sorry too.
I said terrible things to you,
and I didn't mean them,
and I shouldn't have
said them, and...
- Donna.
- I know I didn't make you.
Managing Partner, Louis.
But I was a part of it,
and I felt responsible
for it, and...
You didn't want to regret
making it happen.
If I'm being
really honest, yeah.
But the truth is, we all need
to learn in our own time,
and I just found out
I'm no different.
I'll tell you what.
If I'm keeping score,
I would say we're both doing
a pretty good job.
And even if you didn't
put me here...
Donna, I wouldn't be here
if it weren't for you.
So... co-Managing Partners?
Let's not get carried away.
Okay.
Thank you, Donna.
- Thanks, Louis.
- Come on, Red.
Train's leaving the station.
Let's go.
- So you're in.
- You kidding?
You think
I'm gonna stay here
and listen to Louis' ideas
on coed bathrooms
while you fools
go out drinking,
- you got another thing coming.
- Wait a second.
You guys going out?
Can I come?
- No.
- That's fine.
You go out,
have a good time.
I got some cool shit
I gotta do.
I gotta hand it
to you, Robert.
You really came through.
Right back at you,
Harvey.
I'd say
we did our girl proud.
To Jessica.
- What?
- You know, I was just thinking.
I sold Jim that this case
was Rocky IV,
but it turned out
to be Rocky III.
You mean, the one where
Apollo and Rocky
come together
to beat Mr. T?
Sure as hell wasn't
talking about Rocky V.
You know what happens
at the end of Rocky III.
Yeah, Rocky and Apollo
go toe-to-toe.
You're wondering what would
happen if we went toe-to-toe.
I don't need to wonder.
I know what'd happen.
I'd win.
Good. Whatever gets you
through the day.
- Holy shit.
- What?
We're in here
arguing about
who's better
between you and me.
What if Louis turns out
to be a better Managing Partner
than both of us?
Jesus Christ, that'd be
the worst Rocky ever.
No, Rocky V is still
Finally, something
we can agree on.
Truth be told,
I never even saw Rocky VI.
Neither did anybody else,
Robert.
You know,
that new Creed franchise,
oh, that's quite
a little something.
- Really?
- Mm-hmm.
Maybe I should watch it
tonight.
- Wanna come over?
- Do I look like
I don't have nothing
to do but to
come and watch Rocky VII
with your lonely ass?
But I got popcorn.
I'll call Laura.
♪ Ah ♪
♪ There ain't
No running from me ♪
www.tvsubtitles.net