Previously on "Suits..."
There was a guard...
who was getting suspicious of
what was going on in there.
They wanted me to put him down.
I told him I wouldn't do it, until...
whoever was running the
show came to me directly.
Who exactly was that?
Roger Shapiro.
CEO of Reform Corp.
And then what happened?
I killed him.
So you two
were in on this together.
I have no idea what
you're talking about.
You're never gonna pull
this shit again on prisoners.
That's a signed confession
from Roger Shapiro,
saying he entered into a
conspiracy, and that conspiracy
was arranged by you.
I'm not going to stand here
and write my resignation letter
in front of you two.
What's going on with you
and Brian?
Donna, he's married.
I would never do it.
I know, but I also
know that the heart
doesn't always listen
to what the brain
says it would never do.
- Denise Gallo?
- Who are you?
Someone who knew your father.
He wanted you to have this.
- Did you know?
- Know what?
That Gavin Andrews was gonna
ask me to launder money for him?
I knew he was gonna
ask you to do something.
Help me get out of this.
What did you do with my money?
I found you a legitimate
business opportunity.
- You're fired.
- I don't think so.
Because if I can do this to you,
imagine what I can do for you.
- Hello?
- There you are.
What the hell time
do you get to the office?
I'm at my desk 10 minutes
before I need to every morning
Wich means, you tracked me down.
The question is, why?
- We've got a situation.
- What did you do now?
I didn't do anything.
One of my transport flights
was carrying some art.
Apparently, the whole depressurized,
and one of the pieces
got damaged.
- What kind of art?
- The expensive kind.
Well than, it had to be insured.
What's the problem?
The problem is the insurance
inspector just left here,
and the son of a bitch has got
the balls to say
they'd sue me for damages.
All right, I'll get into it.
Who's the insurance company?
Dexhart Insurance Group.
Shit.
What's the matter?
Is that gonna be a problem?
Just tell me, have the papers
been filed yet?
Why do you think
I'm calling you this early?
Louis...
...this is silly.
Where are you taking me?
Relax, we're there.
Then can I take off
this blindfold?
No.
Not until you guess exactly
where we are right now.
We're in my new office.
What the f...
How could you know that?
Because you told me I'd make
senior partner next quarter,
and it's next quarter.
Now, can I take this blindfold off?
Holy shit. You just suck the fun
out of everything, don't you?
In that case,
I have dreamt about
making senior partner
since I was 9 years old.
You not only fought
for me to get this,
I wouldn't even be
at this firm without you.
And on top of all that...
Louis...
this office is the most
beautiful thing I've ever seen.
All right. I was wrong.
You don't suck the fun
out of anything.
Thank you, Louis.
Thank you for fighting for me.
Samantha, we need to talk.
- Let me guess. Gavin called you.
- He did.
Then you know
we have a conflict,
which means, one of us
has to drop their client, so...
Do you have Gavin's
private line,
or do you need me
to give it to you?
I don't need anything,
because you're gonna call
up Dexhart Insurance
and tell them you can't handle
this particular matter.
Are you kidding me?
You wouldn't even have Gavin
if it weren't for me.
Doesn't matter how I got him.
I'm not dropping him.
Alex I told you, the guy
isn't worth the trouble.
View this as an opportunity
to cut him loose and be done.
Wait a second.
Did your client say they wanted to
sue mine, or did you suggest to it?
What difference does it make?
The difference is,
I thought we were past this.
Well, if this is how you're making
your play for partner,
it's not gonna work.
The only play I'm making is to
protect my client from yours,
because Gavin
sabotaged that plane.
And I know that
because I know everything
else he's done.
And you just admitted using privileged
information against a former client.
And I'm not gonna have you
tossed of this just for that.
You mean information,
like using a member
of your client's family
against them?
That's not breaking privilege.
And you know it.
Neither is catching that asshole
with his hand in the cookie jar.
Cut the bullshit Samantha
and step out of the ring.
Because this thing isn't happening,
no matter how much you want it to.
I don't want it.
My client does.
And I've never stepped out
of a ring in my life.
So, either call Gavin,
or someone can do it for you,
because this case
is moving forward.
Nice home you've made
for yourself here, Robert.
Nicer than the home
you should have, Tommy,
since you belong in prison.
Funny you say that, because
that's why I'm here.
What are you talking about?
Talking about he fact that you're
sitting pretty in this firm
after you forced me out of mine.
You're lucky that's all I did.
Because you're responsible for
the deaths of multiple inmates.
- According to you.
- According to Frank Gallo.
That's right,
you got him on tape
saying what monsters we all are.
And then you used it to blackmail
me into early retirement.
But that gave me
plenty of time to think.
Why the hell would Frank Gallo
cooperate with you
if it meant admitting to murder?
What are you getting at, Tommy?
You and this firm
offered Frank Gallo money
for his daughter in exchange
for fabricated testimony
that you used to leverage me.
And now I'm here...
to make you pay.
You're coming at us to get revenge
for something you actually did?
I'm coming at you
for what's owed to me,
which is compensation
for the firm that I lost.
How about you compensate
the families
of the people
that you had killed?
Because the only thing that you are
owed are a pair of prison stripes.
And if you do this,
I promise you'll get them.
Robert, if I wanted empty threats,
I would have brought this
right to Harvey.
But I didn't,
because I wanted to be here
to see the look on your face
when you realized
I'm going to take you all down,
just like you did to me.
Let me get this straight.
Tommy Bratton is
accusing us of conspiracy,
and suing us for $20 million.
Blackmailing us for
$20 million dollars.
Call it what you want.
I'm not giving that son of a bitch one nickel.
What are we gonna do, Robert?
Because I hate to say it:
we did conspire with you.
I'll tell you what we're gonna do.
We'll go through every piece
of communication on that case
and make sure there is nothing
lingking me to this firm.
Robert, I went to your house.
Mike went to your house.
We never exchanged one e-mail,
phone call. We're good.
I don't feel like risking
my future on your memory.
Wait, maybe we don't have
to risk anything on anything.
What are you talking about?
We're talking about
someone close to Bratton
who might be able to
stop this thing dead in his trash.
You like Eli Gould.
Exactly.
He was Bratton's partner.
What's more,
Alex got him on tape admitting that
he committed a disbarrable offense.
Which means, you've been dangling
a sword over his head ever since.
Guess what.
I got the sword right here.
That settles it.
We have our game plan.
Hold on, if this thing
goes to trial,
couldn't Bratton
end up in prison?
What are you getting at?
Why would he risk that
just to get revenge?
People do crazy things when they
think they've lost everything.
Now, let's get to it.
We've all got something to do.
Samantha, whatever it is,
now is not the time.
Too bad. We have a problem,
and his name is Gavin Andrews.
Oh, what now with that man?
Long story short,
Dexhart Insurance
needs to sue Starboard Airlines.
How exactly is that
supposed to happen
when we represent them both?
Why do you think I'm here?
Better not be to get me to
tell Alex to drop his client.
Robert, you know Gavin is not worth
the headache. He needs to go.
Here's a better idea.
Since you and Alex
each just lost a client,
these two clients stay.
What?
You think I wouldn't find out
about that Rand Kaldor shit?
- Robert, I was going to...
- Listen to me.
This firm is under attack.
We can't do this right now.
What do you mean?
That's none of your concern.
But, what is your concern
is fixing this situation.
And how do we do that when neither
client is gonna back down?
I'll tell you how.
You and Alex stop
acting like children,
get your clients into a room
and get them assembled.
What do you propose we do
when that doesn't work?
Samantha...
instead of taking up
more time that I don't have,
I propose you make it work.
Good morning, Katrina.
Can I help you with something?
If this conversation
goes as planned,
you're going to be helping
me with a lot of things.
I don't understand.
I just made senior partner.
- So it's official?
- It's official.
And as my first act...
Brian Simon Altman,
will you be my associate?
Katrina, I'm honored.
But before I answer,
are you sure the two of us
working so closely together
is a good idea?
What?
I mean, we've become
good friends.
So it might get complicated
if I officially work for you.
I appreciate that, Brian.
But I'm okay with it if you are.
In that case, I would love
to be your associate.
Then I suggest we start with
some ground rules.
First, every day, you get here
before everyone else.
- Done.
- Next, power ties only.
Not any of the ties
I have seen you wear.
Been meaning to replace
my collection anyway.
Finally...
I don't wanna yes man.
So I don't care
what the topic is.
If you disagree with me,
I want you to push back,
whether it'll
piss me off or not.
Are we clear?
If I say yes to that, that would mean
I'm being a yes man.
So I don't know what to do right now..
I'll tell you
what you're gonna do.
You're gonna help me win the case
that's going to put us on the map.
Hey.
Do you have a second?
Only if you have an hour to go
through that box over there.
Actually, I think I may have
a better way to spend my time.
Okay. What's going on
in that brain of yours?
I didn't want to say it
in the room,
but I don't think
Eli Gould is the only person
we should be going to.
We need to pay a visit
to Gallo's daughter.
You think she knows
something that can help.
I don't know what she knows.
But we better find out.
Because there's a chance
Bratton has her in his pocket.
Who knows what lies he told
to get her. You're right.
I'll go right now.
No, no, no. That's what I'm trying
to tell you. It can't be you.
I know you're part of
the firm's leadership, but...
Harvey, if Bratton has
convinced her of some bullshit,
it'll be next to impossible
to change her mind.
And the man who put her father
away in the first place
isn't the one to do that.
You're right.
Do what you can.
Oh, finally.
I've been looking for you.
Why? Got another
lawsuit to drop?
Actually, I have
a settlement to reach.
Are they putting something
in this coffee?
It sounds like
you're backing off.
Alex...
Robert doesn't want
either one of us
losing any more business
right now.
You asked him to make me
drop Gavin. He said no.
The important thing is,
keeping both clients
wasn't a request.
It was an order.
Which means we need to figure out
a way to stay out of court.
- We do.
- Well...
I'm not selling out my client
just to please Robert saying so.
What exactly are you suggesting?
I'm suggesting
that we do what two people
that like to go to war
sometimes have to do.
Find a way to make peace.
Eli.
I hope you don't mind.
Your wife let me in.
Louis Litt.
You've got some balls,
coming to my house.
I knew you might not like it,
which is why
I brought you a gift.
Is that what I think it is?
If you think it's the only
copy of the recording Alex
claims made that night,
then yeah, it is.
- I'm offering it to you.
- Why would you do that?
I thought we could
work out an arrangement.
You get Tommy Bratton
to back off his lawsuit,
you get back the one thing
that can cost you your license.
What makes you think I'd
help you just to get that back?
Eli, I don't think you fully
understand the situation.
We may have forced him out,
but his name
is still on your wall.
You take this to court,
you're risking the name
Bratton Gould
forever being associated
with corruption and murder.
When he convinces a jury
that you fabricated material
just to blackmail him,
the world's gonna think
you're liars.
That little tape of yours
will be worthless.
And the name Bratton Gould
will be just fine.
Eli, you need
to think this through.
The man is guilty.
The man was my partner.
You cost him millions.
Blackmailed me twice
with that thing already.
And now, you're gonna pay.
Eli, please.
Get the hell out of my house.
This is a bunch of bullshit.
I take it that means
you're up to speed?
I'm not just up to speed,
I know more about
women's clothing
than I ever thought possible.
Then you know Hi-Rise Fashion
has been ripping off
our client's designs.
I do.
The thing I don't know
is how we're gonna stop them,
because copyright laws
are notoriously vague.
Which is why when we win,
it's going to make a statement.
Then since I'm not supposed
to be a yes man, I have to ask.
You sure
you don't want our first case
to be a guaranteed win?
Okay, the truth is, I'm not just
doing this to make a statement.
I'm also doing it because
the designer's my friend.
Which means
this case is personal.
And I told myself
that when I had enough clout
to pick my cases...
I would pick hers.
In that case,
why don't you tell me
what our first move is?
Easy.
Tomorrow morning,
we slap them with this.
Denise Gallo?
Yeah?
My name's Donna Paulsen.
I'd like to ask you
a few questions.
About what?
I was wondering if a man named
Thomas Bratton came to you,
asking about the money
you received from your father.
He came to me, to ask about
the money I got from you.
What'd you tell him?
I don't know what my
father did to get that money.
A man came to my home
and dropped off a check,
and I wasn't about
to turn it down.
And didn't that man also tell you
that your father
was a good person?
So, what if he did?
So these people are trying to say
that we paid him off to lie for us.
And it isn't true.
What do you want me
to do about it?
I want you to take
the stand and testify.
Your father died trying
to redeem himself.
They're trying to
take that away from you,
and you can't let them do it.
Let's say I believe you,
and Frank actually had changed.
Thomas Bratton told me
the reason he got killed
is 'cause of you.
Are you gonna tell me
that's not true?
No.
I'm not.
Because they might lie to you,
but I won't.
Frank never would have
tried to redeem himself
if we hadn't contacted him.
So yeah,
he might still be alive.
But the reason he's dead
isn't because of us.
It's because they killed him.
Well, it doesn't matter,
'cause I never knew
the man he became.
I only knew the man he was,
and that man
would have lied, cheated,
done whatever else it took
to get what he wanted.
Which, most of the time,
was money.
If you ask me
about that under oath,
that's all I'll be able to say.
All right,
Louis, we're all here.
- What's going on?
- It didn't work with Gould.
And I hate to pile on
more bad news,
but if Bratton puts
Denise Gallo on the stand,
she's gonna say that Frank Gallo
never did a thing
that wasn't for money.
Which makes it look like
we paid him off to lie.
If we did that,
we'd conspire with each other.
Which means we're right back
at square one.
I wouldn't say that.
- What are you doing here?
- I'm here with an offer.
Give me that tape back,
I'll get him to settle.
Five million, and you two
admit what you did.
- No deal.
- It saves you money.
It also puts us in a position
of losing our licenses.
Which is what he's been holding
over my head for two years.
- I don't give a shit.
- No deal.
Look,
I thought about
what you said last night.
But if I'm gonna convince Tommy,
I gotta give him something.
Sign a civil admission,
and we'll seal it.
Sealed or not,
we sign something like that,
it finds its way to the bar.
Listen to me.
I want this to go away as much
as you, but I'm telling you,
this is the best
you're gonna get.
I hate to say this, but I think
maybe we should take his deal.
We can't trust Eli Gould.
And we sure as hell
can't trust Tommy Bratton.
And I think you're forgetting
that they may be lying
about the Gallo part,
but you and Robert did
what they're saying.
So what?
So we may have no other choice
than to trust them.
I'm not trusting shit,
because I know
what's going on here.
And it goes back
to Donna's original question.
You mean, why would a man
like Tommy Bratton risk prison?
And the answer is, he wouldn't.
This whole thing is
a good cop, bad cop bluff,
and I'm gonna put a stop to it.
How?
The way you put
a stop to any bully.
You take his bluff and you
shove it down his throat.
Those are lovely.
Whose are they?
I'm sorry?
She means, who designed them?
Since we know your people didn't.
Just like they didn't
design this or this or this.
I don't know who you are,
but these items were part
of our last spring line,
and we designed them ourselves.
What you mean is you copied
my client's designs,
then beat her to market
and undercut her price.
I see what this is,
because I've seen it before.
And no associate
at some middling law firm
is going to shake me down.
I'm not an associate,
I'm a senior partner.
And this isn't a shakedown. It's
a chance at a settlement before
we clean you out in court.
Then file your suit,
because it's a thin line
between theft and inspiration.
Particularly in
a creative industry
where people have
similar ideas all the time.
My lawyers
have assured me of that.
Have they also told you about
Johnson v. Olympia Records?
Because a songwriter was awarded
15 million for plagiarized work
in exactly the same situation.
And since precedents
can cross industries,
in particular
the creative ones...
We thought $15 million for our
client's designs would be fair.
We'll give you 24 hours
to consult your lawyers.
After that,
we'll see you in court.
As your lawyers, it is our job
to go to war for you.
Most of the time,
that means going to court.
The thing is,
court is ugly, expensive,
and most of all, it's risky.
So last night,
Samantha and I came up
with a way to avoid all that.
The painting in question had
a market value of 120 million.
Our proposal is that Starboard
Airlines pay 45 percent,
with no admission of fault.
Let me get this straight.
You want me to pony up
$50 million dollars
when we didn't do anything?
Gavin, it's a compromise.
There's gotta be pain
on both sides.
That's a lot of pain on mine,
and not enough on theirs.
You've got exposure
for the full 120.
So I'd say, you're
getting a hell of a deal.
I don't care what you say.
Then I'll say it.
If anybody's coming out
ahead here, it's you.
- And I don't like it.
- Nina, listen to me.
No, I did listen to you.
Two days ago, when you said
this shady son of a bitch
destroyed that painting
intentionally, and you'd prove it.
I don't believe it.
Shady son of a bitch.
Is that how you talk
about your former clients?
- Gavin...
- Yeah, that's what she said.
Nina, this deal puts money
on the table now.
You don't take it,
I will appeal this till 2020.
Assuming we don't get it tossed,
which we will, knowing what I do
about how you and
your company do business.
About how I do business?
You gonna let him
push us around like that?
Alex, this is a loser for you.
Get your client under control.
Don't tell me how to handle my client
when you started this whole thing.
And don't talk to me about this case
being a loser.
- You lucky you're even in here.
- Bullshit.
You're lucky we're in here.
We go to court, and I
will clean your clock.
Bring it on.
- If only we could.
- As far as I'm concerned, you can.
'Cause I've had enough of this.
You want my money Samantha,
come and take it,
'cause I'm not signing
any deals with anyone.
Harvey, can I talk
to you for a second?
What about?
About the fact that I've had
it with Samantha's bullshit.
Slow down. What's going on?
What's going on is,
she deliberately encouraged
Dexhart Insurance
to sue my client.
And I'm tired of tip-toeing
around the situation.
Meaning?
I wanna go toe-to-toe
with her in trial.
You want us to go to trial
representing both clients?
Harvey... I was in a room
with all sides today.
They wanna fight
as much as I do.
They'll waive conflict.
That would work Alex, except we can't
afford having two partners
fighting a death match
in front of the world when...
we need to look unified.
What do you mean,
"we need to look unified"?
What's going on?
I don't wanna get into it,
but we're handling it.
Here's the thing Harvey.
We're not unified.
Even if we were,
those two clients aren't gonna settle.
So like it or not,
my next move is going to court
to get her kicked off this case.
Samantha, if you're here
about your case
against Starboard Airlines...
You know about that?
I'm a name partner.
It's my business to know
when one of our attorneys
files suit against another.
While we're on the subject
of filing things,
Alex Williams filed this.
This is a motion to force you
to recuse yourself.
Yeah. He's trying to get me
kicked off my case,
which means you're gonna
kick him off instead.
- Wait, what?
- You heard me.
Alex is gonna drop Gavin.
You're gonna make him do it.
Wow, you want that done,
you go to Robert.
Robert's not here,
and I need it now.
- Well, I can't do it for you.
- You can and you will.
Because you owe me.
Oh, no. You don't get to call in
that chit for this.
I get to call it in
for whatever I want,
because you came to me
and made me drop Delta,
and then I went against Robert
when you wanted back on the case
he took from you.
So we are dropping Gavin Andrews
whether you like it or not.
You come here for the steam?
Because I hate to break it to
you, you gotta take the suit off.
That's a good one, Tommy.
But I'm here to tell you
I don't care if you get
Eli Gould or Mother Theresa
or Gandhi
to be your good cop.
We're not taking your deal.
I don't know what the hell
you're talking about?
I didn't offer a deal.
Oh, yes, you did,
because you don't have the
balls to risk going to prison.
That's funny.
What are you gonna say
when I put you on the stand
and ask you point-blank,
"Did you conspire
with Harvey Specter?"
You talk a big game, but
it's not going down like that.
Because I'm gonna say that you
conspired to keep people in prison
for the purpose of lining
your own pockets.
And when you end up
in prison yourself,
every inmate in there is gonna
know that's exactly what you did.
Now who's talking a
big game, Robert?
I am.
Because we're gonna show
this video of Frank Gallo
calling you out.
We might even put it up
on YouTube.
You're making
a big mistake, Robert.
I'm calling your bluff.
So drop this thing.
Or go ahead
and pick a trial date.
But Tommy, just to be clear,
when they close that cell door,
you're not gonna last the night.
Harvey, we need to talk.
If it's about Robert and
Bratton, I haven't heard back yet.
It's not.
It's about Alex and Samantha.
- What did he do now?
- Not him. It's her.
She wants me to make him
drop Gavin Andrews.
Then, what the hell
are you doing in here?
- Just tell her no.
- Here's the thing, Harvey.
I gave her a chit.
I owe her. She knows it.
Now I don't know what to do.
- Alex was right.
- What do you mean?
I mean, I've had about enough
of Samantha's bullshit.
So I should sacrifice my honor
and not let her
cash in her chit?
No, Louis, I'm saying
the complete opposite.
Katrina, we've been going over
this all day. We've got them.
- They'll take the deal.
- Maybe they will.
But I am going to keep dotting
my I's and crossing my T's.
I need to be sure.
What you need is for someone
not to be your yes man.
And that starts right now.
Brian...
Katrina, you just
became senior partner.
I bet you haven't even
taken time to celebrate yet.
- I'll celebrate after we win.
- No, you won't.
Because there'll be another case,
then another.
And if you don't stop
and appreciate the big moments
when they come...
you'll regret it.
What are you saying?
I'm saying, I'm pulling rank.
We're going out to celebrate,
and we're going out right now.
What the fuck
do you think you're doing?
- Whoa Alex, calm down.
- You told my client
we're dropping him,
and you want me to calm down?
You're lucky I'm not
putting you on the floor right now.
Listen to me. I had to it.
It was the only way.
The only way to what,
screw me over?
Alex, I owed Samantha.
The only way for me to get out
of it was to do this for her.
- So you put her over me.
- No, I didn't.
Because if she wasn't asking for this,
she'd ask me to back her for
name partner when the time comes
instead of me and Harvey backing
you for name partner right now.
You're telling me I'm name partner?
Because I didn't get the memo.
Harvey's going to Zane
as we speak.
Well Louis... the second you put
my name on the door,
I will call Gavin and drop him,
like a hot potato.
Until then, he's my client,
and don't you ever contact him
without my knowledge again.
To ZSL's newest senior partner.
You've already
toasted me four times.
I figured you're new to this
whole celebrating thing.
I wanted to show you
how it's done.
Well, in that case...
to ZSL's best associate.
Because, Brian, that precedent
was a stroke of genius.
Thank you.
By the way...
how did you come up with it?
The music industry
is the perfect parallel,
yet no one's ever
thought of it before.
It's actually
a little embarrassing.
What do you mean, embarrassing?
I thought about
the music industry
because I considered
becoming a songwriter myself.
- You're kidding.
- No.
In fact, Julie and I talked
about it a long time
before finally deciding
on law school.
Let me guess.
She wanted you to take
the safer route,
and you wanted to explore
your artistic side.
Actually, the other way around.
When I told her
I was gonna be a lawyer,
she said I should have more
faith in myself as an artist.
You're lucky to have someone
who thinks so highly of you.
I am.
But the thing is,
once I moved into law,
I found I loved it as much
as I ever loved writing.
What?
Nothing, it's just...
Julie doesn't understand that,
and sometimes, I wish she would.
Anyway, it's nice to be able
to talk about law
with someone
that's actually interested.
If that's what
you're looking for,
consider me happy to discuss
the nuances of the law anytime,
because I love it as much as you do.
Thank you for tonight, Brian.
This was exactly what I needed.
Thanks for asking me
to be your associate, Katrina.
I'm really happy you did.
Oh, Harvey, good.
You can help me go through
the last of these files.
I'm not going through anything.
Robert.
Not until we've talked
about Alex Williams.
If this is about what I think it is,
we already talked about it.
No, we agreed to kick
the can down the road.
Well, this is the end
of the road,
because Louis and I are backing
Alex for name partner right now.
Harvey, now is not the time
to be discussing this.
Yes, it is, because Samantha
and Alex are about to go to war.
If you're talking
about Dexhart Insurance,
- I told her to settle.
- Well, she didn't.
She went to Louis,
called in a chit
to make him drop Gavin Andrews.
I didn't let you
become managing partner
just so your lieutenant...
You didn't let me do anything.
And if Samantha did that,
I'll deal with her.
How?
Because as far as I can tell,
you've never dealt with her.
OK... you listen to me.
No, you listen to me.
You let her do whatever she
wants since she got here.
Alex has been fighting for
this firm ever since he got here.
And I made him a promise...
Before you two go further,
we've got a bigger problem.
Tommy wasn't bluffing.
He just sent over a trial date.
- It's for a week from today.
- Shit.
Exactly. So you two need
to stop fighting each other,
because now we've got
to fight him.
No, we don't. Because I know why
Bratton's doing this.
What are you talking about?
You thought Bratton wouldn't
risk going to prison for this.
Well, he will, and I know why.
I don't know about you,
but getting here at 7 a.m.
isn't as easy with a hangover.
I don't care, Brian,
because Hi-Rise Fashion
just dropped a bomb.
Wait, what? How?
- We've got them.
- In court, yes.
But they just cut a huge deal
with our manufacturer.
Suddenly, our manufacturer
is telling us
they no longer have the
capacity to handle our product.
You mean they made it
a condition of their order,
which is illegal.
Yes, it is.
And if they did it to us,
they did it to others.
I'm gonna tell them I'm going to
the DOJ if they don't back off.
No, without proof, a threat
like that could be construed
as inducing
malicious prosecution.
You can't do it.
Well, I have to do something.
Because instead of spending
my time last night
thinking about
how to prevent this,
I took my eye off the ball.
Katrina, don't be so hard
on yourself.
You couldn't
have seen this coming.
I might have seen it coming
if I'd stayed here
like I wanted to instead of...
letting you convince
me to go party.
Hold on a second.
You're saying this is my fault?
Because I didn't convince you,
I invited you.
And you said you wanted an
associate who would push back.
Push back on case work.
Not tell me not to do my job.
Then let me push back right now,
because you bluff these guys,
you're opening yourself up
to huge exposure.
So what?
Harvey Specter
bluffs all the time.
Harvey Specter has
a 15-plus-year track record
of kicking people's asses.
So you don't have faith in me
to pull this off.
I didn't say that.
I'm saying it's not a risk
worth taking,
and I'm not gonna let you do it.
Well, Brian,
there's a time to push back
and a time to get in line.
I'm going there
at 3 p.m. today,
and you are either
with me or you're not.
Then I'm not,
because this is a mistake,
and you know it.
Harvey, you have a minute?
I'm about to file a few motions.
But, yeah, I have a minute.
I was under the impression
you don't normally file
your own motions.
Well, it's kind of important.
What's on your mind?
Trouble in senior partner town?
How'd you know?
Because that's the first thing
that happens
after you make it
to senior partner town.
Well, then, long story short,
it's my first case,
my back's against the wall,
and my only way out is to bluff.
- But?
- I'm opening myself up
to significant exposure,
and...
I'm not sure I can pull it off.
Then think of another way out.
How come?
Because if you're not sure
you can pull it off, you won't.
And Katrina, life is long.
You don't want to start senior
partnership with exposure.
Now... I got to go.
Thank you, Harvey.
I see they're letting
you use your old office.
First Robert, now you.
Well, he had his turn at bat.
We thought it was time
for me to have mine.
Go ahead, take your best shot.
Like I told Robert,
I'm not bluffing.
That's the thing, Tommy.
We know you're not.
We figured out why.
You don't know what
you're talking about.
Yes, I do.
Turns out three months ago,
you were diagnosed with cancer
and given a year to live.
Well, if you know that,
then you also know
I'm never going to settle.
What I know is what our
trial strategy's gonna be.
Motion to delay,
motion to delay,
motion to delay.
The wheels of justice
turn slowly, Tommy.
Which means even if you win,
you won't be here to see it.
You really are a son
of a bitch, aren't you?
No. You did this.
You brought this on yourself.
It's time to let it go.
Spend what time you have left
with your family.
Just let me go back to my firm
for nine months more,
and I will drop this.
I can't let you do that
because I've seen what you do.
I'm not gonna let you
get back in the game
and do something like this
to someone else.
Then you know what?
Delay all you want.
Because they say when you're
fighting something like I am,
you have to have something
to live for.
Well, you just gave me two years
to live on hate alone.
Now, get the hell out of here,
and I'll see you in court.
That looks like a job
for your associate.
If you're just here
to talk me out of my bluff,
you don't have to worry.
I'm not gonna do it.
Good.
Because you don't have to.
I don't believe it.
You got proof they colluded
with our manufacturer.
I did.
Brian, how did you get this?
Simple. I called up the factory,
pretending to be in Hi-Rise's
contracts department
and started complaining
about how all we had
were verbal assurances
they'd uphold our agreement.
Eventually, they agreed
to sign a memo.
They agreed to
incriminate themselves?
Not exactly. I told them copyright
laws are notoriously vague,
so their memo could be too.
But even a vague memo is enough
for us to get them investigated.
Or threaten to.
But now...
you can do it with proof.
Did it occur to you
that misrepresenting yourself
like this
could have opened you up
to huge exposure?
It did.
But I decided
it was worth the risk.
Because my job may be
to push back,
but it's also to have your back.
And from now on, I will.
Two more years on hate alone.
He said that?
He not only said it,
the son of a bitch meant it.
He's gonna fight us
until his last breath.
What?
A man gets told he only has so
much time left on this earth,
you would think that would
put things in perspective.
You would.
But I guess
he'd have to be human.
And as it turns out,
he was more like the Terminator.
Just won't go down.
Come with me if you want to live.
I'll be back.
Hasta la vista, baby.
If it bleeds, we can kill it.
First of all, that's Predator.
Second of all,
you sound Jamaican.
Not German.
Oh, man. Get off my back, man.
You know what?
He's Austrian.
Yeah.
What are we gonna do?
We're gonna do what we have to.
We're gonna delay this
as long as possible,
and then fight it on its merits.
We don't have to
fight anything anymore.
Tommy Bratton's dead.
What?
Eli Gould just called.
He said Tommy
had a heart attack.
They think it was brought on by the
stress of fighting his illness.
And fighting us.
Anyway, for what it's worth,
Gould's dropping
the whole thing.
I gotta say, I
always thought we'd win.
But not like this.
Robert, you okay?
I don't know.
We may have been at war, but...
I knew the man for 30 years.
I could use a minute
to process this.
You take all the time you need.
How'd it go?
I didn't know you like baseball.
I didn't know you like music.
You heading home for the night?
- Yeah. Actually...
- Don't go yet.
Brian, you came through for me
in every way on this case.
And like you said
the other night,
if we don't stop to celebrate
the little things,
then what's any of this for?
I didn't know any better,
I'd say this is your way
of thanking me...
for looking out for you.
It is.
And I happen to have
made us reservations
at an amazing place
with live music
in honor of your love of music.
Katrina, I can't tonight.
I really need to get home
with Julie and the baby.
Oh.
The baby. Of course.
I'm sorry, I didn't
think about it.
No, it's okay.
If you don't have one, why
would you think about it?
Right.
But let me just say that I would
love to get a rain check.
Rain check it is.
In the meantime, I gotta go.
I'm sure you have someone else
who would love to take my place.
Oh, of course.
Have a good night, Brian.
Good night, Katrina.
Am I interrupting?
- Not really.
- Good.
Because... I happened to have walked
in on a conversation last night
that made me wanna have
a conversation with you.
I'm listening.
This...
thing between you and Alex
is coming to a head.
Harvey and Louis want Alex
to be the next name partner
and Robert doesn't.
Skip the preamble, Donna.
What's on your mind?
I don't suppose it would
do any good to ask you
to let this go and let Alex
go up there first.
- I don't believe it.
- Believe what?
That Harvey doesn't have
the balls to come in here
and ask me himself.
Instead he sent you.
He didn't send anybody.
I'm here on my own.
Well then you may have internalized
the patriarchal system here,
but I have not.
I haven't internalized anything.
I told you I'm not here
at the behest of any man.
I'm here on my own,
woman to woman,
asking you to take
the long view and wait.
I'm sure you think that's true.
But did it occur to you
to ask Alex to step down
before you came to me?
Because that's what I mean
by patriarchy.
I did think to ask Alex.
And I chose to ask you.
And I did that
because it comes down
to who the promise
was made to first.
Not the gender of the person
it was made to.
What's to stop them
from changing their minds
before it's my turn?
Because they're not gonna
put a second name up there
for at least another year.
What if they put it in writing?
You're a lawyer.
You make it airtight.
You really make a person
get to the bottom
of what's inside of them,
don't you?
- What do you mean?
- When you put it that way,
it's not about them
changing their minds,
or it taking too long,
or even Robert
getting hit by a bus.
The truth is,
I'm not backing down because...
I think I'm better than
Alex Williams.
And I'm not gonna say
that I'm not.
Then I respect your decision.
Good night, Samantha.
Hey.
I heard you won your first case.
And the fact that I
already heard about it
means you're making a name
for yourself.
So...
Thank you, Louis.
Wait a second.
Is something wrong?
Goddamn it, did they spell
Bennett with one T again?
No. Nothing's wrong.
It's...
just been a long
day, and I'm tired.
Katrina... ahem... I know you.
You don't get tired
after winning a case.
Something is going on.
It's just, I know
I should be happy right now.
I finally made it
to the top of the mountain.
I get it.
It only made you realize how much
further you still want to go.
Yes, that's it.
That's exactly it.
No, it's not it.
I have seen that look before,
and it was on my face.
Katrina...
when it comes
to that part of life...
you can't force it.
It's unpredictable.
- I hate unpredictable.
- I know. I do too.
But...
you once told me that someday,
I would find someone.
And I did.
And you will too.
Life is gonna put
that special someone
right in front of you,
and when it happens,
I know you'll be ready.
Hey, I just realized,
I never took you out
to celebrate your promotion.
What do you say we go out
and get dinner right now?
Another time, Louis.
I have some work to catch up on.
Drinking alone?
I guess what they say is true.
None of us know
how much time we really have.
No, we don't.
Listen, Robert,
I've been doing some thinking
about the Samantha
and Alex situation.
Harvey, not tonight.
Just hear me out, please.
I think we should
let them fight.
Harvey, we do that, we're
admitting our house is divided.
And we make it that much easier
for another Tommy Bratton
to try and pick us apart.
I know.
But our house is divided.
I made a promise.
You made a promise.
And if we keep doing nothing...
It's worse than letting them
settle it themselves.
One case, head-to-head.
Winner gets name partner.
You think they'll go for it?
I think they've been
wanting to go at it
ever since you two got here.
Then I say we let them fight.
You want to tell them,
or should I?
Why don't we both tell them?
But let's do it tomorrow.
Because after today,
all I wanna do is
finish this drink,
go home, and...
see Laura.
Good night, Robert.
Good night, Harvey.
www.tvsubtitles.net