Previously, on
"Suits"...
You're afraid she won't
have time for the baby.
I don't know
how it's gonna work.
When the time comes,
you'll be able to step back little
and trust that the firm's
in good hands.
We pushed the price back down
to what Teddy sold it for.
We get Stu Buzzini to help us.
Putting downward pressure
on a stock to help a takeover
attempt is illegal.
We can't ask Stu.
to do that.
- Although, I'm...
- Sure you wanna do this?
I'm sure, someone's gonna to do it,
whether I like it or not.
You wanted to
be what they wanted,
- so they would choose you.
- They can't choose you.
They've already chosen
someone else.
This deposition is over.
I have no idea
who my parents were.
I bounced around
foster care system.
What does that have to do...
I helped you because
I would've given anything
to have someone like you
looking out for me.
If you short that stock,
you make a fortune.
A good man will get
his company back.
You guarantee I'm gonna make money
and not get caught?
- What're we gonna do?
- I dunno.
But you can't be
my associate anymore.
I don't wanna wait
three days to call you.
- Can tomorrow be three days?
- What about date to tonight?
And you come on up?
- Hi. You're up.
- Been up for a while.
Hope you don't mind, uh-yeah,
I made us coffee.
What?
Too presumptuous,
right?
I was just thinking...
last night
was really nice.
It was.
And this is really nice
too.
It is.
As much as I'd love to spend
all morning with you,
I've got a big meeting.
We're actually expanding
our retail presence...
- I get it. You have to go.
- I do.
You remember
what I said last night,
about not waiting
three days?
I'd love to go out again,
Thomas.
Is tonight too soon?
Let me check my calendar...
Yep, I'm free.
Heh. I'm gonna head out.
And do you mind
letting yourself out,
because I was up
really late last night
with this handsome man
that I just started seeing.
I might just go back
to sleep.
I don't mind at all.
Sweet dreams.
Judy.
Oh, my God.
It's been years.
I know.
But you've never left
my thoughts.
Side effect of being a mother,
foster or not.
Well, it's great to see you.
Let's get some breakfast.
I'll put my day on hold.
I'd love to, but the truth is,
I don't have time.
I'm here
because I need your help.
Come on in.
I'll make us some coffee.
You can tell me
what you need.
I know you said
you wanted an animal theme
for the nursery,
so I was thinking,
what about Peter Rabbit?
Or Paddington Bear?
Or we could just do
all football.
And baseball.
All sports.
Even wrestling.
Love it. Sounds great.
You're not listening,
are you?
Sheila, I'm sorry. I just...
I just got an e-mail
that Katrina and Brian
shit the bed in a deposition,
and I...
I know you're busier
than ever.
But this baby's coming,
whether we're ready or not.
And I need you
to be fully here,
not just physically here.
- I promise, I will do better.
- Good.
Then we can decide on Peter Rabbit
and Paddington Bear
- with the designer tonight.
- Tonight?
We set it last week.
Is that a problem?
No, tonight's perfect.
Good.
And, honey, whatever's going on
with Katrina,
I'm sure
there's a good reason.
One of my kids got pulled over
while driving my car.
He's a good kid.
He reminds me of you,
in more ways than one.
I get the picture.
What happened?
There were some pills
in the car.
And they arrested him.
So he needs a lawyer.
He doesn't. I do.
What are you
talking about?
I told the police
the pills were mine.
How could you do that?
When my back
started acting up,
I had to cut down
on my hours at school.
Corey figured it out,
so he started selling pills.
And he used every penny
for groceries, or gas,
anything to help us get by.
Judy, I'm not sure
- I should get involved in this.
- Why not?
You're telling me
you didn't do this.
And you want me not to use that.
If you want,
I can refer you to someone.
No one else can understand
what's at stake for Corey
and the rest of the kids.
Because if that prosecutor
has her way,
then I'm gonna lose
my fostering license,
and they'll take my kids
away.
- I understand that, but...
- Please.
I lost you
all those years ago.
And I have never regretted
anything more.
I can't let something like that
happen again.
♪ See the money
Wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
For your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
How it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
What it's like ♪
♪ I'll even eat a bean pie
I don't mind ♪
♪ Me and Missy is so very
Busy, busy makin' money ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ All step back ♪
♪ I'm 'bout to dance ♪
*SUITS*
Season 08  Episode 13
♪ The greenback boogie ♪
Episode Title: "The Greater Good"
Synchronized  by  srjanapala
Stu Buzzini.
What are you doing
on our side of town?
Waiting for you to come out.
'Cause I didn't want
to have this conversation
in your office.
You're gonna wanna
take a look at this.
What is it?
Remember that trade
you had me make
to tank Doyle Shoes'
stock price?
I get it.
Someone figured it out.
Now they want to use it
against you.
Not just someone,
a trader at my firm.
He knows what he's doing.
And now he wants my job.
Or what?
Or he goes to the SEC.
Once they start
an investigation...
- I know.
- Harvey, what are we gonna do?
Two things. First,
you're gonna hire a consultant,
to review your firm's
risk tolerance policy.
And second?
You can tell me everything there is
to know about this trader.
How old he is, how tall he is,
what he eats for
breakfast in the morning.
What do you need
to know all that for?
Because he's got you,
which means I'm gonna have
to bluff him.
And the best way
to bluff someone
is to know more about him
than he knows about himself.
And who's this consultant
you want me to hire?
Let's just say
I got the perfect guy.
Louis, how are you
this fine morning?
Don't give me that crap.
We don't want to spy on you and Brian
shit the bed
on your perfume case?
Louis, it's complicated,
but I've got it handled.
I thought
this was you and Brian.
Well, about that.
Brian and I...
Brian and you what?
Well, I think
that this case calls
for more expertise
than Brian can offer.
I was wondering if you'd
be able to help me.
Katrina,
I just asked Samantha
to take a new client meeting
for me.
I told Sheila I'd help
pick furniture for the nursery.
I have a million other things,
I'm trying to balance.
And you were the one who said
that I had people
who could step up
if I needed to take a step back,
were you not?
- Yes, Louis, I was.
- Then you step the hell up.
'Cause I don't want the world
to think we can't handle
a simple infringement case.
There you are.
Donna, we need to talk.
Okay. About what?
For starters...
I've been looking for you
all morning.
Hi, if you must know...
I overslept.
Why? What's going on?
I need to know exactly
what you said to Stu
when we made that
Teddy Doyle trade last year.
Well, if I recall, I told him
he wouldn't gonna be a
gunslinger for long
- if he didn't do it. Why?
- See, you made sure he knew the risks?
I didn't have to make sure.
He knew before have the words
were out of my mouth.
- So once again, why?
- He's being blackmailed for it.
Holy shit. Now how you're planning
to get him out of this?
'Cause, Harvey,
we have to get him out of it.
I know.
But I need to know
who lost,
and how much they lost,
- on the other side of that trade.
- Wait. What?
I need to know
how badly Stu can get burned
if this guy ends up
turning him in.
Okay.
I'll take care of that.
Harvey, if this is about
getting financial information,
Louis is the logical choice.
Look. I know
he's the managing partner,
and we should tell him.
But I don't want him involved
- unless there's no way out of it.
- Then I know who to go to.
Robert,
can I talk to you?
- It's important.
- Of course.
I'd say good morning,
but I can see
it hasn't been good for you.
'Cause, Judy O'Brien came to my place
as I was headed in this morning.
- Judy? Your old foster mom?
- That's the one.
She's asked me to represent
her on a drug case.
She's innocent.
It's one of her kids
who's guilty.
She won't let me tell
the prosecutor that.
Samantha, as I recall,
this is the woman that took you in
when you were 12 years old.
She stuck with me, no matter
how much trouble I got in.
Till I blew it,
and the state took me away.
Then why won't you help her?
Because what if...?
Samantha, I didn't handle
my sister's case
because I was afraid.
And I've regretted
that decision ever since.
Well, if Judy goes to prison because
of me, I'll regret that forever.
If she goes
because she told you
not to tell them the truth,
it's on her, not you.
- All the same.
- No, it's not all the same.
Samantha,
when you care about someone,
you fight twice as hard.
It's the reason
she came to you.
If it were me,
I wouldn't
turn her away.
Okay.
Louis asked me
to take a meeting tonight.
I can't be in two places
at once.
Give me the details,
and I'll take it for you.
And, Samantha...
I'm proud of you
for doing this.
Mr. Stockman.
Yes, that's me.
Nick Pavonotti.
I was told to see you.
I understand, you're doing
some consulting for the firm.
That's right. And I started
looking at your trade history.
Gen Biotech,
you lost 2 million.
Shale Futures,
10 million down the drain.
Ridley Pharma, same thing.
We make bets,
and sometimes you win,
sometimes you lose.
Well, you're about to make
your worst bet yet.
What you're talking about?
You can after rethink your choice
to go after Stu Buzzini.
You're no fucking consultant.
You're right.
Then, you pursue this, Stu's not
gonna be the one in trouble.
- You are.
- What I got on Stu is real.
- That's why you're here.
- Doesn't matter what you have.
Half the guys on Wall Street
make dirty trades.
And they see you throwing
one of their own under the bus,
they'll never wanna work
with you.
Something else
about Wall Street guys:
They're more loyal to money
than anything else.
So unless
you're here to tell me
I'm moving
into Stu's office...
I'd say we're done.
Nick.
My name is Harvey Specter.
Ask around.
You'll find people who go up
against me, they never win.
So I think long and hard
about what you'll do.
Thomas, hi.
Is everything okay?
Yeah, uh... It's fine.
It's just a work thing.
Wanna talk about it?
Or tonight,
if now's not a good time.
To tell you the truth,
I just wanna go out,
and spend time with you,
and not think about it at all.
Then I'll see you tonight.
Donna.
You wanted to see me.
Yeah. I was hoping you could point me
in the right direction.
The right direction
of what?
A trader we represent is
accused of manipulating a stock.
And in order to understand
how much exposure he has...
You need to know if anyone
was significantly harmed by the trades.
Exactly.
I'll call my guy,
have the answer for you
in no time.
That's the thing, Alex.
It needs to stay
under the radar.
I don't understand.
If they're already charged,
what difference does it make...?
I never said
they're already been charged.
Then what exactly
is going on here?
'Caude, if they're not
being charged,
how do you know there was a...?
Please tell me we're not involved in this.
We may have been the
ones who asked
the trader to make the
trade in the first place.
So we're not just in it.
We orchestrated it.
We did. But it was
to save hundreds of jobs.
The guy who caught wind of it
has no idea
that we have anything to do
with it.
Then, I'll find who was on
the other side of those trades.
I'll do it so quietly,
no one will know I was there.
Did you want Brian?
Excuse me?
He said you two
have been working very hard.
Immediately he was gonna spend
the morning at home.
He should be in
any minute.
Great.
I can have him come see you
as soon as he gets in.
Unless there's something
I can help you with?
You know what, Susan?
There is.
Good afternoon.
I'm Samantha Wheeler.
I represent Ms. O'Brien.
Unless...
and you must be ready
to plead guilty,
we don't have much
- to talk about.
- Then, I'll get right to it.
Ms. O'Brien pleads guilty
to misdemeanor possession
with a hefty fine
and six months' probation.
Problem is that,
this isn't a misdemeanor.
Those pills were for distribution.
Which is circumstantial
at best.
Not based on
how many pills there were.
You know what I'll do with
how many pills there were?
I'm gonna question the count.
Then I'm gonna to adjust
for what they were cut with.
Then I'm gonna question the legitimacy
of the stop in the first place.
When I'm done, you'll be lucky
to get her on a parking ticket.
That might work
where you come from,
but no jury in this town
will believe any of that.
What's wrong with you?
Ms. O'Brien has been an asset
to this community
for 20 years.
With all the respect,
Ms. Wheeler,
you don't know damn thing
about this community.
And I don't know what that woman did
to get some Manhattan lawyer from Corner
but it won't stop me
from doing what I have to.
What is that
supposed to mean?
Do you think
I don't know what's going on here?
Those pills weren't hers.
They were that kid's.
I don't believe this.
You think she's innocent,
and you'll still throw the book
at a 65-year-old woman?
I am going to do
whatever it takes
to keep those drugs
out of my county.
Look, I am not a monster.
You want to do right by her,
convince her to make that kid
take responsibility for what he did.
I don't understand.
If the deposition
didn't go well,
can't we re-depose them?
- No, Susan, we can't.
- Why not?
Among other things,
they'll be ready
for our line of questioning.
What if...?
Just...
give me a minute to think.
Excuse me, Katrina.
Can I talk to you for a second?
Of course.
Can you give us the room?
- When were you gonna tell me?
- Tell you what?
That you were pulling me
off the Adored case.
I already told you,
we can't work together anymore.
I know,
and I let that go,
because you weren't
in the mood to talk about it.
But I didn't think
you were gonna pull me off
in the middle of a case.
Well, I wasn't going to,
but then you weren't
at your desk,
and I...
You what?
I picked someone else,
okay?
Because like I said,
it's not going to work
between us.
Oh, well, that's fantastic,
Katrina.
But when I'm your associate,
and I find out from someone else
I'm no longer on the case,
it makes me look
like an idiot.
I don't think
I should be punished
when this was your fault.
We said
it was nobody's fault.
It sure as hell wasn't mine.
It's not fair that my reputation
in this firm takes a hit
when you were the one...
I was the one that what?
You know what, Katrina?
You don't wanna work together,
then we won't.
But I aprreciate,
you think of a reason we can give
that doesn't make me look
like shit.
Harvey Specter.
Kevin Miller.
From a prison cell
to a corner office
- in record time.
- Uh, not just a corner office.
Biggest office
in the firm.
I think
things have been good?
Better than good.
The Sutter cloud is gone,
things are great
with Jill,
and the firm
is growing like crazy.
Glad to hear it, because
I need you
to make room for one more.
You're sending someone my way?
Must be a star.
Actually, Kevin, he's a snake,
but you'll take him on anyway.
And why would I
do that?
'Cause, someone I care about is being
blackmailed by this bastard.
Ah. I get it.
You're asking me
to make him an offer
to get him off your back.
That's right, except...
I'm not asking.
Harvey, come on, heh.
I mean, I've just got my life back.
I can't bring someone else...
that'll send me back to prison.
I know I owe you,
but not like this.
Yes, like this.
Because, I did hell of worse for you.
If I hadn't,
you'd be rotting in prison.
So when I call in a favor,
you don't put conditions on it.
All right. Just tell me his name.
I'll write up an offer,
and make it look like
a headhunter found him.
His name is Nick Pavonotti.
And you can skip
the headhunter part.
He'll know it's from me.
You make him an offer.
And you tell him it's not worth it
to mess with Harvey Specter.
Never thought
I'd see this place again.
I have to say, it doesn't look
too much worse for wear.
How did it go
with the prosecutor?
Were you able
to make a deal?
It's not gonna be
that easy, Judy.
She knows the drugs
are Corey's, not yours.
Then she should be willing
to go easy on me.
No, she shouldn't.
And she isn't.
Because she won't let you
stop her from doing her job.
Well, I have a job too,
and that's to protect
my children.
I won't let them ruin his life
because of one mistake.
It won't ruin his life.
They'll take him away
from me.
If you don't do this,
they're gonna take them
all from you.
I can't do it.
I can't sacrifice him
for everyone else.
- Why not?
- Because I already did that
with you.
No.
You didn't have a choice
with me.
They took me from you.
And before they did...
they asked if I wanted
to keep trying.
And I said, no.
I don't believe this.
You've been lying to me,
all these years?
I didn't want to hurt you.
If you didn't wanna hurt me,
you should've kept me.
Or at least
told me the truth about it.
I couldn't do that.
I couldn't tell you
I was choosing the good
of everyone over you.
- What would it have done to you?
- What do you think it did?
- Samantha.
- No.
Let me just get this
straight.
Rather than fight for me,
or even tell me the truth,
you gave up on me.
And then years later,
walk into my home,
to have me save you from making
the same mistake again?
You were the only person
I knew who could help.
I could have, Judy,
but not anymore.
Samantha, please.
I used that word
with you.
I said, "Please,
don't let them take me."
But you could've stopped them,
and you didn't.
So now I'm giving up on you.
Katrina, whatever it is,
I'm on my way out, so...
- That's what...
- Then, this won't take long.
I would just like
to start the process
of having Brian removed
as my associate.
What?
He's too advanced for me.
All right.
You wanna tell me what
happened between the two of you?
Or should I figure it out
myself?
- Nothing happened.
- Won't take long to figure out.
I'm pretty sure you would rather
just tell me about it yourself.
Okay, look.
You told me
not to go into the kitchen.
And I tried not to.
But it turns out,
everywhere we go is the kitchen.
So did something happen,
or not?
No. But we both wanted it to.
Then I told him
I can't work with him anymore.
Then we can't to have fight, because
he said it would hurt him
if I can't explain
why he's not my associate anymore.
And that's why
I told you that bullshit
about him being too advanced.
Bet it feels good
to get that off your chest.
Only so much because
I still don't know what to do.
Talk to him about it.
- I told you, I tried.
- No.
You told me you fought with him.
Fighting isn't talking.
- I know that better than anyone.
- What do you mean?
I mean I understand
what it's like
to have complicated issues
with someone you work with,
especially when a person can't
have a real conversation.
- What you're talking about...?
- You know who I'm talking about.
Knowing that doesn't tell me
what I should do.
I told you.
Talk about it again.
If you can't,
we'll have a real problem.
Because Brian's right.
You could really hurt
his career.
Now I'm gonna go.
Because sometimes the answer
is to fall for someone
who has nothing to do
with this place at all.
Robert, plase tell me you haven't gone
to Louis' client meeting yet.
I was just on my way.
Why?
Because I can take it
from here.
You can't be at two places
at once.
Doesn't matter.
I dropped Judy's case.
What? Samantha,
why would you do that?
Same reason any attorney would.
Because, my client lied to me.
So thank you
for covering for me,
but I've got it from here.
You're not taking anything
until you tell me
what's going on.
I've got all night,
Samantha.
I always thought
it was the state
that took me from her.
Turns out it was Judy.
She put me back
in the system,
just when I thought
I had a real home.
So tell me,
why should I stick by her
when she didn't
stick by me?
I don't know,
Samantha.
But for her to admit all of that
must have killed her.
Didn't do wonders
for me either, Robert.
What You're saying
I should throw her a party?
I'm saying that
sometimes being a parent
is living with choices
that break your heart.
It's not often
you get to make up for them.
You have a chance
to help this woman do that.
I think
maybe you should take it.
Even if I was willing to,
I still can't get her a deal.
Let's put our heads together
and figure something out.
What about Louis' meeting?
He'll understand.
If he doesn't,
you tell him to come see me.
Pretty nice office
for a fake consultant.
What are you doing here?
I made to tell you that
You're negotiating
from a position of weakness.
Because first
you try to stop me,
and then Kevin Miller
offers me a job, out of nowhere,
telling me it's not worth it
to go against you.
It isn't.
Yeah,
you keep saying that.
But I did some digging.
On the very same day
the Doyle Shoes trades
were made,
a woman,
who is now your COO,
signed into our visitors' log
to meet with Stu.
"Donna Paulsen"
I think is her name, right?
Be very careful
what you say next,
and who you threaten.
Looks like
I touched a nerve.
Nick, you have no idea
who you're dealing with.
What I know stock manipulation
is a crime.
So is blackmail.
And we can avoid prosecution
for either of those
if you stop coming at me,
and start working on
Stu Buzzini's retirement party.
But you better do it soon,
because I'm not gonna wait
much longer.
If you're trying to play a game
of chicken with me,
you'll never win.
But I'm not just playing
with you.
I'm playing with you,
Stu Buzzini, and Donna Paulsen.
Really is a nice office.
What the hell is your problem?
It's bad enough Samantha
farms out her responsibilities,
without telling me.
Then you blow them off?
- You just calm down.
- Calm down?
I take one night off
to prepare my home
for my unborn child's arrival.
I'm supposed to enjoy it,
but I can't,
because you and Samantha
don't give a shit.
You finished?
No. When you stepped down,
it's like you said,
"I can do what I want."
Apparently what you want
is to let this firm down,
let our clients down,
and most of all, let me down.
That's enough! I won't listen
to another word at your loose end.
From the minute
I stepped down,
- all I've done is help you.
- Help me?
First with Harvey
on the Malik case.
Then again with Harvey
on your poker bullshit.
Now with a partner
who's going through
something more important
than a client dinner.
Are you saying Samantha's
going through something?
Yes, Louis, I am.
I'm sorry, Robert. I...
It is just so much.
The pressure, it's just...
- It's too much.
- I know, Louis.
And I wish I could tell you
it gets easier. But I can't.
But I can tell you
do your best
not to take it out
on people around you.
You're right.
Thank you.
I'm sorry I blew up at you.
No need to apologize.
Asking you
what is going on with Samantha?
Louis, if you think your people
have something going on...
you should probably ask them
yourself.
Donna, good.
Let's grab a coffee.
Sure.
I could use some caffeine.
And since we both know
"let's grab coffee"
is code for
"shit's gone sideways,"
Harvey, just tell me
what's going on.
Nick Pavonotti put
the pieces together.
He knows we were involved
in that trade.
So the firm's
in his crosshairs now too.
Not just the firm.
He also knows that you came
to see Stu that day.
I'm sorry, Donna.
I never should've let you...
Harvey, don't even bother going down
that road. I made my decision.
We have to decide
how to fix this.
- We may not be able to fix it.
- Don't tell me.
Someone got burned
by that trade.
Not just burned.
Scorched.
A Police pension fund sold at
the wrong time, took a huge hit.
This thing comes out, you're not able
to say, "No harm, no foul."
Son of a bitch.
Harvey, if you're out of time,
- I don't see any other way.
- Any other than what?
Giving in
to what this guy wants.
No. Harvey, we can't ask Stu
to step down.
Stu knew the risks
when he made that trade.
And you can tell yourself that
to feel better,
but I'm the one
who convinced him to do it.
I only did it because you said
it's just a civil violation.
Now it sounds like
he could go to prison.
Nothing is gonna happen
if he does this.
He won't do it.
- You'll have to make him do it.
- Me?
Yeah, you.
You said it yourself.
You're the only one
who could've convinced him
to do this in the first place.
Because he trusts me.
I won't take advantage of that
until you tell me that
there's nothing else we can do.
Because there is,
and you know it.
What is she talking about?
She's talking about going
to Sean Cahill
to make him bury this thing.
He's going to wanna help us
even less than Stu.
If you want me to make Stu
take the hit for all of us...
the least you can do
is give it a shot with Cahill.
Samantha. I was afraid
I'd never see you again.
You almost didn't.
Before you say another word,
I need you to look at me.
Take a good long look.
I don't understand.
I turned out just fine.
So as far
as I'm concerned,
the problem wasn't
that you cut me loose,
it's that you lied to me.
So if you want my help,
you're gonna tell Corey
the truth.
He's gonna take
responsibility for his actions.
And then we're gonna get him
the best deal possible.
- And it won't ruin his life.
- How do you know that?
Because I know what I'm
gonna say to that prosecutor.
Sean.
What a surprise
running into you here.
You hungry? Why don't we grab
a big, fat steak.
Nah, I'd rather go vegan,
- because I know that look.
- What look?
The look, it says either "My nana died,"
or you need a favor.
All right, I do.
A client of ours
may or may not
have manipulated a stock
at our behest.
We're being blackmailed
for it,
and I need you to bury
the whole thing.
- Are you out of your mind?
- I know it sounds bad.
No, no, no. It sounds illegal.
You're lucky
I'm not arresting you right now.
Listen to me.
We onlyorchestrated
this trade so hundreds
of innocent people
could keep their jobs.
I don't care why you did it.
I'm not helping you.
I don't believe this.
I helped you
put away the man
that cost your mother
everything.
How's Mike doing, Harvey?
Because if memory serves,
I helped save his life.
You did, and
I will always be grateful.
Your idea of gratitude
is sticking to handout for more?
I wouldn't be here,
if there was any other way.
I moved heaven and earth
for you once before,
and now the well is dry.
...dig little deeper. Because,
if people found out
about that heaven and earth,
they wouldn't throw you
a parade.
You just admitted to
stock manipulation.
Instead of threatening me,
you should thank me
for not slapping cuffs on you.
I warn you,
go back to your office and pray
that blackmailer
doesn't come to me,
'cause if he does,
I'm not gonna bury this thing.
I'm gonna bury you.
All right, Donna, I'm here.
Last time I took meeting with you,
you had me to do something I regret.
I hope you're not
here to try to get me
do somrthing
like that again.
I'm here to say that that trade
screwed over a pension fund
to the tune of $20 million.
I get it. Yes, I mean,
if I don't give
that piece of shit my job,
I'll lose my license.
I'm telling you
it could get a lot worse.
- And I'm sorry...
- I don't want an apology.
- I want a way out.
- This is a way out.
- It's for you and Harvey, not me.
- Stu.
Ah, damn. This whole thing was his idea.
Now, instead of getting me out,
- he wants me to take the bullet?
- It's the only way...
Is it? It took me 20 years
to get where I am.
I'm not gonna to surrender
to some blackmailer
unless my only option is
that or prison.
What if that is the choice?
Then I'll step down.
But I'll always remember, it was
my friends that made me do it.
Allow me to ask this one,
what makes you think he won't
keep using this against us?
Harvey will make Nick sign
something implicating himself
if he brings it up again.
It'll be mutually assured
destruction.
Then if you'll excuse me,
I gotta get back.
Got lot of work to do,
while the firm is still mine.
I hope you're here
to sign my plea offer.
Because, I don't have time
for more negotiations.
I'm not signing
anything.
I'm sorry?
She's not signing on anything.
Because, we both know
she didn't do it.
So you're saying
I'm free to go after the kid.
You are. When you do,
I'll be representing him, and
I'll be giving the jury this.
And this is a rap sheet
from 20 years ago.
That's right.
Possession, theft, vandalism.
- And the name's been redacted.
- So what?
You said I didn't
know about this community.
Well, you're wrong.
I grew up here.
Those crimes?
I committed them here.
That's my rap sheet.
Nice story, but it has nothing
to do with this case.
Yes, it does. Because,
you wanted to know what Judy did
to get a lawyer like me
in her corner.
She raised me.
And if you take Corey away
from her,
he won't have the chance
to turn
into the productive member
of society
that she can help him
become.
So he's gonna plead down
to misdemeanor possession,
community service,
and it will not go
on his record.
And if I say no?
I'll take my story,
my rap sheet,
and that 16-year-old...
And you tell it again
in open court.
I can break a jury in
a number of ways. That's one.
You raised this?
I did.
And I'm proud of her.
Well, I suppose
that's punishment enough.
You have yourselves
a deal.
I'll have my office draw up
the paperwork.
Samantha, thank you.
I couldn't have done this
without you.
I could say the same thing
to you, Judy.
If you're in here,
I take it Cahill said no.
He didn't just say no.
He said I was lucky
he wasn't arresting me.
Which means Stu's our only hope.
Not necessarily.
- Please tell me you got him to agree.
- I did.
It was hard, and it hurt,
but I did.
Then he asked how we're sure
Nick won't keep holding this
over our heads.
Easy. We'll make him sign
an agreement,
- which I can draft now.
- If I'm right,
Nick won't have to sign anything,
Stu won't have to step down.
If Stu doesn't step down,
Nick goes to the SEC.
In case you weren't paying attention,
Cahill said no.
Maybe that because
you didn't him ask the right question.
What the hell
you're talking about?
I'm trying to tell you,
I have an idea.
Looking over
your future kingdom?
Sorry to disappoint you,
but you won't get the crown.
And who the hell are you?
You heard from the B team.
Well, I'm the A team.
The guy you know nothing
about.
Not my name, or where
I'm from, or what I do.
Well, I know who sent you.
- Harvey Specter isn't gonna...
- Harvey Specter didn't send me, Nick.
Neither did Stu Buzzini.
- Oh, that just leaves Teddy Doyle.
- Whom I've never met in my life.
And yet here I am,
calling your bluff.
And what bluff is that?
The one where you think
anyone is gonna to believe
you're gonna to march
into Sean Cahill's office
and tell him
your fairy tale.
Because blackmail
is a crime,
and you don't have
the balls for it.
I see what this is.
I'm not blackmailing anyone,
and you can record me
all you want.
Because it occurs to me
that I don't need Stu
to step down at all.
I just have to do
what you say I won't,
and I'll have a clear path
to the throne.
Nick.
No, no, no.
You don't call my bluff.
I call yours.
So tell Harvey, or Stu,
or whoever the fuck sent you,
it didn't work.
And get out of my firm.
'Cause make no mistake,
come tomorrow,
this place is mine.
Working late?
I have to look for another way
to get noticed around here,
now that you have to
cut me loose.
Look, Brian,
I'm sure you're busy,
- but I think we should talk.
- About what?
About the fact that
you're an outstanding attorney.
And you don't deserve
to be hurt
by a personal matter
that I should've kept in check.
- Katrina, you don't...
- No, it's my fault.
You said it,
and you were right.
I've been feeling...
pulled to you,
for quite some time.
I pretended it wasn't true,
and that I could control it.
Well, I couldn't.
But I'm not going to let it
hurt your career.
That's not fair.
I lashed out,
because I was feeling guilty
about...
You know.
And I'm afraid for my career.
And it feels like
I can't make the right decision.
And the wrong one is gonna
bring everything crashing down.
I'm feeling
exactly the same way.
So... what are we gonna do?
Well, I have an idea.
I'm not completely sure
about it.
But the one thing I do know is
that no one is going to believe
I traded you
for Susan Carter
- because she's a better lawyer.
- That bad?
Worse.
So, what's your plan?
If we work together for a year,
and it's successful,
which I know it can be...
you'll be on
the junior partner track.
You can have
your own cases.
And I can say
that you're ready
to be more than
just someone's associate.
That sounds like a plan.
Good.
Am I allowed to say
you're not just someone?
You probably
shouldn't.
Thank you, Katrina.
Thank you, Brian.
♪ A line in the sand ♪
♪ To show them what you see ♪
As you see, it's clear
stock manipulation,
involving my boss
and his law firm,
all orchestrated
to service a takeover.
- It does appear that way.
- Oh, where is that way.
And I'm not gonna let
Stuart Buzzini
put a black mark
on my firm.
And you chose to do this after hours,
because if you want a career,
you surely don't wanna do this
in broad daylight.
The thought did occur to me.
So, what now?
You're gonna
take these guys down, right?
Well, now, that all depends.
Because as much as I hate
crooked traders,
I hate blackmailers
even more.
What?
- I'm here because...
- You're here because
I wanted you here.
And, before you say you don't know
anything about blackmail,
you do. But so does Sean,
because I told him.
That's bullshit.
Shh. Save your breath.
You're gonna need to do
some thinking.
Because, I'm gonna tol tell you
the exact same thing.
That I told Harvey
when he came to me.
You're lucky I don't arrest you
right now.
- Bullshit you said that.
- He did.
Whether you believe him
or not... I do.
I'm a whistleblower.
I have protections.
Not for blackmailing charges,
you don't.
As far as I'm concerned,
I think, you're both telling the truth.
Which means,
you should both be indicted.
But since I have discretion,
I can go after both,
or neither.
I'm sure as shit
not just going after Harvey.
My question I've for you,
Mr. Whistleblower,
is do you want
to be prosecuted today, or not?
I'm sorry
to have wasted your time.
Nick,
one more thing.
Stu asked me to let you know
that you're fired.
- On what grounds?
- You remember all those trades
I consulted you on?
They were real,
and they sucked.
But Stu's a generous man.
He gave you a healthy
severance package.
Don't spend it all
in one place.
Like it or not, Sean,
we still make
a pretty good team.
Good team or not,
if he'd gone the other way,
you'd be wearing handcuffs
right now.
For what
it's worth,
we'll make
an anonymous donation
to a certain pension fund.
We'll make them whole,
Sean.
Good for you, Harvey.
But I don't wanna know
about it.
Because this is where
the gravy train ends.
And if you ever threaten me
again,
I'll take you down
on the spot.
Sean.
Harvey.
Louis,
what are you...?
I wanna
ask you something,
and you don't have to
answer, but...
If this is about
the Chelsea Connor case...
- I've..,
- It's not about the case.
Did something happen
between you and Brian?
What?
When I brought your new business cards,
you rememmber.
You were upset. You said you
didn't have love in your life.
And then yesterday,
I bring his name up,
and you get weird.
I just want you to know
I care about you.
If something happened...
Yes and no, Louis.
- Yes and no.
- What does that mean?
Brian and I developed feelings
for each other.
We didn't mean to,
and we didn't act on it.
But it got complicated,
and we messed up
that deposition.
And I know you must be thinking,
he's married, and I'm horrible.
I don't think
any of those things.
- You don't?
- No. Things like this happen.
I know that
as well as anyone.
The only thing I think
about you
is that you are the same
brilliant, wonderful,
quirky woman I've had the honor
to work with all these years.
And that's
never gonna change.
- You really think that?
- Yes.
Thank you, Louis.
Come on. Bring it in.
Unless you're worried.
If you find Brian attractive,
I can only imagine
the temptation
that this hotness
must be aware.
Too soon?
No, Louis.
Right on time.
Donna, you're calling
to get together again to night?
Because that's never be
three nights in a row.
We might find ourselves
in trouble.
I'm not calling
to get together.
- Hey. What's going on?
- You remember when...
I said I had a work thing
on my mind,
and I didn't wanna talk
about it?
Yeah, of course.
I wanna talk about it now.
- I'm right here.
- It's not always easy
knowing what the right thing
to do is in my job,
and it worked out this time,
but...
Sometimes it just sucks.
Oh, you may not believe this, Donna,
but I know exactly what you mean.
How could you?
When Louis and Alex got me out
of that contract,
it was because Larry was shady.
But what if he wasn't?
What if it had just been
a mistake?
I'd still need them
to get me out of that contract.
I wouldn't care what it took,
because it was my business.
That would've put you all
in a tough spot.
There really is more to you
than meets the eye, isn't there?
Anything you want to know,
I'm right here.
What if I wanna
get together tonight, after all?
All that, I'd say that
maybe it's time for you
to come over to my place.
Give me an hour.
Oh, and Thomas...
take your vitamins.
I'm not here right now.
So, if you want me to call you back,
say something interesting.
Hey, I just thought we could
get a drink and celebrate.
I leave it to you whether
that's interesting enough
or not.
♪ But I know
how you pay your dues ♪
You've reached
the phone number of Mike Ross.
Please, leave a message.
Hey, Mike, it's me.
I got a hell of a story
to tell you.
It involves Kevin Miller,
Stu Buzzini, Sean Cahill,
and that trade we made
for Teddy Doyle last year.
Give me a call
if you wanna hear it.
Miss you, buddy.
♪ If you want me
You can call me ♪
♪ Call on me ♪
♪ I'm not wasting
all the rest of this night ♪
♪ For a little drop
of honey ♪
♪ A spoonful is poison ♪
♪ Poison ♪
♪ But you know
You need a fix ♪
♪ What ain't enough
To kill you, darling ♪
www.tvsubtitles.net