Previously on "Suits"...
Was this whole thing
designed to get Restoration
back to the table?
It was designed to either
get them back
or to take a chance
on an up-and-comer.
Thomas isn't gonna want to be
in business with Simon
when he finds out about this.
And he's not going
to find out about it,
because we're not
gonna tell him.
Get on the ground.
Wallet and phone.
The same thing
that happened to you
happened to me.
The deal you made
was a ploy
to get Restoration Hardware
to the table.
- You know.
- You're damn right I know.
I'm taking Glen's offer
at the original rate,
and I'm putting out
an announcement about it.
You cannot do what we did.
I'm telling you,
you'll regret it.
You didn't regret it.
You don't know
what happens over time
when you do
something like that.
I'm upset
because I lost a client.
No, you are upset because
I chose Thomas over you.
Louis didn't get
the wrong guy,
and neither did you and I.
It's not about
the wrong man.
It's about taking matters
into your own hands
and what happens
when you do that.
You broke privilege,
and now
I'm gonna make you pay.
- Thomas, hi.
- Hey.
You busy tonight?
Actually, I think
I'm gonna work late.
Donna, you okay?
You sound upset.
I didn't know you were
gonna put out a press release
when you took that other offer.
Donna, the risk you run
when you're known
as a nice guy is,
people think
they can push you around.
I had to show them
that if you push me,
I'm gonna push right back,
and I'm sorry that resulted
in your firm getting fired.
We're not just
getting fired, Thomas.
We're getting sued.
Oh, shit.
Well, no wonder you're upset.
You guys are getting sued
because of me.
Well, that's the thing.
It's not just because of you.
It's because of me.
Robert.
If you're here for a drink,
I'd love to,
but I've already had
a long week,
and Rosalie's expecting me.
I'm not here for a drink.
What's on your mind?
That prison situation
you had
a couple years back.
What about it?
Those men murdered
an innocent man.
You knew about it.
And you didn't do anything.
You here to make me
feel like shit,
or is there a point
in there somewhere?
I'm not judging you, Alex.
I did something
some years back
that I'm not proud of
either.
And I guess I'm wondering...
how do you live with it?
At first, I tried
putting it out of my mind.
But then it kept
popping back up.
Then I thought about
doing something, but...
anything I tried, I'd just
end up in prison myself
for something I didn't do.
Mm.
So I guess the question is,
can you do something
about what you did?
No, I can't.
Then all you can do is try
and make up for it somehow
the rest of your life.
You stuck around and ate
the rest of my Chinese,
didn't you?
You think Laura's
gonna let me
get egg rolls
and fried rice at home?
Look, I wanted to thank you
for staying late.
It means a lot.
Don't mention it, Robert.
Whatever you need, I'm here.
You know that.
I know this
sweet and sour chicken
isn't gonna eat itself.
No, it won't--
Oh!
Samantha, you still there?
Robert, call 911!
Samantha!
I'm at--
Samantha, talk to me.
God damn it.
911.
What's your emergency?
♪ Suits 8x16 ♪
Harvey
Original Air Date on February 27, 2019
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ I'll even eat a bean pie,
I don't mind ♪
♪ Me and Missy is so busy,
busy making money ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ All step back,
I'm 'bout to dance ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
♪ The greenback boogie ♪
Harvey.
What are you doing here?
We have a problem.
Come in.
What is it?
Long story short,
Simon Lowe tried to
screw over Thomas Kessler.
You mean that lease deal
that came across my desk
was bullshit?
- Yes, that's what I mean.
Well, Harvey, I know Thomas
is one of my oldest clients,
but you can't tell him.
We're way past that, Louis.
Donna told him.
What?
How could she even know?
Because I told her.
Why the hell
would you do that?
Because she knew
something was wrong,
and I didn't know
what else to do.
I told her to give me
some time so I could fix it.
But before I could,
she told him.
Then Thomas bailed, and Simon
suspected what happened.
Let me guess.
He fired us.
He didn't just fire us,
Louis.
He hired Daniel Hardman
to sue us.
Say that again.
- Simon hired--
- No, tell me again
that Donna put her
goddamn relationship above us
and now Daniel fucking Hardman
is suing my firm.
You want to get
pissed off at Donna,
or you want
to figure this out?
I want to figure this out.
And I sure as shit know
you didn't come here
without a plan,
so what do you have?
As I see it,
we have two options,
the first of which
involves going to Robert.
Pass.
Look, he's the only one of us
that actually
gets along with Hardman.
It's the only chance
we have
of getting him
to be reasonable.
And you and I both know
that there isn't a frozen
dick's chance in hell
that that rat
is gonna be reasonable.
Then tomorrow morning,
you and I need to go in there
with an offer so good,
Simon has no choice
but to take it
and Daniel's left with nothing
but a frozen dick in his hand.
Robert,
what are you doing here?
I came as soon as I found out
where they took you.
- My purse, it had--
- Don't worry about it.
The important thing is,
you're here.
I am so sorry, Samantha.
I never should have
kept you so late.
It's not your fault,
Robert.
If anything, I should have
had my guard up.
This isn't on you.
This is on that piece of shit
who did this to you.
You're right.
We need to get
to the police station.
- I want to make a statement.
- You can do that tomorrow.
- Right now, you need to rest.
- No. If they have any chance
of catching this guy,
the first 24 hours--
Samantha,
whatever we have to do
to make this right, I'm gonna
be right there with you.
But tonight, you're staying put
and getting better.
Okay.
Thanks for being here,
Robert.
I'll always
be here for you, Samantha.
Robert.
You need something?
Yeah. You hear about this
Hardman-Pierpont Malls thing?
I did.
Alex told me.
- What did he say?
- He said he wasn't too happy
with Donna making him look
like shit with his own client.
Mm. Can't blame the man
for that.
No. You can't.
Robert, are you okay?
Because ever since
that thing with Louis--
I'm fine, Samantha.
Do me a favor.
Get to know everything
there is to know
about this whole
Hardman situation.
You never know how
it's gonna shake out.
Harvey, Louis,
good of both of you to come.
- Can I offer you a beverage?
- Oh, actually, yeah.
because this thing's
ending right now.
- What is that?
- We're doubling the money
that you lost
when Kessler backed out.
This says that Kessler
found out about
the Restoration deal
because of a clerical error.
That's right.
Information was included
on certain deal memos
that were just--
Bullshit!
You told Alex Williams.
And a clerical error isn't
gonna cut it with his board.
They need a head to roll.
Louis is just too stupid
to understand that.
You arrogant son of a bitch.
You always underestimated me.
And you're
underestimating me,
because if I'd wanted
to settle with you,
I wouldn't have called
Daniel Hardman.
I thought you said
you called him.
Did I? I must have made
a clerical error.
Regardless,
it's Louis' firm now,
not yours.
And, Louis, we go to court,
the world's gonna discover
that your firm
can't be trusted,
and then you will be
the king of nothing.
But if you admit
that Harvey broke privilege,
this can all go away.
I see what this is.
You want to use that admission
to come after Harvey's license.
Look at that.
I didn't think you had it
in you to figure it out.
Let me tell you something
that you will never figure out.
Leaders never betray
their partners.
Let's save
the betrayal talk
for Harvey's ethics hearing,
shall we?
I imagine I can win
this lawsuit
and have it scheduled
by the end of the month.
You do this,
I promise you,
I'll be the biggest regret
of your life.
No, Harvey.
My biggest regret is,
I wasn't the one to rip
Jessica's name off the wall,
so I'll just have to settle
for ripping yours off instead.
Good day,
gentlemen.
Harvey, how did it go
with Hardman?
It didn't.
What does that mean?
It means he's not
just suing us.
He's trying to get
a guilty verdict
so he can use it
and come after my license.
What?
- No, he can't do that!
- He can, Donna,
because I broke privilege,
and he knows it.
But you didn't
break privilege.
I'm the one
who told Thomas.
And I'm the one
who told Alex,
and that's how they think
Thomas knows.
So what are we gonna do?
We aren't doing anything.
Louis and I
are handling this.
But if I told them
that it was me and not you--
You'd just make it worse.
We told them
it was a clerical error,
and you'd be proving we did
what they're accusing us of.
Harvey, I'm responsible
for this.
I want to help.
I'm sorry, Donna, but--
I get it.
If I really wanted to help,
I never would have told Thomas
in the first place.
Well, I was gonna say
the genie's out of the bottle.
We can't put it back in.
But what you can do is let
Louis and I do what we have to
to get us out of this.
Samantha,
how are you doing?
Physically, I'm fine.
Mentally,
I am pissed the fuck off.
You want to talk about it?
Because we can get you
some counseling.
This isn't about
my feelings, Robert.
I got mugged like 30 other
people that night.
The police aren't gonna
do anything about it,
and you know it.
What are you getting at?
I want the name
of your investigator
and a few days off
to handle this.
You think I'm gonna let you
track down this guy yourself?
- Listen to me--
- No.
Let's say you find him.
What happens then?
You hear of
an eye for an eye?
That's what happens.
Look, if someone attacks you,
they attack me.
So we're gonna go to my guy
and find this son of a bitch.
But when we do,
we turn him over to the DA
and let them do
what they do.
No, that won't work!
I'm not asking, Samantha.
I'm telling.
If you want justice,
you're gonna get it.
That's the only way
this happens.
Okay.
We'll do it your way.
Just give me the name
of your investigator.
Harvey.
What an unpleasant surprise.
Well, it's about to get
more unpleasant,
because I got to thinking:
if Simon was willing
to double deal
behind Thomas' back,
what's to stop him from
doing it with someone else?
That is evidence
of an off-the-books meeting
between two of the largest
mall owners in America,
divvying up retailers
and colluding on rents.
So I'm giving you
a one-time opportunity
to save Simon an investigation.
Well, Harvey, you're right.
Simon did get into a room
with Westhaven,
and it was off the books.
But they weren't colluding.
- They were discussing a merger.
- Bullshit.
I represented him.
He never said anything
about this.
I'd be happy to show you
the offer we made to them.
And I assure you,
they have a copy
in their files right now.
Because you went back
and created a paper trail.
Which means
all you have on Simon
are a couple of dates
on a calendar.
And all you have on me
is conjecture about what I may
or may not have done.
- No, Harvey.
I have a phone call you made
to Travis Tanner
the night before
Restoration backed out.
Turns out, Travis just happens
to represent
the competitor of Simon's
that was drawing up an offer
to Restoration
when Kessler backed out.
Do you think Tanner
will protect you
when I get him on the stand?
You son of a bitch.
Now, now.
Name-calling
won't get us anywhere.
Or maybe it will.
Because I'm willing
to drop this whole thing
if you will do me
the simple courtesy
of putting my name
back up on your wall.
You would have to resign,
of course.
But at least you'd be able
to slink away
and start up somewhere else,
like you did to me.
You really think I'm gonna
let you get away with this,
don't you?
I think you did
what I'm accusing you of,
and the chickens
are coming home to roost.
Are you up to speed
on Hardman?
I am.
Robert, he's not
gonna give up,
and if this thing plays out
the way it's headed--
I know. That's why
I came up with this.
- Are you crazy?
- No, I'm not.
But I need you
to make that happen.
Well, then think
of something else,
because I'll never be able
to convince him to do this.
Samantha, you have
convinced people
of a hell of a lot more
than this.
Because I could get to them.
He won't even take my call.
Well, he's sure as shit
not gonna take mine.
And you can use
his hatred of me to--
You, me--it won't make
a difference.
- He hates us both.
- And if we don't do this--
I know what's at stake,
Robert.
Then I need you
to get this done.
Because I agree--
if this thing plays out
the way that it's headed...
All right.
I'll make it happen.
Louis.
This is only the second time
you've ever come to my home.
First time I was here,
I told you that I got you
out of a jam.
This time, I'm asking you
to get me out of one.
If you're talking about
Simon Lowe suing your firm,
I heard about that,
and I'm sorry.
Well, he's not just
suing the firm, Thomas.
His lawyer's using the suit
to come after
my partner's license.
- You mean Harvey Specter.
- Yes, I do.
So as your first lawyer
and your friend,
I'm asking you to help me.
Help you how?
Simon's lawyer
is trying to prove
that Harvey broke privilege,
and the only people
they can go after
are Harvey, Alex, Donna...
- And me.
- That's right.
And Daniel Hardman
has not subpoenaed you yet,
but it's only
a matter of time.
And you want me to what?
Leave town?
- Or worse yet--
- No, Thomas--
No, no, I don't
believe this, Louis.
The guy helped Simon Lowe
try to screw me over,
and you want me
to cover for him.
Thomas, listen to me.
I know you value honesty,
so I'm gonna be
perfectly honest with you.
Simon was a bigger client.
And Harvey should have
sided with him,
but he tried
to protect you anyway.
And if you don't
cover for him,
all it's gonna do
is take down a good man
who I care about.
I'm sorry, Louis.
If this Daniel Hardman
subpoenas me,
I won't perjure myself.
I assume you're here
to discuss my pending action
against your firm.
- I am.
I'm also here to drink
this 30-year scotch
with an old friend.
I appreciate that, Robert.
But what's the saying?
Never trust Greeks
bearing gifts?
I look Greek to you?
You look like a man
who's trying to have it
both ways.
And you look like one
who's letting a vendetta
cloud his judgment.
They took my firm, Robert.
It's not a judgment.
That's a fact.
And from what I recall,
you all but handed it to them
with your indiscretions.
And if you're here
to litigate the past--
- Fuck the past, Daniel.
I'm here to work
something out.
What will it take
for you to drop this thing?
I said what it would take:
my old firm back
and Harvey Specter's
resignation.
Now, you know
I can't do that.
Why not?
Because Rachel married
his protégé?
Because you and Jessica broke
the glass ceiling together?
We were friends
before any of that.
We talked about starting
a firm together.
I know that we did.
Then why are you
siding with them?
They stole everything
I built, Robert,
forced me out in disgrace,
and I have been in
the wilderness ever since.
And until my name
is up on that wall,
I'm not dropping this.
Then what if I can get
your name up somewhere else?
You mean Rand Kaldor.
Ever since I left the firm,
they've been one man down.
You could come in and--and--
And what?
They hate you
as much as I hate Harvey.
Why would they throw you
a lifeline?
Because you're
Daniel goddamn Hardman,
that's why.
Okay, Robert.
You get Eric and Ellen
to go in on this,
I will let this go.
But if you can't,
our friendship
isn't gonna stop me
from taking Harvey down.
So...how'd it go
with Daniel?
It didn't.
What do you mean,
it didn't?
He already backdated
an excuse, and not only that.
He found out I went to Tanner
behind Simon's back.
Wait, you did what?
I was trying to save Thomas'
deal without telling him.
- I had to go to somebody--
- You know what? Never mind.
I don't give a shit.
But what we need to do
is figure something out,
because this is my firm,
and I'm not gonna let that
son of a bitch take it from me.
- Louis--
- Why did you have to tell her?
That's what I don't get.
Why?
He was my client
for 13 years.
I wouldn't have
told her.
Yes, Louis,
you would have.
Last year, you came to me
about putting Sheila
over the firm.
And I told you
as managing partner,
I wouldn't do it,
but as your friend,
I would.
If I had asked you
about telling Donna,
you would have done
the same thing.
You're right.
I would.
God damn it!
What's going on, Louis?
Thomas said
that he wouldn't help us.
You mean
he wouldn't help me.
Yeah, I guess
that's what I mean.
Why couldn't Donna
just wait for you?
I don't know, Louis.
I really don't know.
You think you would have
come through if she had?
Well, I'd like
to think so.
Yeah, well, I do too.
'Cause let's face it, Harvey:
you pretty much always do.
You're right, Louis.
I do.
And right now, I think I can.
What do you got?
They said a head
needs to roll on this.
What if, instead
of one head rolling,
we give them two?
Good. You're here.
I was going over
my testimony
and could use
another set of eyes.
I don't know
how to tell you this.
I talked to Cameron Dennis.
The guy's friends put him
at a different location, and--
Don't you fucking say it.
Samantha, I'm sorry.
I never should have
listened to you.
Look,
I know you're upset--
Save it. I've got
something to take care of.
So what are you gonna do,
hire someone to break his legs?
God damn it, you told me
if we did this right,
there would be justice.
Where is the justice?
That son of a bitch gets off,
you know what that makes me?
A victim.
I am not a victim, Robert!
One of my foster parents
would hit me.
It's why I joined the service,
why I learned self-defense.
I can't be a victim
again, Robert.
I just...can't.
All right, then.
We'll go the other way.
What are you
talking about?
Cameron Dennis said
that if any new evidence
came to light,
he'll prosecute.
Let's get to
doing that, then.
No.
You took a risk once
to get me this firm.
It's time I took a risk...
for you.
God damn it, Ellen, there's
got to be something you'd--
Well, in that case,
go to hell.
Well, how much?
What's the bastard's price?
There is no price, Robert.
He said no amount
of money or clients
would make up for seeing
his firm get torn apart.
But what about Ellen?
You try horse trading with her?
I did, and I struck out
there too.
God damn it, Samantha!
I got Daniel to agree!
He thought I came up
with Rand Kaldor on the fly,
and I sold it to him.
What do you want me to say?
I want you to tell me
exactly what happened.
Because Eric Kaldor
and Ellen Rand
are two of the greediest
people I know.
So if you're trying to tell me
that they're standing
on principle,
I'm calling bullshit!
And it's pretty clear
what happened.
Eric tried to force
something down your throat,
and you let your pride
get in the way--like always.
Robert...
I offered him
half your client list,
a dividend stream
from your equity share,
a no-poaching commitment--
And if the carrot
doesn't work,
you use the goddamn stick.
And threaten him with what?
We took half the firm
from him.
There is nothing left
to take.
I'm sorry, Robert.
I did everything I could.
We're gonna have to find
another way.
Gentlemen, you have
five minutes to make your case.
You don't, this will be
the shortest lunch
in the history of lunches.
- Then I'll get to it.
We offered Simon Lowe
a settlement
no reasonable CEO
would refuse.
So we want to see
if cooler heads can prevail.
This isn't about
cooler heads.
This is about driving a wedge
between me and my CEO,
and that's not gonna happen.
- That's the thing, Elaine.
There's no need
to drive a wedge,
because it already exists.
That is an email chain
between me and Simon
from 18 months ago.
As you can see,
he was looking
to relieve you of your duties
as chairwoman.
I don't know about you,
but if someone did that
to me at my firm,
their ass would be on the
sidewalk ten seconds later.
And if this is true,
why didn't you
bring it to my attention then?
Because unlike Simon,
I'm loyal to the guy
who writes my checks.
There's no two ways
about it, Elaine.
Simon's a threat to you.
Daniel Hardman's
a threat to us.
Do you want to neutralize
those threats,
or do you just want
to sit there eating salad
while they neutralize you?
Gentlemen, I do believe
I'll bring this to the board
and see if
we can't reach a deal.
Just so we're clear,
this settlement doesn't close
if you only let Simon go.
Believe me, Mr. Specter,
when the board hears
about all of this,
you won't have
to worry about Simon
or Daniel Hardman
ever again.
Robert!
Long time, no chat.
To be honest, I wasn't sure
they were gonna let me in.
So I take it this means
you're accepting my offer.
Well...I don't accept
opening bids,
but if you want to tell me
what you need--
God damn it.
She didn't tell you, did she?
- Eric--
- No, don't.
We worked together
20 years, all right?
I know when you're stalling.
Samantha didn't tell you,
and now you're covering for her
like you always do.
All right, she didn't.
So, what, you want to mock me,
or you want to tell me
what it's gonna take?
It's simple, really.
Daniel Hardman's name
for yours.
- Excuse me?
- I said you retire,
I take Daniel on as a partner,
and that is
take it or leave it.
All right.
Let's get to it.
What the ----
is your problem with me?
- My problem?
- Yeah.
Why'd you take my firm
from me?
See, that--that right there!
That's my problem.
All we ever heard
is that it was your firm,
your name, your reputation.
You know, we had
a little something
to do with it as well.
You think
I didn't know that?
You think I never
gave you credit?
I think you never
let us forget
that it was you that got
our names on the wall.
I did put your names
on the wall!
And maybe if you were a little
more focused on the big picture
than getting a pat
on your back--
Well, you never had a problem
giving a pat on the back
to your little protégé.
- Don't you talk about her.
We would have never
gotten this place
if it wasn't for Samantha.
- So you always say.
Although you never
quite say how.
But if I had
to venture a guess--
Not another word, Eric.
If that's how you
really feel about me,
the answer is no!
I'll take my chances
with my friend!
If you're talking about
Ellen, Ellen's not your friend.
I'm talking about
Daniel Hardman.
Mark my words, we'll come
to some accommodation,
and then you and Ellen Rand
can kiss my black ass.
Well, I don't know about you,
but I think we've earned
a drink.
Well, I'd pour you one,
Louis,
but I'm fresh out
of Peachtree Schnapps.
All right,
enough messing around.
What's the big news?
We got the suit dismissed,
and Daniel Hardman
is out of the picture.
- Louis, that's great news.
- I just wish I could see
the look on his face
when he finds out
we got the better of him.
- I hate to break it to you,
but you didn't get
the better of anybody.
Robert, what are you
doing here?
More importantly,
what are you talking about?
I knew what you were
up against,
so I went to Daniel as a friend
and offered him a deal.
- What kind of deal?
I know what kind of deal,
because there's only one thing
that son of a bitch would
trade taking me down for,
and he told me what it is:
his name on our wall.
And I would never
give him that.
It doesn't matter now,
because...
when Daniel heard
that Simon got fired,
he thought I was playing him,
and he pulled the trigger
on an ethics hearing.
What the shit
did you just say?
They set the date, Louis.
When?
- Harvey, before--
- When, Alex?
This says the hearing's
tomorrow.
They're summoning you,
me, Simon,
Thomas, and Donna.
- Which means we have
less than 24 hours
to get our story straight,
convince Thomas
to corroborate it,
and get Donna
the fuck out of town.
It's not gonna work, Louis.
Leave me alone, all of you.
- I need time to think.
- Harvey--
I don't want to talk
about it, Robert.
You know, I don't care
if one day,
they get me on any of
the other shit that I've done,
but to go down for this?
To go down to him?
- Harvey, we can still--
- No, we can't!
Look, he's got me
dead to rights.
Mike was dead to rights.
Look what happened to him.
This isn't a jury.
It's a fucking ethics board.
And I did exactly
what he said I did.
- Harvey--
- Motherfucker!
I said leave me alone.
I know I'm interrupting,
but can I come in?
Why not?
Sitting by myself doesn't seem
to be getting me anywhere.
Well...maybe this will.
Technically...
You did not break privilege
when you told Donna.
In other words, I could
throw Donna under the bus.
I know you won't do it.
But it had to be said.
Then it's been said.
What?
If this were
another firm,
she wouldn't even
still be working here.
You saying
we should fire her?
If you're asking me
as a name partner,
I would say yes.
If you're asking me
as her friend,
I would say...
There's no way in hell I am
ever letting that woman go.
Never thought
in a million years
something like that
could come out of your mouth.
Well, maybe this place
is rubbing off on me.
You are all...crazy.
But...
maybe that's what
I love about it here.
He's gonna lose everything
because of me.
Donna...you never know
how these hearings will go.
You know...
the worst part is,
I don't even know
why I did it anymore.
I didn't sleep that night.
I just lay there wondering,
"What if Harvey
can't get it done?"
And then I would tell myself,
"Well, he always gets it done."
And then it was morning,
and I hadn't heard from him,
and Thomas' business
was at stake, and I just--
Donna, you told him
because you love him.
Love him?
We just started
seeing each other.
I'm not talking
about Thomas.
Third year of law school.
Rosalie went behind my back
about a pro Bono we were doing.
We got in a huge fight,
and it broke us up,
'cause I thought
she betrayed me,
and she thought I thought
I was a better lawyer.
But she didn't betray me, and
I didn't think I was better.
And none of that had anything
to do with it anyway.
What does this
have to do with me?
I was afraid of committing.
Deep down, she knew it,
so she closed the window.
And it made me realize
I didn't like being
on the other side of the glass.
I didn't do what I did to
make Harvey realize anything.
Neither did Rosalie.
She did it
so she could move on.
Thomas, I appreciate you
seeing me
on such short notice.
You said it was about Donna,
so of course I'll see you.
- What's going on?
- It's simple.
Donna was the one
who told you about Simon...
but I want you
to say it was me.
You want me to lie.
Look, I know
you're a man of your word,
but she risked all this
because she knows
how much your business
means to you.
Well, she worked
her entire life
to get to where she is,
and the truth comes out,
she'll be barred
from working in a law firm
for the rest of her life.
What am I not seeing here,
Harvey?
How does all this protect you?
It doesn't.
I just don't see
why she has to stand
in front of
that firing squad too.
All I'm asking you to do
is protect her...
like she protected you.
Oh, no, no, no.
You were the first one
to take an offer.
Yeah, but then you
went to another firm.
Because back then,
they weren't gonna hire
a man like me,
no matter what school
I went to.
I could have got you in.
They hired Jessica.
Years later.
I couldn't wait for that.
I still think we would have
made a great firm.
Zane Hardman.
Wait, why is your name first?
You let Jessica go first.
You let Rand and Kaldor.
Yeah, you're right.
I don't have to go first.
I know where I stand.
Go ahead, take it.
Hardman Zane.
No. I don't want it now.
- Excuse me a moment, Daniel.
- Mm-hmm.
Cameron?
Robert, I have some news,
and I thought
I owed it to you to call.
Please don't tell her.
Robert,
whatever it is,
- I have to testify this morning.
- I know.
Then what is it?
Remember when I said
I couldn't make up
for what I did?
I think I can.
But I'm gonna need your help,
and you might not like
what I need it for.
Well, I know what it's like
to live with a weight
on your shoulders.
And if I can help you
take it off,
why don't you go ahead
and tell me what you need?
- Thomas.
- Can I come in?
Of course.
I was just getting ready
for this morning.
I know. That's what
I wanted to talk about.
Look, if this is about Louis
coming to see you,
if I had known
he was gonna do that--
It's not about Louis
coming to me.
It's, um--it's about
Harvey Specter coming to me.
- Harvey came to you?
- Last night.
- What did he say?
- Well, he pretty much said
that he was about
to lay himself down
on the train tracks for you,
and he wanted me
to help tie him down.
Well...
I-I don't know
exactly what that means--
Who are you to him?
I don't know
how to answer that.
I got it when Louis
came to me.
This comes out,
it hurts his firm.
It hurts his partner.
He wouldn't want
to see that happen.
But then Harvey came to me,
and...
all he seemed
to care about is you.
So if you can't tell me
who you are to him, maybe...
you can tell me
who he is to you.
I don't know
who he is, Thomas.
I just know
that he's somebody
that I can't seem to figure out
how to cut out of me.
But I want to.
And I have wanted to,
and apparently, I tried to
when I told you
what was going on.
But the truth is,
I don't know
if I'll ever be able to.
Thomas Kessler shook my hand
and said yes to a deal.
He had no reason
in the world to back out
until Harvey Specter
gave him one.
When you confronted him
with this allegation,
what did he do?
He paid off my board
and got me fired.
It wasn't a payoff.
It was a settlement
that we offered you first.
Along with a fabricated
explanation
about Kessler finding out
due to a clerical error.
The contents of that offer
are not admissible here.
In other words, you're
preparing to change your story?
As far as I'm concerned,
it's time to get
to the main course.
I call Harvey Specter.
Where is she?
She said she didn't care
if she was summoned or not.
She couldn't watch.
What are you gonna do?
I don't know.
Shortly after Simon Lowe
told you
he was using Thomas Kessler
as a pawn,
Kessler pulled out
of their deal.
- Why was that?
- If you're asking
if I told him about
my client's plans, I didn't.
- Then how did he find out?
- I don't know.
Maybe Restoration
clued him in.
Maybe he overheard someone
at dinner.
Or maybe it was
the clerical error nonsense
you tried to pull before.
- What's nonsense is,
I did not share my client's
privileged information
with another client, yet...
he brought
this complaint anyway,
and he did it because
he knew Pierpont Malls
was about to drop their suit
against my firm
because it had no merit.
They dropped it
because you paid them to.
Mr. Specter,
Mr. Hardman has a point.
I find it hard to believe
that Thomas Kessler
wasn't informed by your office,
so I ask you...
do you stand by your answer?
I stand by the fact that
he has to prove what I did.
I don't have to prove
what I didn't.
Then I say it's time
we ask someone else.
Mr. Williams,
did you or did you not
inform Thomas Kessler
that his firm was being used
as a stalking horse?
No, I did not.
Then is it true
Mr. Kessler knew
he was being used?
I can't speak to what
my client did or didn't know.
Then let's talk
about what you knew.
You got his original landlord
to make him a better offer,
did you not?
Yes, I did. And there's
nothing wrong with using
Pierpont's offer to get
a better deal for my client.
It's what
they were doing to us.
Yes, but the difference is,
when he got the offer,
he turned it down.
Why would he do that?
- Because...
what?
Why would a man
turn down a better offer
and then take out an ad
in the "Journal"
pronouncing the value
of integrity
over profits?
It's because he knew
what Simon Lowe was doing,
and you knew he knew.
And I remind you,
I will call Thomas Kessler,
and he will tell me the truth,
because he is a man
of integrity.
All right.
I knew.
And I told my client,
which was my obligation.
Finally. You knew...because
Harvey Specter told you.
No. I knew because
Robert Zane told me.
What?
I can't cover for you anymore.
You're not covering anything.
I had no reason
to break privilege.
Yes, you did.
You saw a way to get back at
Harvey Specter and Louis Litt
for taking you down
as managing partner.
You knew if you
broke privilege,
he would take a hit and you
would take the firm back.
Mr. Chairman,
that is a fabrication.
This is obviously a hit job
on an innocent man.
If he's so innocent,
then why do I have an email
from Robert Zane
informing me of
Simon Lowe's duplicity?
- You're in on this?
- Mr. Zane.
Is this true?
It is.
I can't hide it anymore.
Oh, no.
They orchestrated
this whole thing.
Ask Kessler.
Mr. Kessler, who was it,
Robert Zane
or Harvey Specter?
All I know is that
Alex Williams
informed me
of Pierpont's plan.
I can't speak
to who told him.
No. Travis Tanner admitted
Harvey called him
the night before.
Then why isn't he here?
Obviously
because he got to him!
Robert, as this is
a disbarrable offense,
I ask you again, under oath,
is this email real?
Did you do this?
I did.
Then do you have anything
to say in your defense?
Only that I did
what I felt
was right at the time.
I didn't regret it then.
But I do now.
Robert,
why are you doing this?
I'm making up
for what I did wrong.
Well, I'm sorry to say,
but that's not enough.
You hereby forfeit your
license to practice law.
This matter's now closed.
How could you do it?
- Samantha.
- You've been working
your whole life for this.
How could you just
throw it away?
I didn't throw it away.
That's what I need you
to understand.
Well, I don't understand it.
How could you take the fall
for something you didn't do?
How could you do that to me?
Because I did something else,
and I can't live with it
anymore.
What are you
talking about?
That man that attacked you...
the one that we put away--
That's why you did this?
Robert, he got
what he deserved.
He was killed, Samantha,
murdered in his own cell.
And it's my fault.
Now, he may have been
a piece of shit,
but he was someone's son,
and he wouldn't have been
in there if it weren't for me.
Why didn't you tell me?
Because it wasn't
your burden to bear.
But I am telling you now
because I need you
to understand.
This is redemption for me.
What am I gonna do
without you?
You've got your name
on the wall.
You don't need me
anymore.
The truth is...
you haven't needed me
for a long time.
I don't want
to be alone.
You're not gonna be
alone here.
You've got...
Louis and Donna and Alex.
It's not the same thing.
Ha-ha. You want
to talk the same?
I've seen you
and Harvey together.
You're peas in a pod.
Go to him.
Seek him out.
And who knows?
Over time,
you might even...
Might even what?
Nothing.
Now come over here
and give an old man a hug.
You looking for him too?
I went to call Donna
after the hearing.
She didn't answer,
but when I came back,
all you guys were gone.
There wasn't really
a reason to stay.
Alex, if you'd have told me
you were gonna do that--
That's why Robert
wouldn't let me tell you.
I know I need
to thank him...
- But you need to know why.
- Yeah.
- I do.
- Because, Harvey,
sometimes people
are carrying around a burden
they need to put down that
has nothing to do with you.
What burden?
None of your
goddamn business.
Stop moping around
my office.
I'm retired.
I'm not dead.
And, Harvey...
I knew what I was doing.
I'm good with it.
Well, then if it's
all right with you,
what do you say,
to celebrate your retirement,
I finally take you out
for that burger?
You got it.
But not tonight.
Something like this happens,
makes you know
what's really important.
And for me, it's Laura.
Hey.
You sure you don't want to
tell me what that burden was?
Isn't it enough
I saved your sorry ass?
And by the way,
most people get a gold watch.
I get a goddamn burger.
Why you gotta push it?
Now we gotta get him a watch.
Hey.
u want to get a burger?
Sorry, Harvey.
Robert's right.
I need to get home
to the woman I love.
Shouldn't you be out
celebrating?
You'd think so,
but losing Robert
kind of takes the charm
off the victory.
Listen, Harvey,
I appreciate this,
but...
I don't need you
checking up on me.
Where else
do I have to be?
You know,
I lost my mentor too.
Jessica Pearson.
Robert used to talk
about her all the time.
What was she like?
Let's just say she was to me
what he is to you.
It was hard losing her,
but...
it gets easier.
He believed in me.
He was the only one
who ever did that.
The only one
who saw who I was.
All my baggage,
all my flaws.
And he accepted you
anyway.
He didn't just accept me.
He loved me.
Not easy to find someone
like that in this world.
No, it's not.
I mean, what am I
supposed to do when I have
a big victory
or a terrible loss
and the only person I want
to run and tell isn't there?
What am I supposed to do?
Samantha, I'm so sorry,
but I have to go.
Where?
I just have to.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
www.tvsubtitles.net