Previously on "Suits"...
I had a nightmare last night
that we made Louis
Managing Partner.
I couldn't get back
to sleep till dawn.
That wasn't a nightmare
and you know it.
I cannot let my clients down.
It's just not in me.
Louis, I just found us
a new managing partner.
I think I can handle
finding Thomas Kessler
a new general counsel.
Now, the better question is,
can you handle this job
that you agreed to take?
I was just thinking about
where we were a week ago
when I thought you were cold
and heartless
and I went from that
to being your best friend.
What's going on with you
and Brian?
Donna, he's married.
I would never do--
I know, but I also know
that the heart doesn't always
listen to what the brain says
it would never do.
Finding you
the right general counsel
isn't just about
knowing your business.
No, it's about chemistry.
- Yes, it is.
- How do you know my type?
Life is going to put
that special someone right
in front of you
and when it happens,
I know you'll be ready.
Truth is,
I am running this place
and we all need to get on
board with that
and it starts
with you reading me in.
Have dinner with me.
Thomas, I'm flattered
but you're a client and--
I'm gonna give you
a bit of time
and if you still feel
the same way
then I promise
I will never ask again.
Fair?
Fair.
Well?
Well what?
Are you gonna say yes
to your mystery man?
What are you talking about?
You think we didn't
all catch you
looking at your phone
all night?
Those were work texts.
Work tests don't use emojize.
- It's emojis.
- Don't change the subject.
The point is you got a man
who wants to go out with you.
Gretchen,
it's not just any man.
It's Thomas Kessler.
Well, if you think
Louis would object
because he's a client--
- No, it's not just that--
Well, what is it?
Because you clearly like him
so what's stopping you
from going out on a simple date
and maybe getting
your freak on.
Nothing, Gretchen.
Absolutely freaking nothing.
Harvey, can I talk
to you a second?
Sure, Louis,
what's on your mind?
Well...
I wanted to say,
I shouldn't have yelled
at you and Robert about Malik.
I should have heard you
when you came to me
and let you know
how I was feeling.
It's okay, Louis,
I should have made
you listen to me
like Robert said
in the first place.
Well, I've been thinking.
I'm trying to be
the best leader I can
and a good leader inspires
people to do what they do best,
and what you do best,
Harvey, is close.
Can't argue with you there.
So what do you say you go out
and land a big whale for us?
I get it.
You're a new captain, you want
to make a new statement.
I want us to make
a new statement.
Well, in that case,
I did hear that Steven Palmer
is looking for
new representation.
Well, you get that harpoon
sharpened
because I'll be expecting
a nice piece of scrimshaw
by the end of the week,
matey.
- The hell is scrimshaw?
- Carved whale bone.
What the hell's
matter with you?
Where'd you get your education?
Not in the 1800s,
I can tell you that.
Well, for your information,
scrimshaw dates back
to the mid-1700s--
And if you finish
that sentence,
there's no way I'm going
after Palmer.
Consider the sentence
unfinished.
- Louis.
- Yeah.
It takes a big man to come
in here and say all that.
I appreciate that
and I'll get you your whale.
Chips ahoy, Harvey.
One decaf chai tea,
three sugars.
Brian, you're my associate,
not my assistant.
You don't have to bring me
my preferred beverage
when I ask to see you
in my office.
Oh, I can give it to Louis,
if you don't want it.
Gimme that,
and it just so happens
I have something for you too.
Katrina, I don't really
wear women's--
Chelsea Conner's Adored.
As in, Chelsea Conner
the makeup and fragrance giant.
Don't tell me, they're
looking for representation.
They reached out to me
this morning.
Apparently they heard about
our Hi-Rise Fashion victory
and now Chelsea wants us to go
after a rival company
who's copying
their flagship fragrance.
Brian, I think I might have
found my partner specialty.
Consumer goods.
It's not as sexy
or exciting as tax law,
but let's face it,
what is?
You don't get out much,
do you?
You know what I mean.
I do.
What do you need me to do?
Find out everything there is
to know about our product
and theirs and figure out a way
to shut them down.
Consider it done.
And hey, for the record,
this is your victory
as much as mine.
Thanks, Katrina.
It's got pretty good speed,
for something
that runs on plants.
Uh, that particular vehicle
runs on 91 unleaded.
But you're gonna make one
like it that doesn't
because you're more interested
in changing the world
than you are in making money.
For a guy I've never met,
you know a lot about
my business.
I make it my business to know
a lot about my clients,
Harvey Specter.
And I take it you heard
I'm on the market.
What I've heard is you're
looking for a guy
to kill it for you.
And you think
you're that guy.
I know I am.
People said you were cocky.
People said I was confident
and I am,
but only because
I can back it up.
But I'm afraid you, uh,
wasted your trip,
because I'm not
signing with you.
- Why not?
- You have a reputation.
My reputation is being the
best closer in the city,
which is exactly why
you should sign with me.
It's also that you never do
what you're told,
and I may consider myself
a maverick,
but I don't want
my lawyer to be one.
- Steven--
- Harvey, I just said no
and the reason is
that you don't listen.
So if you even want a shot at
my business,
your best chance at changing
my mind
would be to turn around
and let me be.
What do you say to that?
Hell of a car, Steven.
Hell of a car.
♪ Suits 8x12 ♪
Whale Hunt
Original Air Date on January 30, 2019
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ I'll even eat a bean pie,
I don't mind ♪
♪ Me and Missy is so busy,
busy making money ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ All step back,
I'm 'bout to dance ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
♪ The greenback boogie ♪
- Hello.
- Yes.
The answer is yes.
Uh, yes to what?
Yes to the question
that you asked me.
I'm sorry, you're going
to have to forgive me,
but, um,
which question was that
because I'm a very,
uh, curious person.
I ask a lot of questions.
Okay, I get it.
You want to hear me
say the words.
Yes, I will go out with you.
I might have.
Well, I just did.
Good, in that case,
the answer to your question
is also yes.
I didn't ask you a question.
But you were going to ask if
I made reservations,
and yes,
I already made some.
How could you know that?
Well, one, I'm an optimist
and, two, I know you've spent
your entire career
making plans for other people
and I thought you might
appreciate
someone making plans for you.
Yeah, I would.
Here's what I want you
to do.
Be ready for me to pick
you up tomorrow night at 7:00,
wear something stunning and,
um, hope to God I show up.
Done.
And Thomas, why did you want
to hear me say it?
Because I may be an optimist
but it's still nice to hear.
I'll see you tomorrow night
then.
And then he tries
to tell me he was right.
The man shows up 30 minutes
late to our date
and I'm hearing some bullshit
about Johnson v. Florida.
He didn't.
Hey, that's what she gets
for dating a law student.
Uh, no, I was also
a law student
and somehow I still managed to
communicate like a human being.
Well, I believe
my skills have gotten
a lot better since then.
- Oh, really?
How are his "I'm-sorry's"
and "you-were-right-honey's"?
- How do you think they are?
- You know,
I'm starting to think
this lunch was a bad idea.
To be honest,
I was surprised you suggested
it in the first place.
Well, the truth is Alex
didn't suggest it, I did.
Well, now I'm curious.
Rosalie figured
we'd just been through a war
and what better way to start
fresh than by breaking bread
and I figured,
you've already met Joy
and this couldn't go
any worse.
Though, clearly,
I was wrong.
Well,
there is another reason
I wanted to sit down
and have lunch.
After I had my babies,
I left my law firm
and I wanted to raise them,
but they are older now and it's
time to get back in the game.
Wait a second,
is this about your case?
It is.
I've got dozens
of graduates that went to
a worthless university,
they got a worthless degree
and now they're in debt.
And you've been thinking
you could use
a little help with it.
- Yes, Yes I could.
Rosalie,
we didn't talk about--
Quiet, Alex,
your wife and I are talking.
What kind of help do you need?
Robert Zane, just the man
I was looking to see.
Whatever it is, Louis,
I have a tee time in an hour.
Well, that's okay,
this won't take long.
What are those?
My walking papers?
Rigoletto tickets,
best in the house.
I know Laura's a fan.
I wish these were
my walking papers.
Oh, sorry,
I didn't mean to--
I'm just kidding, Louis,
this is a wonderful gesture.
Do you mind if I ask
what it's for?
I know that it couldn't
have been easy for you
stepping down for me,
so I just wanted to show you
how much I appreciate it.
Thank you, Louis,
means a lot.
Louis, Gretchen texted
that you wanted to see me.
Yeah, I wanted to see
how it went with Steven Palmer.
How do you think it went?
I got him on the one yard line.
Harvey, English, please.
You know I don't know baseball.
In that case,
the fat lady's singing.
That's music to my ears.
Should I lob a call
to get her to wrap it up?
- Not necessary, Louis.
- I got it.
You're all over it,
I won't push.
Robert, enjoy the tix.
Gentlemen.
Fat lady singing my ass.
Excuse me?
The only one yard line
you're on is your own.
How do you know that?
Because it's a lot easier
to tell someone's lying
when they're lying
to someone else.
Well, for your information,
I'm not really lying
because it doesn't matter
what yard line,
I'm landing this guy.
Boy, I am glad I'm not
managing you anymore
because that is some prime cut
Harvey Specter bullshit.
- Yeah.
- Speaking of fat ladies,
you want these opera tickets?
'Cause there's no way
I'm letting Laura drag me
to another four hour
snooze fest.
- I don't really.
- That's a good man.
I have to say,
I really think you married up.
I've been saying
that for years,
but right now,
I need to say something else.
I don't want you taking
that case with Rosalie.
Yeah, I think you made
that pretty clear at lunch.
The question is, why not?
You want me to list
all the hundred reasons?
Come on, Alex,
Rosalie said it herself.
We just went to war,
and I know you know what
happened
between me and Katrina.
We need something
to bring us together.
Then let's have
a bake sale,
because there's a reason
she and I don't mix work
and our relationship.
Alex, I already told her
I would help
and I am not going to break
my word to your wife.
Then I want to be clear right
now.
I don't care what happens,
you leave me out of it
because you're two strong
women who have strong opinions
about anything you've
ever thought
and I don't want to be caught
in the middle of it.
Well,
I can't speak for Rosalie,
but as far as I am concerned,
you will never hear one word
about this case from me.
Linda Janowitz,
I'm Katrina Bennett,
this is Brian Altman.
We're here on behalf
of Chelsea Conner.
In that case, this
should be a short meeting.
If you prefer a long court
fight, that can be arranged.
Actually, it's been arranged.
You're trying
to shut me down?
This is a joke.
Oh, I don't think
you'll be laughing
when a court orders you
to close your doors
and burn your product.
And why would they do that?
Because,
as you're well aware,
there's a 97% overlap
between the packaging
of your product and Adored.
It's not because we're
copying your product
and we can prove it.
- Bullshit.
- Is it?
We market-tested every aspect
of our packaging
and based on all our focus
groups,
the color that women found
most appealing was red.
They also responded to cursive
lettering and gold foil trim,
so that's what we gave them.
What you gave them is
a carbon copy
of my client's flagship
product.
And as for focus groups,
the best one I know is a jury.
So, pull your product
from the shelves,
repackage with a new name, and
that lawsuit never gets filed.
Except for one thing.
There's no way you prove our
product is a knock-off of yours
when, among other things, they
smell completely different,
which anyone who takes
one whiff of them can tell.
- Hello.
- Steven.
Louis Litt
of Zane Specter Litt.
Uh, is now a good time?
You must have gotten
your wires crossed, Louis.
Your firm already paid me
a visit today.
I know that, I know Harvey
has you well in hand.
I just want to tell you how
much we value your business.
Value my business?
You don't have my business.
Right, well, I--I know
it's not official yet. I just--
Okay, let me tell you
what I told Harvey,
I am not interested
in your firm representing me.
I see.
Do you mind if I ask why not?
I'll tell you
what I told him,
he has a reputation
for not doing what he's told.
Well, I certainly can't argue
with that,
but I do not have
that reputation
and I have just
become Managing Partner.
If you just give me a chance
to sit down with you--
You want a chance to sit down
with me?
I'm having a charity poker
event tonight.
Well, in that case, I'll--
Before you answer,
it'll cost you $100,000.
So if you're willing to part
with that amount of money,
I'll see you there
but I have to tell you,
if you can't tell when
Harvey Specter's playing you,
I'm not sure
it'll be worth your time.
Anything?
I've been thinking about it
all afternoon.
Without proof they're lying,
we have no way
to make our case.
Shit.
Katrina,
we can still back out.
No. We back out now,
Chelsea's brand is
going to mean nothing,
not to mention the fact my
specialty goes out the window.
So what are we going to do?
We have no choice, we have
to try to get Linda Janowitz
to break in a deposition.
Which isn't going to be easy,
because we have no evidence.
Wait a second, maybe we do.
What do you mean?
They lied about
the packaging.
What's to say they aren't lying
about the perfumes themselves.
Oh, my God, you're right.
They might smell
exactly alike.
I can't tell if they smell
the same or different.
That's because you're
smelling them wrong.
Here.
Try it now.
Keep your eyes closed,
it focuses your senses.
Brian?
- Yeah?
- What do you think?
Uh, they are different.
Well, perfume is
a personal thing.
It has to do with how it
interacts with a person's skin
and pheromones and--
it's a personal thing.
Yeah, personal.
Looks like our work
is cut out for us.
We're gonna have to drop
everything and focus on this.
I can't.
- What do you mean?
- I know I'm your associate,
but I've been on the
Hardwick team for six months
and tonight is
the final doc review.
Well, there are
other people on that team.
I--I don't have anyone else.
What does that mean?
It means I'm going
to get you out of it.
I've got to say,
this is an impressive operation
you got your name on.
Well, there's a reason
Alex and I went to war,
but I can't believe this is
the first time
you're seeing the offices.
It's not.
It's just the first time I'm
looking at it through new eyes.
Ah, and what kind
of eyes are those?
The kind that are looking
to intimidate.
I'm listening.
I've got a bunch of victims
who were promised
the moon and the stars,
a job placement
rate close to zero
and an administration
that claims those promises
were never made.
So in other words,
they're lying.
Yes, but I need
an office like this
and a partner like you to get
him to admit what he knows.
And then?
Because even if he breaks
at deposition,
we can only commit
so much manpower.
I'm not looking
to go to trial.
I'm looking to close
in the room.
And how exactly
are you gonna do that?
I was thinking something
like this.
Well, I just like you
more and more.
Let's get something
on the books
because these clowns are not
going to know what hit 'em.
Katrina, if you're here to
suggest
that we go out for
drinks again,
I would love to but
it just so happens that I--
That's not why I'm here,
Donna.
I need you to clear Brian's
schedule tonight
and before you say anything--
Okay, I'll take care of it.
He's all yours.
That's it?
You're not going to tell me
that he's been working on
the Hardwick case
for six months
and you can't just
pull him off now?
No, why would I
tell you that?
And why do you look like you
want me to tell you that?
Katrina, what's going on?
Brian and I had a moment.
A moment-moment?
Yes, Donna,
a moment-moment.
Okay, I--I don't want this
to come off wrong,
but did you share a moment
or did just you have a moment?
We had a moment, Donna,
and nothing happened
but it was 100% a moment.
But I need his help
on this case, Donna,
he's my associate,
I can't just hide from him
the rest of my life.
Are you sure you know
what you're doing?
No, I'm not.
Then I just have
one piece of advice.
If you don't want
to eat a cookie,
stay out of the kitchen.
- Louis.
- Hey, how's it going?
Nice weather we're having.
You mind telling me why
you lied about Steven Palmer?
- Listen to me--
- No, I talked to him, Harvey.
So before you lie to me again--
I didn't lie to you.
I told you I had him and I do.
Then why did he tell me he
wants nothing to do with you?
Because that's what all
the girls say, Louis.
And that's exactly what
he's talking about,
you don't listen.
- I don't what?
- You heard me.
You didn't listen.
- I was sure listening
when you said you weren't
going to call him.
I said I wasn't going to
push and I didn't.
What I did was determine
that I can't trust you
and now I'm taking over.
The hell you are!
I heard him loud and clear.
He wanted me to show him
that I respect him
and that's exactly what
I'm going to do tonight.
Oh, that's right.
I know, at his poker game.
Well, there's a change
of plans, Harvey,
because Zane Specter Litt is
still going to that game,
but Litt's going to be
the one at the table.
You go to that game,
all you're going to do
is show Palmer
that you don't know shit
about poker.
And you go there,
all you're going to do is prove
is all care about is yourself.
So why don't you
prove us both wrong
and do what you're told
for a change
and back the hell off
my client.
I'm not backing off anything.
There's no negotiation,
Harvey,
you stay away from
that game tonight
because your services
are no longer needed.
- Louis.
- Steven.
I have to say,
I didn't actually think
you'd actually put your money
where your mouth is.
Well, I hope tonight shows
that when I make a promise
to a client, I keep it.
Uh, potential client
but I'll tell you what,
if you can take
my money tonight,
you'll be that much
closer to signing me.
Why don't we just have
a seat?
Don't mind if I do.
Harvey,
what are you doing here?
Well, I was in the
neighborhood,
I had an extra hundred thou
burning a hole in my pocket
and I thought to myself,
why not show you gentlemen
how to play some cards.
You think you can take
my money?
I don't know,
but I'm sure Louis can't.
You don't mind, do you,
Louis?
Of course not.
I don't mind at all.
Katrina, there you are.
I've been looking
all over for--
Before you say anything,
I got you off Hardwick,
but instead of working
in the library tonight,
I think we should work in
the bullpen. It's much--
Katrina,
I can't work tonight at all.
What? I just told you
I got you out.
It's not that,
Julie's out of town
and we just lost
our babysitter.
Are you kidding me?
We need to do this tonight.
I know, I'm sorry.
She just got sick and I don't--
I get it.
It's not your fault.
I just need your help.
Hey, look,
I know it's not ideal
but we could work
at my place tonight.
Your place?
I don't know what else to do.
Okay, but we need to focus.
Absolutely. 100%.
All business.
Once he goes down,
he sleeps through the night.
We can work straight through.
Then what time
should I be there?
8:00. Do you want me
to order food?
No, I think it's best
if we've both eaten
before I get there.
I couldn't agree more.
Raise 10,000.
You're bluffing.
Oh, that's what he does,
Steven.
Not me. Call.
I don't care whether either
of you are bluffing or not,
because...
I have a flush.
Oh, shit.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
not so fast, Steven.
I just happen to have
a few queens
reigning over a couple tens.
That's bullshit.
You beat me on the river.
Well, be that as it may,
you had a 4% chance
of having a flush.
The pot odds were in my favor.
River or not,
I made the right call.
Look, I need a drink.
Louis, can I talk to you
for a second?
About what?
The fact that I'm beating your
ass in a game
you didn't even think
I knew how to play?
You don't know how
to play it, Louis.
Poker's about playing the man
and guys like Palmer
don't like to lose.
Oh, please. You don't give
a shit about Palmer.
You're just mad I beat you.
Beat me?
I just had four of a kind.
But I laid it down, like I've
been laying down all night,
because I'm trying
to let him win.
Bullshit,
you don't let anybody win.
I do when I need them
to know I can bend a knee.
Well, then why the hell
didn't you bend a knee to me
by not coming here
like I asked?
You didn't ask, you ordered.
What you asked was for me
to close this guy
because I'm better
at it than you.
Let me get this straight.
You were going to throw a game
he didn't know you threw
just to prove you
can bend a knee?
He'd know it in his heart
and he'd appreciate it.
I say it out loud,
it humiliates him
like you're doing.
No, Harvey, the person I'm
humiliating is you
because I am closing
the client, taking your money,
and you can't stand me
doing either one.
If that's what you think,
then let's get it on.
Because as of this minute,
I don't give a shit
if we land this guy or not.
Hey, how'd it go today?
I thought you said you didn't
want to be involved.
I said I don't want
to be involved,
I didn't say I don't care.
In that case, it went well.
She's good, Alex.
- I know she is.
- Then I have to ask,
why don't you want
to work with her?
All right, the truth,
Rosalie thinks I think
I'm a better lawyer than her.
Do you?
I wouldn't have married her
if I thought that.
Then why does she think it?
We did work together once
back in law school.
- Mock trial?
- Pro Bono.
Something we both cared about.
The case hit a roadblock and
Rosalie suggested one strategy,
I suggested a different one.
We ended up getting in
a huge fight,
actually broke us up
for a while.
But you got back together.
Because we loved each other,
but we also knew if that kind
of thing happened once...
There's a chance
it could happen again.
Which is why I'm asking
you how it went
instead of asking her.
Well, if it makes
you feel any better,
the case is in good hands
and the more I get to know you,
I'd say your marriage is
in good hands.
- Goodnight, Samantha.
- Goodnight, Alex.
Okay, Harvey,
it's just you and me now.
To tell you the truth,
Louis,
I'm impressed that
you lasted this long.
So why don't you take
your participation trophy
and go home.
The only thing I'll be going
home with tonight
is your money.
You two always fight
like this?
Think of it this way, Steven.
If I fight like this
at the table,
imagine how I fight
in a courtroom.
Oh Steven, please,
don't listen to him.
The only thing Harvey fights
hardest for is himself.
Raise 50,000.
50 isn't enough.
I'm all in.
Now, Louis, before you decide
how to play the hand
that could clean you out,
I want you to think
of our entire history
of me always winning
and you always losing
and when you finish
doing that,
you'll realize it doesn't
really matter what you do,
because whatever it is,
it's going to be
the wrong decision.
I fold.
See? That's exactly what
I was talking about.
All I had was ten-high.
Not only did you lose,
but you have to sit here on
tilt for the rest of the night
while I take the rest
of your money
because like I said, poker
isn't about playing the odds.
it's about playing the man.
All I have to say,
that was impressive.
Well, Steven, I didn't beat
him to impress you.
I beat him
because that's what I do.
I don't follow orders,
I don't bend a knee, I win.
So if that's the kind of lawyer
you want,
good luck with your business.
Now if you'll excuse me,
I've got Louis' money to take.
Shit, that woman
was telling the truth.
According to Chelsea Conner's
own focus group,
consumers like red,
cursive fonts--
In gold foiled trim,
which means we've officially
got gold foiled nothing.
Give me the knock-off group
results again.
Which one?
- What do you mean which one?
- They did, like, two dozen.
Wait a second, how many
focus groups did we do?
- Five.
- Five versus 24?
You thinking
what I'm thinking?
If you're thinking
the only time
someone does that many focus
groups
is when they're trying to rig
the results, then yes, I am.
And if we know what
we're looking for,
we know what to do.
Which means our work here
is done.
What?
It looks like it doesn't
matter where we work,
we make a great team.
That we do.
Great job tonight, Brian.
Good. Focus, effort,
got the job done.
Hey,
just in time.
Hey buddy.
Looks like someone wants
to say hello.
That's okay.
I can say hello from here.
You've never held a baby,
have you?
I have--
I've held millions of babies.
Well then, I guess you won't
mind holding one more.
Okay.
How do I do it?
Here.
You just take him
in your arms.
- Like this.
- Okay.
Yeah.
I have to go.
Mr. DiBiase, can you explain
why people pay up
to $25,000 a year
to go to your college.
Why does anyone
go to college?
To make their lives better.
And you promised their lives
will be better by using lies.
We help our students invest
in their future.
By taking on a mountain
of debt and loans,
which your college
profits from
and you profit from personally.
- That is not true.
- Isn't it?
Half your pay is tied
to loan origination, correct?
That doesn't mean that
I profit from the loans.
It means that it doesn't
matter
whether students find jobs or
not,
as long as bodies
keep coming through that door,
signing their lives away
with debt.
And you're paid to say
whatever it takes
to make that happen,
aren't you?
Don't answer that question.
Then I'll answer it for you.
You are paid to do that
and once we prove that,
we can come after
you personally.
- Is that true?
- No it isn't
and even if they do,
we'll indemnify you.
So it's not true, but it
might be true?
Who do you think she's
looking out for, Frank?
You or Logan Tech?
They're going to say you lied
to inflate your compensation--
Then they're gonna
hang you out to dry
and wipe their hands clean.
And this is your one
and only chance,
because right now,
we will waive your liability.
You know what?
We're done here.
I lied about the numbers.
And did
the Board of Directors
instruct you
to tell those lies?
They did.
We'll accept a settlement
of $50,000 per plaintiff.
$15,000 and that is
the best you're gonna get.
The best we're gonna get is
if we play that tape in court
and a jury is gonna give us
$100,000.
Well, if you do,
you won't even get 15,000
because we'll be bankrupt
and if you don't believe me,
I'll send over
our books to prove it.
Good, you're still here.
Actually, I'm leaving early
because I have plans.
The only plans you have is
to stay here and help me.
Okay, Louis,
if you want my help, I'd start
with "what's so important?"
As usual,
Harvey's out of control.
He lied to me about landing
Steven Palmer,
then defies me by showing up
to his goddamn card game
then he proceeds to humiliate
me and a potential client.
And what do you want me
to do about it?
I want you to do for me what
I know you did for Thomas.
- What?
- Matchmake, Donna.
I want you to stay here
to find me the perfect whale
so I can prove I close
just as well as Harvey can.
Louis, I'm sorry you're in
this situation
and I would be happy to help
you at any other time,
but not tonight because
like I said, I have plans.
Yeah, what,
more drinks with the girls?
It's not a girls night,
it's my night.
You think I wouldn't rather
spend my evening with Sheila?
But I need this, Donna,
and I need it tonight,
and you said
you feel responsible
for me running this firm.
Fine, you want my help?
Here it is.
Instead of trying to prove
to Harvey
that you're a better closer
than he is,
why don't you act like
a grown-up and work it out.
Or don't,
either way I'm going out
because I've earned it.
Donna, I'm giving you
a direct order.
So you can follow it or don't
but if you don't,
don't you ever tell me that
you feel responsible
for putting me
in this position again.
- That was amazing!
- You were amazing.
No, you were amazing.
All right, I was.
You know what's
even more amazing
is that we're gonna
get $50,000 per client.
You mean $15,000 per client.
No, 50.
Don't tell me you believed that
bullshit about their books.
You bet your ass
I believed it.
They're not gonna send over
cooked books.
Rosalie, crying poor is
the oldest trick in the book.
Not as old as being poor.
Well, I was poor
and if you ask me,
I'd rather have 50,000
than 15,000.
And I'd rather
get them a million,
but that's not the choice
that's on the table.
Listen to me,
I know you're excited about
getting an offer
after being out of the ring
for so long--
This isn't about
being out of the ring,
this is about getting money
for my clients.
Well, it's also supposed
to be about getting back
in the game
and building a reputation.
And this builds a reputation
for me just fine.
Yeah, as someone
any competent attorney
can eat for breakfast.
Okay, you know what,
I've heard you out,
now you're going
to hear me.
I heard you
and I'm telling you
you are making the wrong call.
Well, I disagree
and I appreciate your help
but this is my case
and we're taking the offer.
Ms. Janowitz,
why did you conduct
two dozen focus groups
before launching your product?
To test the consumers'
response to the product.
Except you weren't
just testing
their responses, were you?
You were reshaping them.
Making changes based on
results is the point of a test.
You mean deliberate changes
to make your packaging
look more and more
like our client's.
I already explained this,
women respond--
We all know
what women respond to.
And you know what?
You gave them exactly
what they were looking for.
You offered a package
they couldn't resist
and that confused them
and you can't deny that
you knew what you were doing
and how it made them feel.
Is there a question here?
I have a question.
Did you know you were
breaking the rules
by enticing
our loyal customers to stray?
We didn't break any rules.
But you flirted with them.
What someone buys
is their choice.
Except you confused
that choice and as a result
people wanted something
they didn't mean to want,
but couldn't help themselves
That's not true.
Just admit it,
you confused innocent customers
about what they wanted
because you wanted to be
what they wanted
so they would choose you.
But they can't choose you,
they just can't.
No matter how much
they want to
because they've already
chosen someone else.
All right, I don't know
what's going on
between the two of you,
but this deposition is over.
Alex, we need to talk.
No, we do not because
there's only one thing
you'd be here to talk about,
and I already told you
I want to stay out of it.
Well before you say that,
you should know Rosalie's
about to make a huge mistake.
What are you talking about?
No, forget I asked that.
Well, you did ask,
we've got them by the throat
but they're saying unless
we take 30¢ on the dollar,
they're gonna go bankrupt.
- What?
- That right there.
You know what I'm getting at,
they're not going bankrupt.
Samantha, I'm not going
to stick my nose in her case.
I'm not asking you
to stick your nose in,
I'm asking
if you think I'm right.
I think I said
I'd say out of it.
Which means you
do agree with me
and all I'm saying is
I think we should counter.
- Then counter.
- I can't, she's first chair.
Well, what do you want me
to do about that?
I want you to tell her
you think my way is better.
God damn it, I don't want
to say whose way is better!
Alex,
I know you don't want to cause
conflict with your wife,
but you know this is
the right thing to do.
Look, I know you kids
eat late these days,
but shouldn't you be going?
Maybe, but if I can't figure
something out soon,
I'm gonna have to cancel
with Thomas.
What, why?
'Cause Louis is an asshole
and so is Harvey.
That's not a reason, Donna,
that's just a Tuesday.
I know you're kidding,
Gretchen,
but I don't find it funny
that Louis and Harvey
are in a fight
and it's going
to ruin my night.
It's not ruining anything
and whatever it is,
it's their problem,
not yours.
And that's what I told Louis
but then he threw it
back in my face
that I'm responsible
for him being Managing Partner.
I don't give a goddamn
what he did.
You need to stop telling
yourself
that bullshit right now.
- Gretchen, I--
- No!
Now I have seen you
put this firm first
more times than I can count.
What you need to be doing
is heading home,
putting on that dress I know
you laid out this morning.
Okay.
But what about
Louis and Harvey?
You leave those two fools
to me.
Robert,
can I talk to you a second?
Of course, Louis,
what's on your mind?
You knew Harvey lied to me
about Steven Palmer,
didn't you?
I did.
Robert...
why didn't you say anything?
Would you have told me if the
shoe was on the other foot?
No, I wouldn't.
Now Louis, I obviously
wasn't successful
dealing with Harvey myself.
But from what I know
of the situation,
you stuck your head in
too early and got it bit off.
What would you do?
I make a gesture
of holding my other hand out.
You'd really do that?
Probably not,
but I sure wish I would.
And Louis, one more thing.
Harvey wasn't
being disrespectful to you,
he was just treating you the
way he treated Jessica and me.
I get it, he's
an equal opportunity asshole.
Serving the community
24 hours a day.
Thank you, Robert.
You're welcome, Louis.
Baby, I don't know what
that celery did,
but I want you to know,
I'm on your side.
Good, because that stalk right
there just put the moves on me.
Hey,
I've been meaning to ask.
How's it going with your case?
You mean Samantha
didn't tell you?
We got an offer
and it's amazing.
That's great.
How much?
- I don't believe it.
- Believe what?
You think I can't tell when
you're trying to back door
your way into a conversation?
Your mother's 80th birthday
come to mind?
- Rosalie--
- Uh-huh,
Samantha told you and you
agree with her, admit it.
All right, I do
because I've seen people
cook the books before.
Damn it, Alex,
this is exactly what happened
in law school.
You think you know better than
me.
Well, if you don't respect
me as a lawyer,
why don't you just tell me
to my face?
Because I do
have faith in you
and the only thing that's
the same about law school
is that you don't believe me,
but I do respect you
which is why I'm telling you
to your face
I think you should reject
that deal.
It didn't sound like
you were going
to tell me that
to my face.
That's because you have
a chip on your shoulder
that always shows up whenever
we talk about the law,
which is why I didn't want
to get involved
in the first place.
You really respect me
as a lawyer?
I wouldn't have married you
if I didn't.
So can we please put
our guns down
and just forget that
I said anything?
No, we can't.
But we can put our guns down.
What do you mean?
I mean, I want
to take you through
why I think I'm making
the right decision.
Gretchen,
what can I do for you?
You need to sit your ass down
and listen to me.
Excuse me?
Yeah, I can see you're on
your way to some fancy dinner
or card game
or whatever nonsense
you're spending
your time on these days,
but you need
to turn yourself around
and make things right
with Louis.
I don't need to do anything.
This is between me and Louis.
No, it isn't because
when the two of you
get into one of
your death matches,
it puts a burden
on the rest of us
and I, for one,
am tired of it.
Oh, you're tired of it,
are you?
Yes, I am.
Makes me sick the two
of you acting like children
and to think I
was considering retiring
when if I left right now,
the two of you would shit
all over your bunk beds.
- Are you finished?
- Are you gonna make it right?
It's a two way street,
Gretchen,
and I'm not the only asshole
in the room.
You're the only one
in the room right now.
Okay, I've said my piece.
I would have been gentle,
but sometimes someone
just needs to knock
the shit out of you
and Donna just so happens
to have plans tonight.
Well? Did you talk to her?
I did and she's still going
to recommend the deal.
God damn it,
that is not what
we talked about.
What we talked about was
me telling her what I thought,
which I did,
and then she changed my mind.
Of course she did,
'cause as you've made
very clear,
your relationship is more
important than any client.
Well, I don't
care who's first chair,
I am not letting
my clients down.
And I'm not backing Rosalie
because she's my wife,
I'm doing it because
she's one hell of a lawyer.
Don't tell me
you're believing that shit
about Logan Tech going under.
- What I believe is
you don't know whether
they're lying or not.
That's why I want
to fight to find out--
And what happens if you lose
that fight, because you're not
the only one who knows
what it's like to be poor
and when you're shaking
the cushions
for spare change,
the difference
between 15,000 and nothing
is a lot bigger than
the one between 15 and 50.
- I won't lose.
- You sure?
Because you have lost before
and one of those times was
to me.
So let it go or don't,
but I'm backing my wife.
And one more thing,
you said it yourself,
this was supposed
to bring us together.
Fine, I'll let it go.
But that does not mean I agree.
If it makes you feel any
better,
if the two of you didn't
team up on this,
those people would be getting no.
Hey.
You ran right out after
the deposition
and I wanted
to make sure you're--
I'm not.
- Katrina--
- Brian, we can't.
I know.
It's no one's fault.
What are we gonna do?
I don't know.
But you can't be
my associate anymore.
So you're sticking with that,
your all-time favorite
is Springsteen?
Are you kidding?
I mean, in the beginning
it was just me and my garage.
I would sketch designs
on the wall,
crank the Boss,
and just build.
Well, looking at your pieces,
it's obvious you're doing
what you love.
What about you?
What about twenty-something
Donna?
What was she up to?
Twenty-something Donna
was eating ramen every night
and acting in an off, off,
extra off Broadway production
of "Cat on a Hot Tin Roof."
Aw, careful Maggie,
your claws are showing.
You know
"Cat on a Hot Tin Roof"?
Know it? I was Brick.
In college?
No, 9th grade,
but it's not the point.
The point is, if I wasn't
so bad at acting,
I never would've realized
my passion for design.
Oh, so you're saying
that I was a bad actor
and that's why
I'm a great COO?
Well, you certainly
couldn't hide the fact
that you liked me
when we first met.
Oh-ho-ho, is that really
how you want to play this?
Well, it doesn't have to be.
In retrospect,
I probably shouldn't have been.
You know, is it getting hot
in here or is it...
See, I knew you liked me.
I do.
And I'll tell you something
else,
as you know, I was worried
about mixing business
with pleasure.
But?
I haven't thought
about business all night.
So it's been all pleasure.
Yeah, it has.
Me too.
I mean, do you wanna do
somewhere and get a night cap?
I'd love that.
Louis, I've been looking
all over for you.
I was looking all over
for you too
and I got thirsty,
thought I'd make myself
a caffeine-free prunie.
Do they usually
have caffeine?
You'd be surprised.
I don't know how to say it
so I'm just gonna come out
with it.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry too, Harvey.
I stepped in too early,
I shouldn't have
and I wish I could say
that I won't do it again
but... I probably will.
Oh, you definitely will.
You are right,
but another thing
I might do again
is call the client
that I'm trying to sign
and tell them
to sign with you
because you are
the best lawyer
that I have ever worked
with, Harvey,
and that's never going
to change.
You called Palmer
and said that?
I did.
That's funny because
I called him
and told him I was
the best lawyer
you've ever worked with too.
No, you didn't.
No, I didn't.
I told him he should sign
with you
because there's no lawyer
in this city
that I'd be more afraid
to go up against than you.
You think it worked?
To tell you truth,
I don't care if we sign Steven
Palmer or not.
We are the two best lawyers in
the city
and that is never going
to change.
- Thank you, Harvey.
- Thank you, Managing Partner.
Prunie?
Don't mind if I do.
Well, this is me.
I know.
Wow, they never actually come
that fast when I want them to.
What can I say,
I got a way with the cabs.
Thank you Thomas
for an amazing night.
Donna, I just got to tell ya,
sometimes you don't know
what you've been missing
until you have it.
So, look, I don't want to wait
three days to call you
or whatever the rules are.
Can we just skip that?
Can tomorrow be our three days?
What if we say it's tonight
and you come on up.
I just called a cab.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
www.tvsubtitles.net