Previously, on "Suits..."
- You can't put the needs
of our child
above your own.
- I'm not saying that.
- Then what are you saying?
Because I may not be
a mother yet,
but I know that's what
parenthood means.
- You wanna take me on,
you go for it.
'Cause I didn't get where I am
by letting people like you
push me around.
- David Fox wants a fight,
and I'm gonna give him one.
- Are you threatening my job?
- I like you, always have.
But if you don't get yourself
on the right of this thing
you're never gonna go further
than you are right now.
- I care about the kids this
charity is supposed to serve.
But you wouldn't know that
because I just don't...
trust...
- People.
- Are you saying
you took another job?
- No, I'm saying I got someone
else to take another job.
- You still didn't do
what I asked.
- I signed a client
that's gonna be worth
a huge amount
to this firm.
I'm a hell of a goddamn lawyer.
- You start paying those people
what they're worth...
- And?
- You get free legal services
from Harvey Specter himself
for the next year.
You didn't notice that one
of your star attorneys
was thinking about leaving.
And now, thanks to me,
he's gonna stay.
- You're talking about Alex.
- Sometimes, you need
to let us do what we do
the way we do it.
- Hello, stranger...
seems the only thing
I see of you lately
is your name on the wall.
- That's because I've been
out of town a few days,
and I need your help.
- Give it to me.
- I've got a legal situation,
and it's personal.
- Which means you need me
to send one of ours your way.
- I was thinking Alex Williams.
- Would you mind if I ask
why you didn't
just call him yourself?
- I was thinking about
a conversation we had
a few weeks ago.
You helped me see some things
about fostering firm harmony.
- And if you called him
directly,
you wouldn't have had a chance
to tell me that.
- Right again, Red.
- I'm guessing
firm harmony is also why
you want Alex and not Samantha.
- A little bit of that,
and a little
of the nature of the case.
- Then why don't you tell me
where you are,
what Alex needs to bring,
and I will make sure
that he is on his way.
- Harvey Specter.
- David Fox.
To what do I owe the--
what's the opposite
of pleasure?
- I'm here 'cause of this.
It's a deal.
It just needs
a little taking care of.
- Well, in that case,
just go ahead
and throw it in the trash,
'cause I don't work for you
and I'm never going to.
- Uh, I'm not asking.
I'm assigning.
This is part of our deal.
- I don't have any deal
with you.
- She didn't tell you, did she?
- Who didn't tell me what?
- Donna.
We made a deal
where you're my lawyer.
I'm holding you both to it.
And if you got a problem
with that...
Take it up with her.
- Donna.
What can I do for you?
- You can get your ass
into the limo
that's waiting for you
downstairs.
- I didn't call a limo.
- I know you didn't.
Robert Zane did.
- And where exactly
is Robert sending me?
- Upstate New York.
He has some business
he needs help with.
So whatever needs fixing,
fix it fast.
- Did you go through
my underwear drawer?
- As fun as that would have
made my morning,
no, Alex, I didn't.
I bought a bag
with exactly everything
you'll need
for as long as you're gone.
- And how could you
possibly know
that's everything I'll need?
- Because Robert needed me to.
And because I'm Donna.
Limo's not gonna wait
all day, Alex.
Morning, Harvey.
What can I do for you?
- You can tell me
David Fox isn't my client.
- I'm sorry, I can't do that,
because he is.
For a year.
Free of charge.
- How is that possible?
- It's possible
because you empowered me
to negotiate with him,
and that's what it took
to get it done.
- And when were you
gonna tell me
about this brilliant idea
of yours?
- I already did tell you
when I added him
to your updated client roster.
- You know damn well
I don't read
my updated client roster.
- Okay.
You got me.
I just wanted to see
the look on your face
when he came to you
and you realized
you didn't have a choice.
And there it is.
- You think this is funny?
- No, Harvey.
I don't.
And the real reason
I didn't tell you
is because I knew
you'd react like a child.
But I made a deal
that you gave me
the authority to make
because you knew
you couldn't come to one
yourself,
so whatever it is
you're feeling,
suck it up,
take one for the team,
and get this thing done.
♪ Suits 8x07 ♪
Sour Grapes
Original Air Date on August 29, 2018
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ I'll even eat a bean pie,
I don't mind ♪
♪ Me and Missy is so busy,
busy making money ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ All step back,
I'm 'bout to dance ♪
== sync by elderman ==
@elder_man
♪ The greenback boogie ♪
- Sheila, I know
we're trying to conceive,
but I can't have sex with you
right now.
I just ate an onion bagel.
- I'm not calling for that,
Louis.
- Well, then, why'd you call
on the sex phone?
- Because I knew you'd answer,
and...
I just couldn't wait
to tell u.
Louis...
We hit the jackpot.
- What jackpot?
-  The  jackpot.
- Publisher's Clearing House?
- No.
I mean we don't need
the sexphone anymore
because... well, Louis...
you hit the bull's-eye.
- Oh, my God!
My boys can swim?
- Yes, my king.
Yes, they can.
- Sheila, this is amazing!
We need to tell my--
- Louis... I know you're gonna
want to tell everyone,
but, before you do,
I want you to promise
that we'll keep this between
the two of us for a while.
- Wait, so you mean
not tell anyone?
- Yeah, just for a while.
- Okay, Sheila,
can you hold on a sec?
I think I'm getting a call.
Oh. Okay.
It was just a billing question.
All taken care of.
- You just jumped up and down
in your entirely glass office,
didn't you?
- Yes, but I stopped now.
- Then I'll see you tonight.
And we can celebrate properly.
- Ah, Gretchen.
Good, you're here.
Listen, I need you to file--
- Sheila's pregnant, isn't she?
- Oh, shit,
how could you know that?
- Two minutes ago,
you were on your sex phone.
Then you started dancing
up and down like "Footloose,"
pointing
to your nether regions.
What else could it be?
- Nothing else.
Gretchen.
I'm gonna have a baby.
- I can't believe
I'm saying this, Louis.
You're gonna be
a world-class father.
- That I am.
And I intend to be a part
of every moment,
which is why I need you
to look into what it takes
to get certified as a midwife.
- If you think I'm gonna
be midwife to your baby,
you got a whole
nother thing coming.
- No, not for you, for me.
- And I'm out.
- What?
You think I couldn't do it?
- I know you couldn't.
- Well, damn it, Gretchen.
- Do you want to be
a wet nurse too?
- You know what?
I would if I could.
And you just said
that I would be a great father.
So are you gonna help me
with this or not?
- All right, Louis.
I'll look into it.
But it's like I said before.
You're gonna be a great father.
- Okay, David.
What exactly is it
that you want?
Because you certainly don't
need me to hold your hand
while you buy a building.
- I do if that building's owner
is my biggest rival.
- And because that owner knows
what an asshole you are,
you need to make sure
he doesn't know
you're the one
doing the buying.
- See, this is why
I'm paying you the big bucks.
Oh, wait,
I'm not paying you anything.
- Just so we're clear,
you get one of those.
Because I may
have to represent you,
but I don't have to tolerate
your mouth.
- And just so we're clear,
this guy's a douche,
not an idiot.
He's gonna be looking
for me to try to buy
that building,
so I need you to be smart.
- And that's the second time
you've brought this up.
Which makes me wonder
if there's something
going on here,
because hiding a buyer
isn't illegal,
but it sure as hell can be.
- The only thing going on here
is that John Billows has
a piece of candy
and I want to take it from him.
One other thing.
This is my business.
So you take this on,
you get it done,
or you don't take it on at all.
- Robert.
Good to see you.
- Thanks for coming, Alex.
How was the drive?
- Scenic. Let me guess.
The owner's our client.
- The owner's me.
- I gotta tell you, Robert,
making wine's
not exactly the hobby
I pictured for you.
- It's not a hobby,
it's an investment.
And right now,
it's netting less than zero.
- What can I do to help?
- Why don't we first start
with a little tour?
- Samantha, can I talk to you
for a second?
- Sure, what's on your mind?
- You and Alex
and Robert and Harvey...
Harvey's got a case
that he doesn't want,
but there's nothing that says
that he can't
get a little outside help
on it.
- Don't tell me you're trying
to give me a leg up
with Harvey,
because you wouldn't do that
and I don't need it.
- You're right.
I wouldn't.
But sooner or later,
it's gonna be
either you or Alex
who go up on that wall next,
and no matter who
goes up there first,
the other team isn't gonna
be happy about it.
But the more we're bonded
as a family
before that happens,
the more likely
we'll stay a family
after it does.
- Then I just have
one question.
When you said
Harvey doesn't want
to take the case
but he has to...
- I did.
- Why?
- Because I struck a deal
with David Fox,
and Harvey can't stand him.
- Can you?
- Not particularly.
- Then why don't you
get me up to speed
before I go pay a visit
to this David Fox.
- Well?
- I'm more of a craft brew--
- Oh, save the bullshit.
I know. It tastes like ass.
That's my problem.
- So you want me
to fire your winemaker?
- No, I want you
to go after the son of a bitch
who didn't deliver the barrels
that I paid for.
Because I had to let my wine
stay in these vats,
and it turned into that vinegar
you're now holding.
- And no one's interested
in buying vinegar.
- I lost my entire harvest!
- Shit.
What did the guy say
when you called
about the barrels?
- That they'd be here tomorrow.
And tomorrow. And tomorrow.
And meanwhile, all my neighbors
got their barrels just fine.
Which makes me think
there's more going on here
than it looks like.
- You think this is about race?
- I think, between the looks
I got at the bank
and the cold shoulder
I got at the market
and now this...
- You've seen this movie
before.
- Different cast,
different location,
but the same damn script.
- Robert,
if that's what's going on here,
I'm not sure a lawsuit is gonna
get these guys to back off.
- Look, I'm not saying
they're wearing white robes.
I'm saying
they're trying to keep me
out of the country club.
- What do you want to do?
- I want to send a message
that if they try this shit
again,
there's not gonna be
a country club.
- The great Harvey Specter
walking through my door.
Now I know I'm a big deal.
- Not as big as the deal
I'm about to offer you,
Mr. Billows.
- Oh, I like you already.
- Then you're really gonna love
my client.
Santana Developers.
They're an up-and-coming
real estate firm
from the southwest,
and, fortunately for you,
they've taken an interest
in your redevelopment project
on Liberty Avenue.
- Have they, now?
Well, that's a shame,
'cause it's not for sale.
And there's no southwest firm
that I've never heard of.
- All right. You got me.
My client's associated closely
with the government of Dubai.
A fact
they'd rather not announce,
and, in exchange
for that secrecy,
they're willing
to offer you this.
- Thank you for your time.
- John, that's 25%
over market value.
All cash.
- And I told you,
I'm not selling.
Least of all to David Fox.
All right, John, look--
All right, look,
I'll give you credit.
I mean, you do live up
to your reputation.
'Cause a fallback straw man
is something
even I never thought of.
- And if you really knew
my reputation,
you'd know a straw man
is just my first move.
You don't want to see
what I'm gonna
come at you with next.
- Well, I believe you'll try
to cut off my financing.
But my partners are in China.
And I've been in bed with them
for ten years.
They trust me implicitly.
Good day, Mr. Specter.
My regards to David Fox.
Louis, I can't believe
you got us a reservation here
so quickly.
- Sheila, you're gonna be
the mother of my son.
I'm getting you in
wherever you want to go.
- Son?
- Or daughter.
- Well, here's to watching
either one of them
take ballet lessons and tap
and learn to twirl the baton.
- Oh, my God,
I get to teach him the baton.
I can't wait.
It's why I want to have a boy.
- And I can't wait because
we're gonna be a family.
And we're gonna
do everything together.
We're gonna get ready
in the morning together.
We're gonna go
on vacations together.
- We're gonna get to visit him
at Camp Brucha
and see him come running out
in his little--
- Wait a second.
Camp Brucha?
- No, Sheila, I know I told you
that the kids there
burned all my underwear,
but I'm telling you,
it made me stronger.
- Louis, your underwear
isn't what I'm talking about.
I meant
Brucha is a Jewish camp.
- Yeah, so what?
- So it never occurred to me
that you'd want
to raise our child Jewish.
- Of course I do.
I thought
it went without saying.
- Just like I thought
it went without saying
that we wouldn't
raise them anything.
- Why would you think that?
- Okay, Louis.
How would your parents feel
if we said
we were gonna raise
our child Catholic?
Exactly.
That's how my parents
would feel
if we raised our child Jewish.
- Yeah, but it's different.
- Not to me, it isn't.
- Sheila--
- Louis, please.
This is supposed to be
a celebration.
Can't you just let it go?
- Of course, Sheila.
Consider it gone.
- Miles Newton.
- Yes?
- My name is Alex Williams.
I represent Robert Zane.
- Represent?
- That's right.
He's suing you
for breach of contract.
- This is ridiculous.
I told him
it was a clerical error.
- And that error cost him
his yield for the season.
- Look, I also told him
that I'll comp him
all the barrels that he needs
next year to make up for it.
- There may not be a next year
because you
cheated my client out of money,
and now
you're gonna pay him back,
plus his lost revenue,
and any other damages
I can hang on you.
- If I cheated him,
then why would I give
the new guy in town,
your guy, a cut-rate deal?
- What are you talking about?
- My other clients
paid 5% more.
Your client was the one
who actually got a break.
A 30% discount.
- And did the other vintners
know you were doing that?
- We're a community up here,
Mr. Williams.
We protect our own.
So they gave the new guy
a break,
and they took the hit,
so you want to slap me
with a lawsuit?
Go ahead,
and we will just see who wins.
- Look at you sweating it out
in the law library
like a first-year.
I didn't know you could read.
- I'm just looking
at the pictures.
- Then why don't you
let me help you
figure out
how to get that building.
- Excuse me?
- Donna thought you could use
some backup
dealing with David Fox.
- Donna did, or you did?
- What does that mean?
- It means
you want to impress me
so when the time comes,
I'll vote for you.
Well,
let me tell you something,
that's never gonna happen.
- I know that.
And I'm here
because I just might have
a solution to your Fox problem.
So you can either trust me
or you can figure out
how to get out of this
yourself.
But for the record,
not everything I do
comes with a price tag.
- This was Donna's idea?
- Yeah, it was.
- Well, then,
why don't you sit down,
and I'll bring you up to speed.
- I have a better idea.
Why don't I sit down
and tell you
how we're gonna get
that building.
- How did it go?
- Exactly as planned.
- In that case, why don't we
have a drink to celebrate,
and then we'll take care
of everything tomorrow.
- As long as you have
a beer or some scotch,
because I'm not drinking
any more of that vinegar shit.
Don't worry.
Neither am I.
- Robert, I gotta ask.
You're a scotch guy.
You're a lawyer.
Why come up here
to buy a vineyard?
- My sister.
She died years ago.
We used to drink wine together,
and we didn't know shit
about vintage or tannins.
We just knew what we liked.
And when I drink wine,
I think about her.
- I didn't know
you had a sister.
- Well, now you do.
I worked a case with Rachel
last year,
got me thinking about her
even more.
And I realized...
I like thinking about her
even more.
- Then here's to making sure
you're thinking of her
till you're old and gray.
- Got that right.
- Oh, thanks for making time
for me, Esther.
I really appreciate it.
- I have to tell you, Louis,
I haven't stopped smiling
since you told me the news.
Have you told Mom and Dad?
- Actually, that's the reason
I wanted to talk to you.
- Okay.
- Sheila and I were talking.
We're not
raising the baby Jewish.
I need you to help me
explain that to Mom and Dad,
and I need to know
how upset you think they'll be.
- How much would it upset you
to be ostracized by them
for the rest of your life?
- Tell you the truth,
I could think of worse things.
- Louis.
It would crush them,
and you know it.
You're Jewish.
You should
raise your children Jewish.
- Wait a second, wait a second.
You feel the same way too?
- I think
this is between you and Sheila.
It's not up to me.
But if you want the truth,
I always thought
if you ever had kids, that
they would go to Camp Brucha
like mine did,
like you and I did.
- I know. I do too.
Remember?
♪ Because... ♪
♪ We're all mishpucha ♪
♪ Here at Camp Brucha ♪
- Anyway,
that's not gonna happen,
because the way
this whole thing started,
when I brought up Brucha
to Sheila,
she nearly choked on her water.
- Wait a second,
she's driving this?
- Of course she is.
You think I want this?
I just said
the goddamn camp pledge.
- Then you need to tell her
how you're feeling.
- I tried
talking to her about it.
She made it clear
she didn't want to,
and here we are.
Louis, I want to talk to you
about Jeffrey.
- Jeffrey's an asshole.
- No, he's not, Louis.
He's the father of my children,
and the reason
our marriage fell apart
wasn't because of
what he did to me
but because of what
he didn't do with me.
- Express how he felt about
you being the breadwinner.
- Yes.
So if you want me
to help you break the news
to Mom and Dad, I will,
but I'm not gonna do it
until you tell Sheila
how you're feeling.
- All right,
what do we have here?
- I'll tell you what we have.
I got a building;
I don't want to sell it;
and these two are in here
crying to you.
- You don't have a lawyer?
- I don't need
a goddamn lawyer.
- We're not crying.
We are representing
the community.
Because that building
was built in 1896,
and all we're asking for
is a TRO
until the landmark commission
can make a decision.
- Give me a break.
They're not representing
the community.
They're representing David Fox.
- I did not say
he was my client.
- And even if he did,
that doesn't mean
this is connected to that.
- How about the fact
that Mr. Fox has been shoveling
my biggest tenant
tens of thousands of dollars
a month to stay in his lease
so I couldn't kick him out?
Is that connected?
- What?
- Your Honor.
Those payments are repayments
for an unrelated debt.
- Bullshit.
Peter Minto doesn't have
two pennies to rub together,
much less tens of thousands
to loan David Fox.
- And the details of someone's
personal financial arrangements
are not your business.
- That's enough.
You two want to push this
up the hill
with the landmark commission,
be my guest,
but I see no reason
to stop this man
from making a living
in the meantime.
Your restraining order
is denied.
- Okay, what we need to do--
- How the hell did you find out
about those payments?
I'll tell you how.
You went to Fox behind my back.
- No.
I had your back.
You had nothing.
I brought you something.
- Well, that something
just blew up in our faces,
because he's been using
those payments
to launder money,
peddle influence,
or God knows what other crime.
- And that is exactly why
I didn't tell you,
because Donna told me
you don't trust him.
- You're damn right
I don't trust him.
Because when a man like that
hides money,
it's not because he's
secretly donating to Goodwill.
- Harvey, he is our client.
- No. He's not.
- You can't just drop him.
- Yes, I can.
Because I don't give a shit
about Donna's deal.
I'm not representing a client
that lies to my face!
What's the matter,
Mr. Newton?
You don't look happy
to be here.
- I'm not.
I don't appreciate
being subpoenaed.
- Well,
if you don't appreciate that,
you're definitely not
gonna appreciate this.
- You're accusing my client
of intent to defraud?
- That's what he did, isn't it?
- I didn't do anything
except be a little bit late
with your barrels.
- What you did
was entice my client
with a discount,
then sabotage his yield
because you knew
the other vintners
would make you whole.
- My client did no such thing.
- Yes, he did.
He admitted it to my face
last night, and now,
instead of a lawsuit,
you're looking
at criminal charges.
- Criminal charges?
Are you out of your mind?
They can't do this to me,
can they?
- Look at his face.
It says we can.
It should be more than that,
you son of a bitch.
- What the hell
is your problem?
- You know what my problem is?
The oldest problem in the book
for a man like me.
And I'm putting a stop to it
right now.
- Race? Race, is that what
you think this is about?
- I know
that's what this is about.
- Oh, you pompous
piece of shit.
- Miles.
- No, no.
I am not gonna sit here
and let him accuse me of that.
You want to know why
you didn't get your barrels?
Because you don't deserve them.
- And there it is.
- No, no, no, no.
See, our families have worked
those vineyards
for generations,
and you just come
waltzing in here
with your Wall Street money,
acting like you own the place,
and you've been here
for, what, ten minutes?
We've been here
our whole lives.
You bought out that man
before you
after he had one down year.
And we're not gonna let you
get away with it.
- You tell yourself
whatever you want.
But you're right
about one thing.
I'm a big, bad motherfucker,
and I'm here to drink
your goddamn milkshake.
- Let me guess,
Samantha told you
what I'm about to do.
- Yeah, she did.
- Oh, so she keeps shit from me
but shares it with you.
- Don't make this about her.
She does what she wants,
just like you do.
- You're taking her side?
- I'm taking my side.
Because you may be done
with this case,
but she's
gonna keep working on it
because, unlike you,
she cares about my reputation.
- You think
I don't care about you?
You're in your position
because I put you there.
- No, Harvey,
I'm in my position
because I fucking earned it!
Now, if you want to talk
about things you did,
you authorized me
to negotiate this deal,
and if you don't honor it,
Fox is gonna tell the world,
and how's that gonna go
the next time
I try to come to an agreement
with anyone?
- It'll go fine
because he has no integrity.
Nobody will believe him.
- Okay.
Let me put this in words
that you'll understand.
I have integrity.
You let him go,
you're making me a liar.
- You want to talk
about a liar?
He lied to my face.
- And so have
a thousand other clients.
You were just waiting
for an opportunity
to let him go.
- Because we never
should've taken him
on in the first place.
- Well, we did,
and like I said,
you drop him,
you're making me a liar.
And I don't care if the rest
of the world knows it or not.
You'll know it,
and I'll know it.
Now, you go ahead
and do what you want.
You always do anyway.
- Louis, what a surprise.
I was just reading.
- Listen.
Sheila... we need to talk.
- About what?
- I want to raise
our child Jewish.
- Louis, I thought
we talked about this.
- No, Sheila, we didn't,
because we were celebrating,
and you told me to let it go.
And I tried to let it go,
but then I talked to Esther.
And now I can't.
- Okay, so you talked to Esther
after you said
we wouldn't tell anyone yet?
- Yes, I did,
because she's my family.
- I get it,
so you and your sister
have a long conversation
about Sheila, the shiksa.
- Sheila, it's not like that.
Esther helped me realize
that I don't care
what my parents think.
I don't care what
your parents think.
It's what's important to me.
- And how about
what's important to me?
- That's why
I want to talk this out.
Because I don't want to end up
resenting you for this.
- And I don't want
to resent you either,
so why don't you tell me why
this is so important to you.
- What's so important is that
it's a part of who I am.
- And being Catholic
is a part of who I am.
- But you said
you were not religious.
- And so did you.
- That's what I am trying
to explain to you.
Being Jewish
isn't just a religion to me.
It's in my blood.
- And you don't think
it's the same for me?
- No, I don't.
- Then you don't get it.
Because when I said
my parents wouldn't like this,
what I meant was,
the people who raised me,
who are my blood,
have had a hard enough time
accepting the fact
that I don't practice anymore.
And I don't want
to separate myself from them
by telling them that my child
is going to be different
than all of us.
- Sheila, I can't just
rip this out of me.
- Louis, I'm not asking you
to rip it out of you.
I just don't want to raise
our child one way or another.
- You know what, to me,
it's the same damn thing.
- Then I don't know
what to tell you.
- Neither do I.
Neither do I.
- Samantha, can I talk to you
for a minute?
- Looks like you need
more than that.
- I tried to talk Harvey
out of dropping Fox,
but I'm not sure
I convinced him.
- And?
- I told him you said
you'd keep working on the case
anyway.
- That's funny,
because I didn't say that.
- No. You didn't.
But the reason
I told him you did is--
- Because you gave Fox
your word.
And even if Harvey doesn't
live up to it, I can.
- Exactly.
- It looks like I've got
some more work to do.
Because I'm not gonna
make a liar out of you.
- Thank you, Samantha.
- No need to thank me, Donna.
I'm sure
you'd do the same for me.
- Louis, what's going on?
It's not usual for you to come
in so many times in one week.
What did Harvey get into now?
- This isn't about Harvey.
It's about Sheila.
I need you to convince her
to raise our children Jewish.
- Louis,
I'm not going to do that.
- Why not?
I know she came
to see you that time.
Did you think I wouldn't
find out about that one?
- No,
I assumed you would find out
when I explicitly told her
to tell you about it.
- Well, if you can order her
to do that,
why can't you order her
to raise our children Jewish?
What kind of therapist are you?
- Louis.
I know
I've told you this before,
and I know
you refuse to believe me,
but my parents were Jews
in Nazi Germany,
and there was a point for them
where they discussed
renouncing their Judaism
for a chance
to save their lives.
They didn't.
So I understand
as much as anyone
the value of maintaining
a Jewish identity.
- But?
- But, to me,
the heart of Judaism is family.
- What're you saying?
- I'm saying,
if you can't be on
the same page about how
to raise your children,
maybe you should discuss
not having them.
- It's too late for that.
- Ah.
Then, Louis,
I would say it's more important
that you make a decision
together
than what that decision is.
- Thanks, Stan.
- You're welcome, Louis.
And there's just one more
small matter before we move on.
- What's that?
- Mazel tov, my friend.
Mazel tov.
- Where have you been?
- I gave you a chance
to calm down.
Because, Robert,
we need to talk.
- We do.
About how
we're gonna make them pay.
- That's the thing.
I think we should try
to work this out.
- Are you goddamn kidding me?
- Robert, he admitted
to a crime
to convince us
he was telling us the truth.
- Because he probably believes
his own bullshit.
Well, I don't care
what he believes.
There's no way, if I'm white,
we're in this situation
right now.
- I'm not gonna tell you
you're wrong.
But you are wrong about
how to handle this situation.
- What is that
supposed to mean?
- It means
we take him at his word.
- Okay.
Let's say that you're right
and this is more about my money
than the color of my skin.
I'm not gonna let
that son of a bitch
push me out
no matter what the reason.
I've been putting up
with this shit
for more years
than you've been on this earth,
and I've accepted
that the way to deal with it
is to bury a part of myself.
Well, I don't
have to do that anymore,
and you're gonna do what I say.
- No, sir, I'm not,
because the world's
a shitty place
and I'm not
gonna make it worse.
And I don't give a shit
if you're my boss.
I'm your goddamn lawyer.
And you're either
gonna take my advice
or you can hire someone else.
- Then call yourself a car,
and get the hell out of here.
I'll handle it myself.
I hope you're here to tell me
you got it done.
- I'm here to give you
one last chance.
'Cause I know
about the payments
to Peter Minto,
and so does Billows.
- Shit.
Well, how much does he know?
- I'm not here
about what he knows.
I'm here about what I don't,
because I asked you
if something shady is going on,
you lied to my face,
and the only reason
I haven't dropped you yet
is Donna gave you her word.
- You know what,
you wouldn't understand.
- I understand
money laundering,
and, knowing the kind
of man you are,
it's exactly what's
going on here.
- You know, you don't know shit
about the kind of man I am.
- Then tell me right now.
What the hell
is Peter Minto giving you
in exchange
for $10,000 a month?
It was nice
representing you, David.
- It's not what he's giving me.
It's what he gave me.
- What does that mean?
- I was 13 years old.
I didn't have any money.
I needed a pack of cigarettes.
So I took one
from Minto's Market.
And then I thought, you know,
while I'm at it,
I might as well take
a bunch of other shit.
- He didn't press charges.
- No, he didn't.
But he did make me work it off.
Next thing I knew,
he took me under his wing.
Look, I gave him that money
because if I didn't,
he'd go out of business,
and if I can't
get this building,
he's gonna
go out of business anyway.
- Why didn't you just tell me
this in the first place?
- For the same reason
I don't want anyone to know it.
All right, I need people
to believe that I'm ruthless.
- Well, wouldn't you rather
have people know you're loyal
than have them think
you're an asshole?
- Look, Peter Minto taught me
how to do business
as a gentleman,
but there's a reason
he can't keep his business
alive and I can.
- Well...
I can't say I agree with you...
but I'll get you your building.
- Donna. You're up late.
- I'm up late because you said
this thing would be done
by now,
and I haven't heard from you,
which makes me wonder...
how's it going?
- I'll tell you
how it's going.
Instead of getting closer
with Alex,
I had to send him packing.
- What? How did that happen?
- It happened
because I'm his client
and he wouldn't listen
to a word I said.
- Look,
I want to say something,
but I'm hesitant to say it
because it's not something
I would normally say
to a managing partner.
- Speak your mind.
- Well, I don't know
what the issue is,
but I do know
when a lawyer and a client
have a falling out,
more often than not,
it's because
the client wouldn't listen
to the lawyer,
not the other way around.
In particular,
when that lawyer
is Alex Williams.
- Is that all?
- That's it.
I hope you get whatever it is
taken care of, Robert.
- Are you still working
the Fox case?
- I believe
Donna told you I was,
and Donna's no liar, why?
- Because I'm back in.
- What changed your mind?
- Fox did.
Turns out those payments
were because Peter Minto
was Fox's mentor.
He wasn't laundering anything.
He was trying
to save that market.
- So he was basically donating
to Goodwill after all.
- I guess he was.
- Wait a minute.
Goodwill.
Public good.
- What do you got?
- There's a public good
requirement for any project.
- Yeah, and this one
has it covered
with the subsidized housing.
- Because that way,
his Chinese investors
have to cover it.
- How do you know that?
- Because I got a copy
of their agreement,
and if that good
is residential,
they take the hit.
If it's commercial,
Billows does,
and Minto's Market
is a commercial public good.
- Which means all we need to do
is tell those Chinese investors
their trusted partner's
been screwing them.
- And Billows either loses
his partners
or foots the bill himself.
which puts him between a rock
and a hard place.
- And his only way out
is to sell to David Fox.
- Look at that.
We make a pretty good team,
don't we?
- Maybe.
But the only problem is,
it makes this whole project
a money loser for Fox.
- So what? He said he's been
subsidizing Minto anyway.
- Privately.
This is in the public eye,
which means
everyone's gonna think
he's either soft or stupid,
and I'm telling you,
it's that man's
worst nightmare.
- What do you want to do?
- Can you get to the Chinese?
- I can.
- You handle them,
and I'll handle David Fox.
- Sounds like a plan.
- Are you sure
you can handle them?
- Ni gan dadu wo keyi.
- Yeah,
but can you handle them?
- What now?
- I'm calling to say I'm sorry.
I lost my shit.
- Truth is,
if I was in your position,
I'd probably feel the same way.
- Well,
you're not in my position.
You're my lawyer.
And if I'm not
gonna listen to you
and go ahead
and handle this thing myself...
- You've got a fool
for a client.
- Something like that.
Anyway, I think I may
have a way through this.
- What you got?
- You said that you wanted
to take them at their word.
If we did that, the problem is,
we're dealing with a community
that feels threatened.
So I was thinking,
insurance covers my losses
this year.
Next year,
my barrels are free,
and then I can build
a community tasting room
that we all can share.
- That's very generous of you,
Robert.
Mind if I ask you
what brought you around?
- Two things.
A conversation with a friend.
- And?
- Where I grew up,
community was everything.
We were tight and close,
mistrusting of outsiders,
and...
if someone had come in
and done what I did to them...
The community wouldn't
have taken too kindly to it,
no matter what
the color of their skin.
So I thought maybe we're not
so different after all.
- Copy that.
- So you're gonna propose
all of that to them tomorrow.
- Robert, I think
if you're gonna be
a part of this community,
we ought to propose it
to them together.
- So get your ass
back up here then.
And Alex... don't ever
call me a fool again.
- Welcome home, Louis.
- Is that...
- Yes, it is.
Your mother's kugel.
- How did you...
- Your sister called.
- Don't tell me.
She tried to convince you
to see it my way.
- No, Louis, she called
to tell me, whatever happens,
she loves me
and wants to welcome me
to the family.
- So why the kugel?
- Because my sister never
would have done that for me.
Louis, I may not be ready
to make this decision
right now,
but what we were
really struggling with
was how to blend
our identities.
So I thought,
what better way to do that
than by starting with kugel?
- Well, if we're gonna
be doing that,
I don't see
why we can't also have
a Christmas tree this year.
- You'd be open to that?
- Yes, I would.
Because I saw
Dr. Lipschitz today.
Sheila, he reminded me
that the foundation
of everything is family.
So I've been thinking...
- Stop right there.
I've been thinking too.
You asked me last time.
I'd like to ask you this time.
Louis Marlowe Litt...
Will you marry me?
- Yes, Sheila, I will.
- Morning.
I was just thinking
about our wedding.
- Louis...
- I was thinking maybe
we can make it a destination.
- I don't want to talk
about our wedding right now.
- Why not?
- I got my period.
I'm not pregnant.
- But the test said that you--
- It was a false positive.
- Hey.
Hey, hey, hey.
You know what this is?
It's just a bump in the road.
That's all this is.
Just a pause.
And sweetie,
there's a bright side.
Because it gave us a chance
to have
really tough conversations.
And that way,
when we do get pregnant,
and we will get pregnant,
we'll be ready in a way
that we weren't ready before.
Are you okay?
- I will be.
Please tell me you didn't tell
anyone other than Esther.
- I told Gretchen.
- You need to untell her that.
- Hello, Robert.
I assume you're calling me
with good news.
- How do you know that?
- Don't you know by now I have
a sense for these things?
- I just wanted to call
and say thank you, Donna.
We worked it out.
- You and Alex?
- Me, Alex, everybody up here.
And it wouldn't have happened
without you calling me
on my shit.
- You know how they say doctors
make the worst patients?
- Same goes for lawyers?
- No.
Lawyers are much worse.
- I guess they are.
Which is why I'm glad
I have someone like you.
- Wow... calling to thank me,
valuing my leadership,
and giving me
an endearing nickname--
Robert, if we're not careful,
we could become
full-blown friends.
- Oh, that's a chance
I'm willing to take.
- See you soon, Pops.
- Right back at you, Red.
- Let me get this straight,
you're telling me
you can get me the building,
but it's gonna
cost me more
to keep Peter in business
than I was paying
in the first place?
- And on top of that,
the whole world's
gonna know about it,
because Billows is gonna
make sure they know it.
- Are you trying
to stick it to me even more?
- I want you to know
the cost of this thing
before you make a decision.
- This is bullshit.
- David.
- God damn it.
You could have done better.
- And you could've told me
the full fucking story
before I only had two days
to stop it.
- So either
I look like a sucker
or I let the guy who gave me
my start go out of business.
- Helping Peter Minto
stay in business
doesn't make you a sucker.
- It does to the world.
- David,
the deal is what it is.
If I could make it any better,
I would, but I can't.
- What would you do?
- As your lawyer, I'd tell you
get your emotions in check.
It's a shitty deal
and a stupid move.
But if I were in your shoes,
I'd take it.
- Take it.
- You know, I never thought
I'd be saying this,
but... you earned my respect.
- Well, don't you look like
the cat that ate the canary.
- I do. And that canary's name
is Robert Zane.
- Let me guess.
He called you and started
unleashing compliments
like you were his family.
- How'd you know?
- He gets like that sometimes.
- Well, I was thinking
that I wanted
to treat him like family
right back,
and maybe you could
give me some advice
on getting him a gift.
- Oh, no, Donna.
You don't want to do that.
- What? Why not?
- He's a terrible
gift receiver.
- You're kidding.
- I once gave him
vintage copies
of "Inherit the Wind,"
"To Kill a Mockingbird,"
and "Twelve Angry Men"
for his birthday.
The next year,
I found them in his drawer
with the bow still tied on.
He's a lawyer.
They're books about the law.
- Did you say something?
- No.
I just took them back.
He didn't even notice.
I'm gonna regift it to him
when he retires.
What?
- Harvey's the opposite.
- Great gift receiver.
- Awful gift giver.
Heart's in the right place,
but two weeks in,
I realized
if I ever really wanted
to enjoy my birthday present,
I was gonna
have to buy it myself.
- Do you still?
- Got these for the last one.
32,
if you're wondering.
Speak of the devil.
Look who's walking in
empty-handed.
- What are you talking about?
- Nothing, Harvey.
- Well, as long as
you're both here,
you weren't just right
about Fox.
You were right about taking him
on in the first place,
and you were also right
about getting her to help me.
- If I didn't know any better,
Donna,
I'd say
he's apologizing to you.
- That's funny, I was thinking
he was apologizing to you.
- Well, I can understand
why we're both confused.
It's a pretty weak apology.
He didn't even use
the word "sorry."
- I don't even think
he knows the word "sorry."
- Are you two finished?
- We're just getting started.
- Take a chair, Harvey.
- And pour us a couple
of drinks while you're at it.
- If I'd known
this was gonna happen,
I wouldn't have said anything,
much less "I'm sorry."
- Ooh, look at that.
He does know the word.
- Yeah, just not how to use it.
- Mm-hmm.
- Louis, where have you been
all day?
- I needed to spend some time
with Sheila.
- Well, I've got good news.
I found a midwife class
for you.
Turns out, you're not the only
mid-aged white man
that wants to be
Dr. Quinn, Medicine Woman.
- That's great.
But I'm gonna need you
to cancel it.
- Louis, what's wrong?
- It was a false positive.
We're not gonna have a baby.
- I'm so sorry.
But that doesn't mean
that she--
- I know that, Gretchen.
I just need a little time
to myself.
- Of course.
You don't have to be strong
for me, Louis.
== sync by elderman ==
@elder_man
www.tvsubtitles.net