Previously on "Suits"...
As of this morning,
we're merging with Robert Zane.
When I came over,
you said my name
would be the one to go up next.
You have my word.
Your name goes up next.
I threw away my diaphragm.
- You're pulling the goalie?
- Yes, Louis, I am.
I need you to get
Robert Zane's biggest client
to sell their
manufacturing division.
This is going to determine
who runs the firm.
I need you to come through
for me on this one.
Your client is dropping
their manufacturing division,
and we can get back to the
business of running this firm
under the direction
of Robert Zane.
You think I can't take
Samantha Wheeler?
I think you said
you'd stay out of it,
and I'm not going to help you
tell your own team
that you'll cut them out
just to get the better
of Samantha Wheeler.
I did what you asked, and
now I have something to ask.
- What's that?
- You know what I want.
- Samantha.
- Robert, I want name partner,
and I want it
before the year is out.
You said
that I should come back
when I was ready to admit
that you were right.
Takes a big man
to admit that, Harvey.
- My office.
- What about it?
- I want it back.
- Your fearless leader
is happy to comply.
- Sheila, what is all this?
- A power breakfast.
And it looks delicious,
but you know I usually like to
eat light in the morning.
Just a bowl of Fiber One, or--
- Oh, I know, Louis.
I also know the day
you take control of the firm
is no usual day.
Before I take control
of what now?
Louis, you just merged,
which means it's time
for a new king
to claim the throne.
All right, Sheila, if you're
saying what I think you are,
Harvey's already
managing partner,
and Zane's going to fight
to take it from him.
Which sets the table for you
to take it from both of them.
Louis, you're a king.
And we should all
be kissing your ring.
But, Sheila,
where is all this coming from?
It's coming from the fact
that Harvey left you
to fight off the hordes,
and you did just that
by subjugating the army
of Robert Zane.
- I suppose I did.
- No supposing, Louis.
You're a god.
A Viking god.
And Viking gods
take what they want.
Now go in there,
and claim what's yours.
I will, but not until
I claim what's also mine--
Not yet.
Let's do it this afternoon,
afterward.
Then we can play
"managing partner/secretary."
In that case you'd better
be ready to take
a whole lot of dictation.
Oh, I will.
Now go.
And return to me a king.
- I know.
- Morning, Robert.
- Harvey, I just got in.
The sign looks good.
- Good, I'm glad you liked it.
You ready to do this thing?
If you mean,
am I ready to get back to being
a managing partner,
I sure as hell am.
Then give me
your John Hancock,
I'll get it to Louis,
and you will officially be
the managing partner
by the end of the day.
Harvey Specter?
That's right, this is
my partner, Robert Zane.
My partner and I
were clients of Mike Ross.
We founded Pod Space.
- You must be Max Louden.
How do you know I'm not Nick?
Because Mike said if one
of you ever came to see me,
it'd be you.
So why don't you tell me
what the problem is,
and I'll get you out of it.
Oh, I hope it's that easy.
Nick and I started
another business venture.
Raised 100 million to
get the thing off the ground.
I can only account
for 50 of it.
Well, when 50 million
is missing,
the math adds up
to embezzlement.
I know that, but I'm telling
you, Nick wouldn't do that.
Not to me,
and not to the business.
Then if he didn't take it,
he got taken.
Look, I don't know
what happened.
But what I do know is that if
we can't account for the money,
and anyone finds out,
we're not just out of business;
we're in prison.
- Trust me, Max.
I'm not going
to let that happen.
Thank you.
And, Max,
don't tell Nick
you came to me with this.
Well, I wasn't going to, but
do you mind if I ask why not?
I don't want him
to know I'm coming.
I know you already know this,
but he's either guilty
and trying
to pin it on his partner,
or it's the other way around.
No way that kid's guilty.
I don't know that,
and neither do you.
I know you're
managing partner,
but you handle your clients,
and I'll handle mine.
Hey, fair enough, but just
to be clear, we just merged.
We need to keep
every client we've got.
Like I said, Robert.
You handle your clients,
I'll handle mine.
I've got an assignment
for you.
Oh, good morning, Robert.
You look nice today too.
Hey, you get to work on time,
I'll tell you that necklace
is pretty all you want.
Right now, I need you
to look into
one of
Harvey Specter's clients.
Let me get this straight.
I just finished tussling
with the guy over sticking my
nose into one of his clients,
and now you want me
to stick my nose
into another one
of his clients?
Samantha,
the man needs your help.
And besides,
he's already seen the bad.
It's time to show him the good.
And again,
what exactly is the good
of me horning in
on his territory?
The good is for the firm.
He may not see it now,
but he will.
- Okay, give it to me.
- He's got two young bucks.
One of them
is up to something shady.
I don't know which one,
but he has a soft spot
for the one named Max.
If that guy's wrong,
he's not going to see it.
And no matter what, we can't
afford to lose the client,
because we just merged.
- Exactly.
I knew I keep you around
for a reason.
That you do.
Now, what's the
"something shady"?
- $50 million is missing.
- Ooh, that sounds fun.
So you're on it?
Oh, I'm more
than on it, Robert.
I know exactly what to do.
♪ Suits 8x02 ♪
Pecking Order
Original Air Date on July 25, 2018
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ I'll even eat a bean pie,
I don't mind ♪
♪ Me and Missy is so busy,
busy making money ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ All step back,
I'm 'bout to dance ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
♪ The greenback boogie ♪
- Hi, you must be Donna, I--
- Let me guess.
- Samantha Wheeler.
- What gave it away?
Several things,
not the least of which is you
ambushing me in my office.
Well, it doesn't
have to be an ambush.
It could just be
a friendly howdy-doo.
In that case,
let me grab my ten-gallon hat,
and help make it that.
You don't need
a ten-gallon hat.
You just need
to sign off on this.
Samantha,
this isn't a howdy-doo.
This is
an expense account request
three times larger
than anyone else's.
Huh, it was only
two times bigger
than anyone else's
at Rand Kaldor Zane.
- Try four times bigger.
- How do you know that?
Because it's my business
to know that.
And what I know about this is
that I can't sign off on it.
Is it because
I didn't say please?
It's because
I don't know that it's for.
- It's for me to do my job.
- That isn't very specific.
No, it's not,
but it's what I had before,
and it's what I need now.
If you want specifics,
talk to Robert Zane.
But he doesn't
have any, either,
which is how he prefers it.
Well, I'm not Robert.
But since I'm also not trying
to get off on the wrong foot,
I will authorize half of this,
which is the most we give.
I get it.
The new girl comes in,
and you want to make sure
she understands
the pecking order.
That wasn't my intention.
But if that's
the way you see it,
that tells me
a lot more about you
than it tells you about me.
Good to finally meet you,
Samantha.
Good to meet you too, Donna.
- Harvey, good, you're here.
- I am, but not for long.
I have to
take care of something
for one of Mike's old clients.
That's fine,
but I need to talk to you now.
You may not like
what I have to say--
Oh, I almost forgot.
Robert and I signed the papers
for him to take over
as managing partner.
They're on my desk.
- You what?
I know, I wouldn't
have thought it, either,
but as it turns out, I'd rather
not be managing partner.
- That's not what I--
- Hey, Louis, do me a favor.
Sign the papers and drop
them off to Donna, will you?
I think it's important that
we do it as soon as possible
to show Zane the support
that I would have wanted
if it would have been me.
Of course, if it
would have been you.
- Thanks, Louis.
- No problem, Harvey.
I'll get that off to Donna
as soon as I can.
- Nick Turner?
- Yes.
- Harvey Specter.
- Mr. Specter.
It's a pleasure meeting you,
but I wasn't aware
we had a meeting.
We don't.
I know we've never met,
but you meant a lot to Mike,
which means
you mean a lot to me,
and I just got a proposal
on your behalf.
Smith Barney
wants to take you public.
You're kidding.
That's fantastic.
And it's not just
your main business.
They want
your new venture too.
I'd love to say yes, but
the new business isn't ready.
Nick, it's not often
you get a top rate
investment bank knocking on the
doors of a fledgling business.
But if we do that,
we won't get
the full price of our upside.
What if I told you
they were willing to send over
500,000 in cash
as a good faith advance
against any transaction costs?
- I'm sorry, who are you?
- I'm Samantha Wheeler.
I work with Harvey.
Like I said,
half a million dollars.
All you have to do
is send your books over
to start the business,
and we'll get down
to making you
and your partner rich.
Well, that's very generous,
but as I was just saying
to Harvey, we're already rich,
and I don't feel comfortable
giving away our upside--
Nick, don't let this
briefcase get in the way
of a great opportunity--
- Look.
I appreciate you both
coming over,
but we're in the middle
of our build out,
so please, for right now,
I prefer to keep things
like they are.
- What the hell was that?
- That was one cool cucumber
who sounds pretty good,
but couldn't hide the fact
that he'd rather cut off his
arm than show us his books.
I meant, what were you doing
coming into my meeting?
I was introducing myself,
so we could get off
on a better foot.
I thought you said
we got off on the right foot.
Well, I think so,
but I could tell you didn't.
Well, let me
tell you something.
Derailing my meeting
when it was going
exactly as planned
isn't the way
to get off on a better foot.
I don't know what meeting
you were in,
but that man was not
going to show you his books.
And offering him a bribe
is going to get him to?
It wasn't a bribe.
It's untraceable cash,
which if he were embezzling,
he would have gone for.
We're missing 50 million.
500,000 isn't going to
get him out of his jam.
Well, maybe
if your ex-assistant
hadn't hamstrung me
with my expense account,
it would have been more.
Samantha,
you bring Donna into this,
we're never getting
on the right foot.
Look, that wasn't
what I meant. I--
That's enough!
I'm going to get
to the bottom of this,
and I don't need your help,
so why don't you have
some respect
for the chain of command,
and stay away from my clients.
Damn it.
God damn it, what the--
You know I knew that,
don't you?
Of course you did,
you were just testing
the structural integrity
of the machine
and the water
and the coffee mug.
- Precisely.
- Listen, Robert.
I didn't come in here
by accident.
I know we were on opposite
sides of the Samantha thing,
but I also know you play golf,
and I thought it might be nice
to get out there
and get to know each other.
I think what you really mean
is you'd like to impress
the new managing partner.
And what if I did?
Now let me
tell you something.
We get on that course, one of
two things is going to happen.
Either you're going
to piss me off
by being a scratch golfer,
or you're going to
piss me off
by being worse than me.
What's your point?
You want to impress me,
don't do it on a golf course.
Do it with a big, fat client.
- Harvey, we need to talk.
- We sure do.
Did you just give
Samantha Wheeler
the keys to Fort Knox
to use in my case?
No, I refused to give her
an expense account
even bigger than Fort Knox.
Why, what did she do?
She tried
to hijack my meeting
with a briefcase full of cash.
Let me guess,
you didn't like it,
and that's when she said
that she got the money from me.
No, she said it would have
worked if you'd given her more.
Which explains
why she went
over both of our heads
to Robert.
I don't believe this.
He tripled her expense account.
Yes, he did.
Harvey, we need to figure out
what we're going to do
about this woman.
Well, I'll tell you
what I'm going to do.
I'm going to go tell Robert
that if he doesn't
shorten her leash, she's gone.
Or you could
extend the olive branch,
and let her
work the case with you.
- And why would I do that?
- Because sometimes,
it's best to
keep your friends close,
and the new senior partner we
know nothing about even closer.
Well, that's
all well and fine,
but I am tired of
knowing nothing about her.
So am I, so while you're
keeping her distracted
with work,
I'm going to go digging
in her medicine cabinet.
Sheila, I need
to talk to you.
Louis, you're an hour early.
I hadn't got
my steno pad out yet.
- I know, but--
- Oh, my God.
You talked to Harvey,
didn't you?
I did, and it turns out
that Harvey's stepping down--
And now
you're managing partner.
I knew it! You're even
more of a man than I thought.
- Sheila--
- Ah, ah, Mr. Litt.
It's not Sheila anymore.
It's Miss Sazs,
secretary to the
managing partner,
and I am ready to be managed.
Sheila, as much as I would
love to manage you right now,
now is not
the appropriate time.
You're right.
It's not appropriate at all.
Just like this isn't,
and this isn't,
and this isn't--
- Whoa, Nelly.
Manage me, Louis.
Manage the shit out of me.
Okay, you want me
to manage the shit out of you?
I'm going to manage
the shit out of you.
And I'm not just Louis Litt.
I'm--
- A joke.
Look at him, pretending
to be managing partner.
I can't believe he thinks
that we would go for it.
Doesn't he know that
the first three letters
of managing is "man"?
Well, at least he's got
the "aging" part down.
Speaking of down,
looks like managing partner's
not the only job
he'd underperform.
Louis?
- Is something wrong?
- No, nothing.
Louis, something's wrong.
You're not at attention.
- I know, I just--I, uh...
- Oh, no, of course.
I should have known.
It's the stress
of your new job.
You just became
managing partner,
and you're gone
in the middle of the workday.
Yes.
Exactly, that's it.
- Then say no more.
Return to your kingdom.
There will be plenty of time
for this later.
Oh, good.
You're still here.
Wasn't about to be.
What do you say
we both pretend I'm not?
All right, what's going on?
Have you had a run in
with Samantha Wheeler yet?
No, but I take that to mean
one's coming.
The way she operates,
you can bet on it.
- How exactly does she operate?
- However the hell she wants.
- Mm-hmm.
- My feelings exactly.
Which is why I decided
to look into
little Miss "I don't answer
to anyone" myself.
Don't tell me
you came up empty.
Worse, half the people I
asked say she's from Kansas.
The other half, Manhattan.
Somehow, she managed to
graduate from an Ivy League,
a state school,
and the Sorbonne
all within the same two years.
One guy even says she's MI6,
but that's "just a hunch."
So you're telling me
that no one has the same story
and we don't know what's what?
And since the only person
with more contacts
than me is you, I was hoping
you could help me
get some answers.
Then turn around and
get a good night's sleep,
because by tomorrow afternoon,
you'll have all the answers
you need
on little Miss James Bond.
Do you think we should have a
secret handshake or something?
- Just go.
- Okay.
Louis, what are
you doing here?
We don't have
a session scheduled.
I'm not here for a session.
I'm here for an erection.
- A--A what now?
- I need a prescription, Stan.
I don't care if it's
for the blue pill,
or for the one with
the couples in the bathtubs.
I need it now.
Okay, Louis, why don't you
tell me what's going on?
Now that we have merged,
Sheila thinks that I should
become managing partner.
I told her that I would
bring it up to Harvey.
But before I could do that,
he told me that
he had already
handed the firm over to Zane.
And as a result
of telling Sheila that,
you are now having
intimacy issues.
As a result
of letting Sheila think
that I'm managing partner,
I can't get it up.
Then I must tell you,
a prescription
is not going to
solve your problem, Louis.
Why not?
Because your issue
isn't blood flow.
It's that you are lying
to Sheila.
- Doc.
- Louis.
How long are you planning
to hide the fact
that you're not really
managing partner?
I don't know,
two to three years?
My father convinced my mother
that he was a vice president
for a decade.
It can be done.
Be that as it may,
as I recall,
you accepted Harvey becoming
managing partner
after Jessica left.
That's when I realized
that I didn't want to
become managing partner.
Then why are you so reluctant
to tell Sheila that?
Because she's always
been attracted to my power.
I tell her that
I don't want to be something
that she wants me to be--
You're afraid she will
no longer want you.
- I can't lose her again, doc.
- I know, my friend.
But true power
is not pretending
to be what you're not.
It's admitting the truth
of who you are.
Katrina, you have a minute?
Of course, what can I
do for you, Alex?
I was actually hoping
you might be able to help me
narrow down a list.
Seems like that's
my specialty these days.
What kind of list?
These are the clients
who stayed with Rand Kaldor
after the merger.
- That's right.
And I want to know
which one of them
Robert Zane would like
to have back the most.
Well, if you want to know
who he'd like to have back
the most,
it's Starboard Airlines.
But if you want to know who you
should go after, I'm not sure.
Why wouldn't I want to
go after Starboard Airlines?
Because they
used to be represented
by Samantha Wheeler.
- I see.
Look, Alex, I don't know
how much you know about her,
but I wouldn't
want to pick a fight
with Samantha Wheeler
if it were me.
Well, I appreciate
the warning,
but if Starboard's the client
Robert would like,
that's the client
I'm going after.
Whether Samantha
likes it or not.
Then I wish you luck,
but do me a favor.
When she finds out about this,
don't tell her
you got it from me.
Thanks, Joe.
Now, you only owe me one.
Harvey.
- Look.
I'm not that big on apologies,
so you're not going to get one.
But I thought about it,
and if you're still interested
in working this thing together,
I'm good with that.
Good,
because I found out
some things
you might want to know.
You kept working on it,
even after
I told you to stay out of it?
I'm not big
on apologies, either.
This is the best
you're going to get.
As far as I can tell
from Nick's bank statements,
he doesn't spend shit
on shit; he's clean.
Well, his spending
may be accounted for,
but the original
50 million isn't.
- What are you talking about?
- I can't find any record
of deposits
before the second 50 came in.
As far as I can tell,
that 50 covered
the entire cost of the project.
Wait a second.
He didn't need the first 50.
He needed the second 50.
And he couldn't
get the second
without saying
he had the first.
Which means
he misrepresented himself
to his investors, and
this is definitely criminal.
Shit, we need to go tell Max,
and run through his options.
Harvey, I've fixed
a lot of situations like this.
The first thing we need to do
is go to the guy
that caused the problem.
And give him a chance
to implicate his partner?
No way, we go to the guy
who came to us.
He's our client.
- The business is our client.
And I'm okay with you
working with me on this,
but I am not okay with you
working it against me.
Okay, we'll go to Max
first thing in the morning.
I have your word
you'll leave it until tomorrow?
You have my word.
Then let's figure out
how to get them out of this.
So you're telling me
Nick defrauded our investors?
No, Max, I'm telling you
that's what it looks like.
I don't give a shit
what it looks like.
We need to know what it is.
- No, we don't.
Because right now,
it's conjecture.
We prove it,
we have an obligation
to inform your investors.
- So inform them.
We do that, your whole
company goes out of business.
And if I keep this a secret,
they'll think I was in on it.
This discussion is over,
I need--
What you need
is to calm down,
and listen to us right now,
because we have a way out.
- What is it?
- According to your contract,
you have the option
to buy out your investors
at a 30% return.
They go away happy, and we put
this in our rearview mirror.
And assuming we can even come
up with that kind of money,
what if someone finds out
before we do?
- No one's going to find--
- That's not an answer.
- Max--
- No.
This is Nick's mistake,
not mine,
and innocent people
go to the police.
Listen to me,
you turn him in,
you'll look like
a guilty man running scared.
- I am scared.
- Max.
You used to trust Mike.
Now I need you to trust me.
We get these guys paid off;
it'll take maybe three days.
Then you're fine.
Okay, Harvey.
I trust you.
Okay, we did it your way.
We talked to Max, and we
presented a united front.
You better not be saying
you want to divide it now.
All I'm saying
is there's another option.
We replace the fabricated
50 million with a real 50
from an actual investor;
no one will ever know.
Oh, so all we have to do
is commit fraud
to get out of fraud?
And how, exactly,
is that any different
from what you want to do?
Because my way
is protected
under the letter of the law.
And we have to pay
a 30% return
on something
that isn't worth it.
Keeping Max out of prison
seems worth it to me.
So instead of fighting with me,
why don't you
start thinking about
where we're going
to get that money?
Gavin Andrews.
You must be the guy
who wants to be my new lawyer.
I see you like
to cut to the chase.
You ever hear the saying
"time is money"?
Well, I got a shitload of one,
because I don't
waste the other.
Then why in God's name
are you wasting
either one of them
at a firm like Rand Kaldor?
You really want to kick them
when they're down, don't you?
This isn't about them.
This is about you.
You've got routes under siege.
You've lost gates at LaGuardia.
And if you think Kaldor's idea
of you merging with Delta
is the answer to your problems,
then you're not the man
I thought you were.
Okay.
You get one case;
you handle it right,
you can have my business.
I'm not in the habit of
sharing custody of a client.
You're not sharing,
because you're not
officially my lawyer, and it's
not business; it's personal.
You're telling me I handle
a personal issue for you,
off the record,
I get your corporate business?
Why would you do that?
- Because I need someone
I can trust to handle both.
Now before you say anything,
if you agree to this,
you're my guy, not some
associate, not another partner.
You.
Okay, I'm in.
And the only thing left for you
to do is tell me what you need.
The truth is, I'm in the
middle of a nasty divorce,
which had led to an even
nastier custody battle.
How many kids,
and what are their ages?
Just one.
And she's 185 years old.
Harvey, I know
you're on your way out,
but you got to see this.
- What is it?
I don't believe this.
- What are you going to do?
What I should have done
in the first place.
Kick Samantha Wheeler
the hell off this case.
What the hell did you do?
- I take it Max called you?
- No, he sent Donna a letter
formalizing Nick Turner's
transition to CEO
since Max is suddenly
leaving the company.
Actually, he's stepping down
to spend more time
with his family.
I don't give a shit
what he's doing.
I want to know what you did.
- I did what you wouldn't do.
Protect the client.
- Bullshit.
Max agreed to exercise
the buyout clause.
And yet, he still contacted
a criminal defense attorney.
- What?
- He panicked,
and he wasn't
going to keep his mouth shut,
and our client was
going to go out of business.
So you felt the answer
was forcing him out?
The answer was and always is
protect the company.
And the fact that you were
more focused on protecting Max
than our client
is exactly why Robert
wanted me to get involved
in the first place.
What?
I wasn't trying to
make things better with you.
He wanted me
to keep an eye on you.
You had no right
to force that kid
out of his own company.
- I didn't force him out.
- Save your bullshit.
You gave me your word
that you weren't going to be
pulling something like this,
so stay the hell away
from my client,
or the next time you
make a move behind my back,
you'll be finding yourself
another job.
Oh, there he is.
How was your day, my king?
Not great, actually.
Well, maybe I can
release your stress.
Sheila, wait.
We need to talk.
Oh, shoot,
you've had a hard day.
We can talk later.
Right now is--
I'm not managing partner.
What?
I went to Harvey,
like I said.
Before I could
get the words out,
he said that he had already
offered the job to Robert.
Well, what happened when you
told him you wanted the job?
I didn't say
I wanted the job.
Wait, so instead of fighting
for what you want,
you decided to lie to me
about getting it?
- Oh, Sheila, that's not fair.
- How could you lie to me?
I didn't. I came here
to tell you the truth.
But you thought
I already had the job,
and you seemed
so excited about it.
Oh, my God.
That's why you couldn't
have sex, isn't it?
Yes.
Yes, so I went to
Dr. Lipschitz to talk about it,
and you know what he told me?
He told me that I should trust
that you love me
and that I can
tell you the truth.
And I think instead
of letting your therapist
convince you to
give up your dream,
maybe you should have marched
back into Harvey's office
to take what's yours.
- Sheila, please.
I'm not giving up anything.
I don't want to be
managing partner.
And now you're not
only lying to me,
you're lying to yourself.
- No, I'm not.
I don't want managing partner,
and you said you love me.
Well, this is who I am,
and you can either accept that
or not, but it's not changing.
And it's understandable
for you
to be concerned about your
brother.
But...
why do you believe
he's lying to himself?
Because I know my brother,
and I know he wanted
that promotion.
And I can't stand seeing him
not go after it,
just because some crackpot
undermined his confidence.
And who exactly is this--
this crackpot?
I'll tell you who it is.
It's his...mother.
Uh, forgive me,
but wouldn't you refer
to his mother as your mother?
Well, yes, but...
Well, this isn't about me,
I'm trying to--
Oh, my God, you're Sheila.
I can't believe
I didn't see it before.
I'm sorry, but I told you
on the phone.
It is unethical for me to see
you without Louis' permission.
I could care less
about your ethics.
- Excuse me?
- Cut the bullshit, Lipschitz.
Louis came to see you after
Zane got managing partner,
and instead of encouraging him
to take it back,
you undermined his confidence.
- Hm.
It's interesting
that you think I'm the one
undermining his confidence,
because the only times
in his life that Louis
has been unable to perform
have been with you,
including most recently
when he went to tell you
the truth and couldn't
because he was afraid
of how you might view him.
What the hell
is that supposed to mean?
It means, as well
as you think you know him,
he may know you even better.
Because Louis does not
want to be managing partner.
And rather than believe him,
you can only see
his admission as cowardice.
But I don't understand.
He wanted
managing partner once.
Why would he
change his mind now?
Because people
are not set in stone.
And I suspect
something has replaced
managing partner
as his heart's desire.
- A baby.
- No, Sheila.
Love.
And I don't think
you need me to tell you
Louis Litt would do anything
to not lose the woman he loves.
You know, I had heard about
the legendary Donna Paulson
long before I even got here.
- Oh, that's interesting.
Because I've never
heard of you.
Because that's how I want it,
but you want to be known.
And I got to tell you,
the reality is a lot more
disappointing than the legend.
- Excuse me?
- I had a run-in with Harvey
because you went running
to him about Max.
You're damn right I did,
he deserves to know
when someone's
operating behind his back.
And I deserve the chance
to tell him
what's going on to his face.
Oh, so you're upset because
I beat you to the punch?
I'm upset because
if you have any issue with me,
you should come to me
and not go around me.
Like how you
went around me to Robert
for your expense account?
So that's what
this is really about.
No, this is about
your behavior with Harvey
and Alex and me
and about 100 other things
that all tell me
you don't care about
anyone here but yourself.
If you really think that,
you know nothing about me,
and I'll tell you
something else.
Secretly digging into me isn't
gonna answer your questions.
Yeah, I know you've been
doing that too.
And I wouldn't have to
if you'd been upfront
about who you are.
You want to know
something about me?
You go ahead and ask.
- And how should I trust
that I'd get a straight answer?
Because I am on
this team now,
and whether
you believe it or not,
I've got its
best interests at heart.
Well, you got a funny way
of showing it.
Because from where I stand,
Harvey is the firm,
and you don't seem to
have his back at all.
Are you enjoying the ballet?
I most certainly am,
and how about yourself?
To tell you the truth,
Mrs. Andrews,
I wouldn't be less entertained
if this were
a second grade musical.
Who are you,
and what are you doing here?
I'm here on behalf
of your husband.
Then you can turn around,
and walk right out
because you can't contact me
without my attorneys present.
And that would be true, if I
was his lawyer, but I'm not.
And what exactly did my
soon-to-be ex-husband tell you?
That whatever issues you had
led you to take
his prized Renoir and loan it
to the Met for the sole purpose
of infuriating him.
He's lucky I didn't
burn the damn thing.
All the same, I'm here to
convince you to take it back.
Now, what will it take
to get you to join the team?
The Villa in Bordeaux,
free and clear.
And I never want to worry
about covering the taxes.
- That's a big ask.
- And it's an expensive
painting that I have
no interest in,
and he can't get back
without looking like an asshole
to the kind of people
he wants to do business with.
What?
I can see
why you don't really care
if your lawyers
are here or not.
So we have a deal?
We need to talk.
Don't tell me
Harvey came to you.
- He sure did.
- What exactly did he say?
I'm not here to talk about
what he said.
I'm here to talk about
what you're doing.
I'm doing what you
asked me to do.
I asked you to help the man,
not piss him off.
You asked me
to save the client.
This is what
it's going to take,
and since when do you care
if I piss someone off?
Since you made me promise
to put your name
up on that wall next.
Because if you do this,
Harvey's going to do
anything he can
to stop your name from ever
going up on that wall.
You asked me
to do it, Robert.
I can't take it back.
What do you want me to do now?
Show Harvey
what I see in you.
Whatever happens along the way,
when push comes to shove,
you will never let him down.
Am I interrupting?
Sheila, what are you
doing here?
Well, I realized, that, um...
that you've been to
my office a lot recently,
but I haven't come to yours
in a long time.
Well, I know it's not
the office that you, uh...
wanted for me.
It's the
perfect office, Louis.
And you are the perfect man.
And I'm sorry
if I made you feel
like I ever
thought differently.
So you don't think I'm weak
for not wanting
to be managing partner?
No, I don't.
And the reason I got so upset
wasn't because
I think you're weak.
It's that I thought
Harvey and Robert Zane
didn't even value you enough
to hear you out.
- No, they didn't.
- And on top of that,
you were so excited to go
in there and make your case.
- Yes, I was.
- So what happened?
- I went in to see Harvey.
- And what?
He didn't even give me
the goddamn time of day.
Okay, Louis, I'm not trying
to get you worked up.
Because I'm telling you,
I don't need you
to be managing partner.
No, and I don't need it
either, but what I do need
is to be given
the common courtesy
of being treated like an equal.
So what are you going to do?
Well, the first thing
I'm going to do
is go home right now
and do what I
couldn't do the other day.
Then tomorrow, first thing, I'm
going to go tell Robert Zane
and Harvey Specter that there
are three names on that wall,
and one of them deserves
some goddamn respect.
Okay.
I got your mysterious message
about meeting in here.
What's going on?
Did you find something out
about Samantha?
- She did.
- What are you doing here?
She's here because like you,
I got a lot of
conflicting information.
She's the only person I know
that's had direct experience
with Samantha.
Well?
People either love her
or are afraid of her.
But anyone who's ever used her
says the same thing.
She is as good as they come.
And when the chips are down,
you want her in your corner.
Do you think
she's in our corner?
I guess that depends
on whether or not
Robert and Harvey
are in the same corner.
I know you're
not in the mood.
I just want to explain what
happened with Max Louden.
I know what happened.
You blackmailed him.
- I did not blackmail him.
- Then what did you do?
I asked myself, how the hell
did Nick pull this shit
on Max in the first place?
He's not an idiot.
He must have been distracted.
What difference
does that make?
The difference is,
Max was distracted
with his sister
who has cancer.
So I pulled some strings,
got her into a trial,
and he was more than happy
to step down.
Okay, so you didn't
boot him out the way I thought.
What's going
to stop Nick Turner
from putting us
in this position again?
What would have
stopped him your way?
Max would've.
That was the reason
I wanted to back him.
Well, this isn't Max,
but maybe it will do.
Let me guess, you want to be
the one to do it.
No, I don't.
He's your client; you do it.
Unless, of course,
you need me to hold your hand.
I'm pretty sure I can
take care of this myself.
This is nice work, Samantha.
I just want to be
part of the team.
You know, the place is really
starting to come together.
Doesn't look any different
than the last time you saw it.
I know, I just figured
you're a bullshit artist,
so you'd probably appreciate
a little smoke
blown up your ass.
- Excuse me?
- Okay, have it your way.
We'll cut the bullshit
and get to the part where you
defrauded your investors
to pay for this place.
- I didn't--
- And before you even
lie to me about it,
why don't you start thanking me
for getting you out of it?
- You got me new funding?
- I did.
Of course, to do that,
I had to let the bank in
on your IPO plans.
- I don't have any IPO plans.
You do now.
I get it.
Once we're publicly traded,
I'll have a board of directors,
and they'll have
full access to my books.
Which means I hope you
enjoyed breaking the law once,
because it's never
going to happen again.
And what if I say no,
and then I fire you?
Well, then you
end up in prison,
which happens 99% of the time
in cases like this anyway.
What happens the other
1% of the time?
You're looking at him.
And trust me, Nick.
A guy who can do what I did,
you want him on your team.
I'll be in touch.
Harvey, you look like the cat
that ate the canary.
More like the man
who took care of business.
- So you got it done?
- Samantha got it done.
- Does that mean we're good?
- It means the next time
you're worried
about how I handle my clients,
tell me to my face.
Fair enough.
And how about Samantha?
You good with her?
I wouldn't go throwing
a ticker tape parade just yet,
but yeah, I admit, I'm starting
to see what you see in her.
Well, that's all
I was hoping for.
Which means now, I can tell you
why I was hoping it.
What's going on?
What haven't you told me?
That her name
goes up on the wall next.
And before you say anything,
I gave her my word.
- Listen, Robert--
- Whatever it is
you're about to say,
it's going to have to wait,
because the three of us are
going to have a little talk
about something
right the hell now.
- What's going on, Louis?
- I'll tell you what it is.
The two of you decided
who's running this firm
without including me
in the conversation.
What are you talking about?
You signed the agreement.
The agreement
that you drew up,
and just expected me
to be okay with.
You're saying that you
want to be managing partner?
No, Robbie.
But you wouldn't know that,
because you never asked,
and I will not
be the third wheel
just because
my name comes last.
No one thinks of you
as a third wheel, Louis.
Oh, really?
Because you wouldn't be here
if it weren't for me,
and you wouldn't have a firm
at all if it weren't for me.
I saved both
your fucking asses,
and not only didn't
you think to thank me,
as far as I can tell, you
didn't even clock what I did.
Now, I am a partner
just as much as you,
and I am done
having to remind you of that.
So the next time there's
a decision to be made, guys,
you better pull up
a seat for me at that table,
or I swear to God, I will break
the whole goddamn thing in two.
Any questions?
No, Louis, no questions.
Good.
Looks like
you're not the only one
I'm going to have to
make good with.
But what were you talking about
before he came
storming in here?
It doesn't matter,
what matters is
what are we going to do
about Louis?
- Beautiful girls.
- They take after their mother.
Hm, well, I hear their father
is going after
Starboard Airlines.
- Where'd you hear that?
- I'll take that as a yes.
- And what if I am?
- If I were you, I'd stop.
And if I were me,
I'd say you're only saying that
because they used to be
your client,
and you're not going to like
how it looks
when they become mine.
I'm saying that
because Gavin Andrews
is a hell of a lot more
than meets the eye,
and the guy isn't worth
the trouble.
What kind of trouble?
Let's just say I would have
thought a guy with your history
would want to be more careful
about who he
gets into bed with.
What the hell are you doing
looking into my history?
I'm doing what you
should be doing with him.
Then tell me
what you're talking about,
or get out of
my goddamn office
because I've got
a client to sign.
Sorry to bother you, Alex.
Good luck with that client.
- There's my lion.
- Are you naked under there?
This is my sex robe,
isn't it?
Yeah, of course, I would
recognize that anywhere,
but Sheila,
where is this coming from?
It's coming from right there.
- Oh, my God, they heard me.
- They heard you roar.
Because you are a lion.
- I am, aren't I?
Yes, you are.
And you should know that you're
not the only one with a clock.
The dean gave you
a clock today, too?
Not that kind of clock.
I have an internal clock.
Sheila, are you saying
what I think you're saying?
Yes, I am,
because when I told you
you're the perfect man,
Louis Litt, I meant it.
And I want to make
a perfect baby with you.
- Are you sure?
- Absolutely.
And I don't want to just
pull the goalie.
I want to start trying.
And I want to start trying
right now.
This is incredible.
Can we still do it dirty?
- Of course.
Why couldn't we do it dirty?
Because I don't want our son
to think of us that way.
Louis, our unborn son
will be a Litt.
He'll respect us
for being dirty.
You're 100% right, we can be
as filthy as we want.
- I'll get the bananas.
- What are you, crazy?
You're going to be
the mother of my child.
I'll get the bananas.
You know, the elevators
come a lot faster
when you actually call them.
I was just thinking.
Well, I wanted to
let you know that I finished
checking on Samantha.
And?
As far as I can tell,
she may not be Mother Teresa,
but she's an asset to the team.
I guess that depends
on who the team is.
- What do you mean?
- Zane promised Samantha
she'd be the next name partner.
And did you tell him that you
made the same promise to Alex?
No, I didn't.
Harvey, you can't put them
both up at the same time.
It'll dilute the promotion
for both of them.
I know.
So what are you going to do?
I'm going to do
what Jessica would.
I'm going to go home,
make myself a drink,
and figure out
how to get my way.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
www.tvsubtitles.net