Previously, on "Suits"...
Which one of my clients
are you after?
Because we both know
you can't have Pfizer.
- Yes, I can.
- Then make me name partner.
You don't just slap
somebody's name on the wall
to get a client.
I'm not just slapping
his name up, Louis.
I'm making a move.
I'm not saying Donna doesn't
deserve a promotion;
I'm just saying making partner
means something.
And I'm concerned that being
one here
won't mean what it used to.
This is an amazing amount
of work.
I stayed up all night
doing it.
But I thought you take the
night shift with your son.
I told my wife she'd have
to take it last night.
I thought you might
need a little relief.
You sure?
Support his head.
There we go.
Holy shit. Gordon doesn't
really wanna take over.
He just wants
to orchestrate a deal
where his guys come back,
they vote to merge with Zane,
and we cease to exist.
I just found out
that my two partners
are willing to stab me
in the back.
God damn it, Louis.
I'm trying the best I can.
Well, then,
try something else,
because giving you the reins
a half hour
before we drive off
a cliff
isn't gonna do shit.
I just came to make sure that
the paperwork was in order
for your clients to come over
and join our new firm.
I went and saw Andy Forsyth
today.
You went to see him about us
moving to Seattle?
If we're ever gonna do
something like this in our
lives, now is the time.
And what about the wedding?
We could move it up.
If I've learned one thing,
it's that there is nothing
that I can't handle
when I have you by my side.
You're the husband I've
always wanted.
And I can't wait to begin our
adventure together.
Rachel and I were offered a
chance
to run a firm in
Seattle.
- Mike--
- Harvey,
this is who I am.
It's who I've always been.
It's time, Harvey.
I'll tell you what, Robert.
Your baby girl
just got married,
I'm gonna throw you a bone.
Your name goes first.
No. No.
You think I don't know
what you're doing.
Then I owe you.
Yours goes first.
You saying I owe you?
You do owe me.
I saved your ass.
Well, you only did
that because we put you
in a terrible position.
Wait.
That's against me.
Jesus Christ,
what have I got myself into?
I'll tell you what.
You got yourself
into Zane Specter Litt.
Or Specter Zane Litt.
Either way...
Litt comes last.
Hey.
Wanna go out and get a burger?
I do.
But it's 2:00 a.m.
If I go out for
a burger right now,
the only thing
I'm getting is a divorce.
Copy that. I'll get you
one from the kitchen.
Yeah, meet me downstairs.
Hide it in the gift bag
or some shit.
- You're here early.
- I am.
I know this is about the time
you finish your morning run.
Look, Harvey.
If this is about me
getting into it with Louis
while you were gone--
It isn't. I didn't even know
that happened.
Well, you might as well
hear about it now.
I came to him with an idea
to save the firm
that involved making me
temporary managing partner
and he bit my head off.
Let me guess, he thought
you were coming after me.
Harvey, I would never
do that to you.
I know that, but that's not
what I'm here to talk about.
I'm here to tell you
that as of this morning
we're merging with Robert Zane.
- What?
- Alex.
I don't believe it.
When I came over
you said my name
would be the one to go up next.
I know that,
but this was
the only way
to save the firm.
And you know
as well as I do,
Zane has been
a name partner
longer than me and Louis
combined.
All right,
I get it.
But we had an agreement.
And I want your word right now
that you're gonna honor it.
You have my word.
Your name goes up next.
All right.
One more thing.
Did Louis know about
the merger before this morning?
Yeah, why?
Because if he didn't tell
me about it,
he must really not trust me.
Which means when it is time to
put my name up there--
- Louis'll be fine, Alex.
- And what if he's not?
Like I said,
you have my word.
Of course I would
do that for you.
I would do anything for you
because I love you.
I promise.
I will never bring it up again.
We never have
to get a Maine Coon.
- Sheila?
- Yes.
Anyway, I brought you in
because I want--
Katrina, what's on your mind?
Nothing.
It's just, giving up cats?
Louis, after all she put
you through, are you sure?
I am.
And besides,
she's still open
to getting a short hair.
- Well, then I'm happy for you.
- And I'm happy for you, too,
because today is the day
that you get to make
your two greatest loves
more efficient.
Don't tell me.
We're merging with Zane;
we have more associates
than we can handle;
and you need
the one person
who worked at both firms
to cull that herd.
Exactly.
And now I need you to come up
with a list of the ten
least-efficient associates
without telling me names
or whether or not
they come from Zane or us.
Got it.
And, Katrina?
Thanks for your concern
about Sheila and me.
Louis, you know I care
for you
deeply in
a completely asexual manner.
And I too care
for you deeply
and see you neither
as man nor woman.
Thank you, Louis.
Kinder words were never spoken.
I'll have my list for you
by the end of the day.
I'm gonna miss her too.
I'm not sure which is worse.
Finding out Mike was a fraud
or that he's taking
my daughter away.
Pretty sure it was
the fraud thing.
You probably got a point.
Speaking of frauds
and your daughter.
She left that for me?
A little welcome to the firm
from your little girl.
By the way,
Harvey wants to meet
at 9:30 in the conference room.
So in the meantime,
why don't you
set yourself up
in Mike's old office.
Thank you, Donna.
It's nice to have you here,
Robert.
Oh, we'll see how nice
it is once I tell Harvey
it's not his old office
that I'm looking to be in.
Claiming managing partner
already.
Isn't that a bold statement
for day one?
Let me tell you something,
Red.
I've been making bold
statements my entire career.
I'm sure as hell not
about to stop now.
♪ Suits 8x01 ♪
Right-Hand Man
Original Air Date on July 18, 2018
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ I'll even eat a bean pie,
I don't mind ♪
♪ Me and Missy is so busy,
busy making money ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ All step back,
I'm 'bout to dance ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
♪ The greenback boogie ♪
All right,
I think we all know
who's gonna be
managing partner
isn't something
we're gonna decide overnight.
Therefore,
for the sake of firm harmony,
I suggest we start
with conflicts of interest.
- Fine with me.
- Me too.
Great.
As you can see,
I've taken
the liberty of suggesting
who drops which client.
And I am confident you'll agree
with all of my proposals
with the exception--
- I'm not dropping Dexterol.
And I'm not
dropping Clavatin.
- Exactly.
- Exactly what?
What do you mean,
"Exactly what?"
I knew that neither of you
would be willing
to give up those particular
clients. Exactly that.
You mean you don't have
a suggestion?
I have a suggestion.
You drop yours,
then the next time
we have a major conflict
I'll drop mine.
You sure about that?
Because the next major conflict
we're gonna have is
who's managing partner.
Then what exactly
is your idea?
I say whoever's
client billed
the most hours
last year stays.
Well, that's pretty damn
convenient
because your client went
through a merger
so their billables
are inflated.
You're saying
that the sun got in your eyes
and that's why you dropped
the big pass?
Wait a second,
Harvey's right.
- Come again?
- No, not about who to drop.
Your client did just
go through a merger.
They're in a whole new
line of business.
Most of which doesn't conflict
with Clavatin anymore.
Where you going with this?
I'm saying if we can get
either client
to drop the one division
where they still overlap
you can keep them both.
Well, in that case
I'll get my client to drop.
It's the least I can do.
Oh, no.
I'll do the honors.
After all, you welcomed me
into your home.
Why don't we make it
a friendly wager.
We each get our client
to drop.
First one who gets there wins.
Sure thing.
Don't do it.
Don't do what?
Don't try to get Zane's
client to dump their division
after telling him you'd get
your client to do it.
How do you even know
that's what happened?
I know because Louis told me.
What do you mean
Louis told you?
The meeting just ended two
seconds ago
and I came right back here.
In that case,
I mean,
I heard Louis' voice
on the recording device
that I had installed
in the conference room.
You bugged the meeting?
Bugged is such
a distasteful word.
- That's not an answer.
- Okay.
You want an answer?
I have been listening
to your conversations
since you were an associate
and I'm not about to stop now.
Now, do you want to quibble
about my methods
or do you want
to get the part
where I save you
from yourself?
- Donna.
- Harvey, you heard him.
Zane's got his eye on
managing partner.
I know good
and well what he's after.
Then why would you give
him ammunition?
Because you think
this is gonna be fun.
But trust me,
you go after him
and it's gonna get more serious
than you thought.
And in the end,
you're just gonna prove
that he's better suited
to be in your office than you.
Okay, Donna.
Okay, you're not gonna pick
a fight with Robert Zane?
No. Okay, I'm gonna find
someone else to do it for me.
Twice in one day.
To what do I owe
the pleasure now?
I'm here to tell you,
you want your name
on the door you got to earn it.
I thought I already had.
Maybe you have,
maybe you haven't,
but I got something for you
to do anyway.
And what exactly is that?
I need you to get
Robert Zane's biggest client
to sell
their manufacturing division.
Harvey,
you point me up the hill,
I'm gonna kill whoever's
at the top.
- But?
- But in this case,
the guy at
the top is on our side.
- Is he?
- What are you talking about?
I'm telling you
this is gonna determine
who runs the firm.
Zane knows it and I know it.
So if you want me
to be able to live up
to that promise,
I need you to do this.
And I don't like
being threatened
for you to uphold
a promise you already made.
I don't either,
but like it or not,
this benefits both of us.
And I guarantee you right now,
Zane's going to
his right-hand man
to ask the same thing.
And who is his right hand?
Your job isn't
to ask who he is.
Your job is to kick his ass.
You planning
on making it in
to the new offices
anytime soon?
What for?
Help you pick out new lamps?
What's that supposed to mean?
It means I knew
you'd come in here
and ask me to take care of
whatever needs taking care of
whenever it needs
taking care of.
So unless you want to step in
and take a beating,
why don't you just get to it?
You think I couldn't
handle you?
I think
if you took your tie off,
we could find out.
Shit, I come up there
and get my ass kicked
by a skinny white girl, my life
would never be the same.
So what do we got?
A number two, a number six?
Number 14 with a side of 11.
Well, leave the file
and the particulars,
I'll get to it when I'm done.
- Samantha.
I need you to come
through for me on this one.
Come on, Robert, have I
ever let you down before?
You've never lost,
but you have let me down
a time or two.
Well, then, I give you
my word this will not
be one of those times.
Damn, could kick my ass.
Katrina,
what are you doing here?
I gave you an assignment--
I finished it.
What do you mean
you finished it?
I asked you to evaluate
50 associates.
How could you have done
that already?
I didn't.
PATTIE did it for me.
- Who the hell's Pattie?
- Not who, what.
Personal
Assessment Tallying
and Totalling Individual
Efficiency.
Say what now?
I plugged in 16 parameters
and quantifiables,
PATTIE popped out a list
ranking the associates
from 1 to 50.
Katrina, this is amazing.
Not only that,
it's completely objective.
The bottom ten are
the least efficient, period.
Well, then I guess
all that's left is for you
to tell me who they are
and for me to let them go.
About that, Louis.
I'd like to be the one
to do the letting go.
Katrina, I could never ask
you to do that.
You're not asking;
I am.
I don't understand.
Why would you want to?
Louis, you told me I could be
senior partner one day.
Which means, I need to be able
to do things like this.
- But--
- And as Ned Stark would say,
"He who passes the sentence
should swing the sword."
You know I can never argue
with Ned Stark.
I do.
Thank you.
Katrina.
Make them clean deaths.
- I will.
Jeremy Stiller.
- Who are you?
- I work for Robert Zane.
Ah. Well, I'm sorry
Ms. Works for Robert Zane,
but this is private property.
I'm gonna have to
ask you to leave.
I have to say,
it almost feels like you knew
this encounter would happen.
That's because
Alex Williams told me
a man named Sam Wheeler
would be coming.
Which means he was
resourceful enough
to find out my name but
didn't have enough imagination
to think I might be a woman.
Well,
he had enough imagination
to tell me not
to take your call.
And he only did that
because he's afraid
you might like
what I have to say.
Well, I don't.
Even if I did,
I'm loyal to Specter Litt.
Look, I'm sorry.
Clearly we got off
on the wrong foot, but I--
We did.
Now if you don't mind,
I have work to do.
I grew up poor.
We lived on a farm
and my only chance
of going to college
was to get a scholarship,
which I did.
Sophomore year, the company
that funded my scholarship
went out of business.
So I had a choice.
Do it myself,
or don't do it at all.
Since then,
I have scratched and clawed
for everything I have ever had.
Why are you telling me this?
Because the details
were different
but I know the same thing
happened to you.
Please.
All I'm asking
is for you to hear me out.
Okay, I'll hear you out.
But there's no way
I'm dropping my business.
Donna, do you have a minute?
Does this have to do
with the associates
we're letting go?
- It does.
And since I understand
you'll be doing
exit interviews with them,
I thought you should know
who's going.
That's funny.
That's not what I thought
you'd be asking.
What do you mean?
Katrina, are you sure you're
going to be okay
firing people you've worked
with for years?
I mean, I know you value
you the firm, but this--
I know it isn't going
to be easy, Donna.
I was once let go
from here too,
but I'll tell you
what I told Louis.
That if I'm going
to grow in my role here
this is something I'm going
to have to learn to do.
Fair enough.
Hang on a second,
has Louis seen this list?
No, why?
There's a problem with
the first name.
He's not gonna like it.
- I know that.
Then I suggest
you let him know
before you pull the trigger.
- I can't do that.
- Why not?
Because this process
is supposed to be impartial.
And if I tell Louis
who I'm going to fire
just because he won't like
one of the names on the list--
What won't I like?
Louis, Katrina was
just informing me
that it's not
a good idea for you--
What name?
- Brian.
- Nope.
- Louis.
- Donna, this is between
Katrina and me.
No, Louis, it isn't.
This is about the firm
and its integrity.
You asked me to come up with
an objective metric
and by that metric,
Brian Altman has to go.
- So change the metric.
- I can't do that.
And even if I could
he'd be just as likely
to go down as go up.
I understand that,
but I don't give a shit.
Anyone but Brian.
- Louis--
Katrina, listen to me.
You asked for this
responsibility
so I gave it to you.
So now I am telling you
to find a way to keep him.
Okay, Louis.
I'll see what I can do.
Harvey, we need to talk.
Don't tell me,
there's a problem.
- There is.
- What is it now?
It's not
that big of a deal,
but you're gonna have
to figure out what font to use
to put my name
on the letterhead.
Because as of 2:00 p.m. today,
Robert Zane's client
is officially dropping their
manufacturing division.
You telling me you did it?
Signed, sealed,
and delivered, my man.
Now let's get down
to figuring out--
What?
How to counter my last move?
Because you may have
them signed and sealed
but I'm here to tell you
your delivery
got lost on the way.
- Who the hell are you?
- Her name is Sam Wheeler.
Truth be told, Alex,
I prefer Samantha.
You two know each other?
No, but it doesn't
take a genius to figure
out she's Zane's guy.
- He didn't figure it out.
What I figured out is,
whoever you are,
if you think you can waltz
into my office--
- Harvey, I got it.
- Do you?
Because unless
I'm misreading the situation,
she's saying you don't.
- Harvey.
You know what, you two are
obviously having some trouble.
The good news is
you'll have plenty of time
to work it out because
as of end of business today,
your client is dropping
their manufacturing division.
And we can get back
to the business of running
this firm under
the direction of Robert Zane.
You two have a nice--
You know I don't mean it.
No.
- What do you mean, no?
- I mean this is my fight.
You asked me to fight it,
and I'm not gonna
let you step into
the middle of round two.
It may be
the middle of round two,
but you just told me you got
a first round knock-out.
Well, I was wrong.
But I'm still in the ring,
my partnership's on the line,
and I'm not getting out.
- Then you better win.
- Where you going?
To pick a fight
in my own weight class.
Robert, how are you?
Settling in all right?
Doing just fine,
thanks for asking.
What can I do for you?
I just dropped by
to tell you I had
an interesting conversation
with your girl, Sam.
She's kicking
your ass, isn't she?
Not mine.
Since neither of you
had the balls to invite
me into the ring.
Just like you
didn't invite me.
And don't give me any of this
nonsense about we had a deal.
Because you broke it
just as fast as I did.
I did,
but my issue isn't
that she's fighting
your battles for you.
It's that she walked
into my office like
I wasn't the managing partner
of this firm.
And I didn't like
the way she introduced herself
to me either.
But that's not
what your issue is.
You're pissed.
Because I didn't get in
the ring myself.
Because if I'm not in there,
you're not in there.
And you can't stand not
being in there.
Are you saying
I always have to shoot?
Because I'm fine
passing the ball.
I'm talking about
being a coach.
And if you were one,
you wouldn't mind
just sitting back and watching
Samantha Wheeler
eat your boy for breakfast.
And if you think
that's gonna happen,
you don't know Alex Williams.
Oh, I know that's what's
gonna happen.
And the person you don't know
is Harvey Specter.
I know myself just fine.
Then tell me you'll stay
the hell out of this.
No problem, I just gave
Alex my word I'd stay out.
And what kind of
managing partner would I be
if I couldn't live up
to my word.
Because,
just so we're clear, Robert,
I am managing partner.
- Whatever you say, Harvey.
But remember,
you didn't only
give your word
to Alex Williams anymore.
You just gave your word to me.
And the next thing I knew...
There were peas everywhere!
On me, on the wall,
everywhere but in his mouth.
I'm telling you, it was--
- Disgusting.
I was gonna say adorable,
but...
Anyway, this is nice.
Katrina, I'm glad
you suggested lunch.
So tell me, Brian.
Do you think
that having a baby
has made you more productive
in the workplace?
- Are you kidding me?
- I see.
Then what about
your efficiency?
I understand children
sometimes necessitate
better time management skills.
For my wife, maybe.
But to tell you the truth,
I'm all over the place.
Then what would
you say
are the areas
where you do excel?
- With my son?
- No, Brian. At work.
Oh, my God.
Am I getting fired?
What?
No.
We were just talking
about babies,
and it got me thinking--
About my time management
skills?
Katrina, don't lie to me.
I've heard the rumors.
Am I one of the ones
being let go from the merger?
You heard right, Brian.
We are making some cuts.
But you should know
the decisions were based
on completely objective data.
Completely objective?
I work my ass off
for this firm.
Well, your numbers certainly
don't show that.
- My numbers?
- Yes, your numbers.
The thing that indicates
how hard you work.
I don't believe this.
You know what, maybe people
were right about you.
What does that mean?
It means they say
you're cold
and all you care about
is your job.
Well, maybe they're right.
Maybe you are a robot.
How dare you say that to me.
How dare I say that to you?
I've been showing you pictures
of my child
and the whole time you've just
been waiting to fire me.
What kind of person
would do that?
You know what,
the kind of person
who's been trying to figure out
how to save your job.
But I haven't heard one thing
that I can use
to justify keeping you.
So as far as I'm concerned,
you're fired.
Louis,
Can I talk to you for second?
Course, what do you need?
I have something I want
to run by you.
I need to know if you think
it'll work.
What's going on?
Harvey's trying
to get Zane's client
to drop their division,
not ours.
And Zane's doing
the same thing.
Let me guess,
you're on team Harvey.
- Exactly.
- What's your plan?
Well?
I love it.
You don't think there's an
end around for her
with an injunction?
- The only way she could do
that if she filed
an ex-parte motion.
Which she can't do
retroactively.
Alex, this is brilliant.
Do you need help filing it?
- No, Louis. I already did.
I was checking to make sure
I didn't miss anything.
Hey, Alex.
Harvey told me that you thought
I was still mad at you
because I didn't come
to you about Zane.
That's not true.
As far as I'm concerned,
you are on our side.
You always will be.
When the time comes,
I'll back you as name partner.
I appreciate that, Louis.
Go get 'em.
Hey, Brian, I was just
about to come--
- See me? Bullshit.
- What do you mean bullshit?
I mean there's no way you
were gonna come see me
because you didn't even
have the balls
to fire me
to my face.
What?
Brian, nobody's firing you.
You're gonna look me
in the eye
and tell me that Katrina
didn't run her numbers
and determine that I don't work
hard enough to serve this firm?
- No, that's not--
- You know what?
If you'd at least come
and told me yourself,
but why should I expect
something like that?
After all, it's not like you
ever held my newborn son.
Brian, please wait.
I told Katrina to find
a way to keep you
because I believe
that you
are more than worthy
of serving this firm.
And I do care about you
and that is the truth.
Yeah, well, maybe you did
tell her all that,
but it didn't stop her
from firing me anyway.
- Brian--
- You know what, Louis?
If you need me, I'll be
spending the next two days
getting my files in order.
Because contrary
to Katrina's analysis,
I care about my clients,
and I'm a damn good lawyer.
Louis, before you say--
What the fuck is
your problem?
I gave you an order
and you blatantly ignored me.
I didn't ignore you.
Then what do
you call firing Brian
when I specifically
told you not to?
Listen to me,
I tried not to fire him.
I took him to lunch, and we--
- Oh, good, lunch.
I hope the chicken potpie
was delicious.
You still didn't do
what I asked.
You know what?
I did do what
you originally asked.
To objectively evaluate
the associates.
Not coddle your teacher's pet.
Screw what
I originally asked.
I told you to rejigger
the metrics
to keep a valued associate.
You think fudging the numbers
wasn't the first thing I tried?
It didn't work.
He always came out too low.
- I don't care.
Well, I do.
Because I care about this firm.
And what kind of message does
rejiggering the metrics
send to the associates
who work 100 hours a week,
who eat dinner here every
night,
who don't even go on dates,
let alone have a baby.
I don't care what message
it sends, Katrina.
Brian is staying.
Then you figure out
who goes instead.
Because I'm not doing something
I don't believe in.
No, Katrina. I told you once
and I'm telling you again.
You asked for this job;
you are doing it.
Harvey.
You need to take
a look at this.
- What is it?
- It just came in.
It's a proposed contract
of sale for Clavatin's--
Manufacturing division.
Son of a bitch.
I need to find out where
Judge Thomas is and I
need to find out now.
Harvey, you can't do this
without Alex. It's his case.
Then why the hell are you
the one telling me this
and not him?
Because he's probably out
there fighting
because he thinks
he can still win.
Well,
he's got one thing right.
We can still win.
But he can't.
And if you cut him out,
you won't win either.
You think I can't take
Samantha Wheeler?
I think you said
you'd stay out of it.
And if you take over now
without even telling Alex,
then you can find out where
Judge Thomas is yourself.
Because I'm not gonna help you
tell your own team
that you'll cut them
out just to get
the better of Samantha Wheeler.
Look, you want
to tell Alex what I'm doing?
Go ahead. I am not
about to sit on the sidelines
and watch us lose.
Harvey.
I'm only gonna ask
you this once.
Is there a chance you're
that overreacting
to Mike having just left?
I don't know, Donna.
But to tell you the truth,
I don't care.
Okay.
You win.
I'll find out
where Judge Thomas is.
Heavy is the head.
Especially when what has
to be done is unjust.
You still don't
think that Brian
deserves to stay, do you?
No, I don't.
And when I told Louis
that it would send
the wrong kind of message
to the people who work
their asses off for this firm
a lot more than Brian,
he said he didn't give a shit.
I see.
And what Louis
didn't understand was
that the people you're talking
about weren't just people.
It was you.
- How could you--
Because I know what
it's like to give everything
and still be taken for granted.
And for what it's worth,
I think Louis
was wrong to say what he did.
But he isn't wrong about Brian.
- Well, I don't agree.
- I understand that.
Probably has something to do
with why you told Harvey
that I shouldn't
be made partner last year.
- You knew about that?
- I do now.
- Donna, it wasn't--
- Tell me.
You ran all the numbers
for Louis,
who are the top five most
efficient associates?
Jesse, Sarah, Ryan, Carl,
and Gina.
- Where does Brian sit?
- Right here.
Right here in the center of
those five people?
Do you think
that's a coincidence?
- I had--
- Katrina.
What you have yet to learn
is that there are players
who never put up great stats,
but you keep them
around because they make
the people around them better.
Are you talking about Brian
or you?
I'm talking about both.
So what do I do?
You do what
you said you'd do.
You evaluate the associates.
Only this time, do it better.
I'm sorry, Donna.
I shouldn't have gone
to Harvey.
It's okay, Katrina.
COO is where I'm meant to be.
- Harvey.
- Alex,
before you say anything--
- No, you gave me your word
that you were gonna
stay out of this.
The next thing I know,
you're having a meeting
about my client without me.
- First of all, it's my client.
- And it's my case.
Which you were about to lose.
- It was a setback.
- Bullshit.
You were getting
your ass kicked.
And don't tell me you weren't.
- God damn it, Harvey.
Listen to me, Alex.
This woman is no joke.
You saying I am?
I'm saying I just met with
Judge Thomas,
so I know exactly what
it's gonna take to beat her.
So the hell what? I can play
dirty just as well as you.
Maybe you can,
but I gave you a promise
to put your name on the wall.
And if you play dirty to beat
Robert Zane's right hand,
it isn't gonna happen.
- You know what I think?
That sounds like some bullshit
by a guy
who's just gonna do what
he wants like he always does.
What I want, Alex,
is to stay managing partner.
This is the way
that's gonna happen.
- Harvey, I--
- That's enough.
I'm taking it from here.
It's done.
Katrina, I've got a lot
on my plate this morning.
So if you don't mind--
You just want your morning
coffee, I know.
Was that part of
your efficiency evaluations?
People's coffee consumption?
Look, Brian,
I was wrong about you.
I understand what you do
for the firm
and I'm sorry for
the things I said.
Well, I appreciate that,
but if you're just saying this
because Louis told you to--
- No, I'm not.
And he didn't.
Then why are you saying it?
Because I took
this assignment hoping
that it would help me grow.
And if I can't ask for help
when I need it,
then I have even more growing
to do than I thought.
What do you mean ask
for help?
My evaluation
of the associates was flawed.
It didn't take into
account intangibles, and...
I was hoping you could help
me fix that.
You mean you want me
to help you figure out
who to fire instead of me.
No, Brian,
that's not what I meant.
Yes, it is.
And I'm sure firing
my fellow associates is
a value to the firm,
but I'm not gonna help you
do it.
- What the hell did you do?
- I didn't do anything.
Well, except for
the thing that I did.
You mean going
to Judge Thomas
and having him allow
fabricated testimony
to overrule my motion.
It wasn't fabricated, but
it sure as hell was allowed.
And how exactly did you get
him to do that?
You know how I did it,
or you don't.
And if you don't,
well, I'm not about
to open up my playbook
and show you.
Well, Mr. Slick,
I don't give a shit
how you did it.
I'm going to undo it
because this is isn't over.
- Yes, it is.
- We'll see about that.
No, we won't.
Because I'm giving you
a direct order.
You are not to take
any action
to affect the outcome
of this situation.
And you can give me all
the orders you want.
The only person I answer to
is Robert Zane.
So if you want to stop
what I'm about to do,
you better talk to him
before I god damn do it.
- Don't you walk away from me.
- Kiss my ass.
All right, Robert.
I have been patient,
but it's over,
and I've won.
Call off the dogs.
What the hell
did you just say to me?
I said call off the dogs.
I'm not gonna have someone
inside my own firm who
doesn't know when she's lost.
The only one in here
who doesn't know
that they've lost is you.
I didn't lose shit.
And if you think I might,
why don't you pick up the phone
and call
Judge Thomas right now?
I'm not talking about
Judge Thomas.
Then what the hell
are you talking about?
I'm talking about the fact
that you stood right here
and gave your word
that you would stay
out of this thing.
And not only did you break it,
now you're in here trying
to drag me into it.
Nothing to say?
That's right.
You may have won the battle,
but you lost the goddamn war.
Because you just showed
this entire firm
only one of us is
managing partner material.
And it isn't you.
This is my firm,
and I'm not gonna
let you take it.
I'm gonna let you in
on a little secret, Harvey.
I already have.
Now, why don't you let
that rattle around
for a little while,
and then come back
when you're ready
to tell me that I'm right.
You can come in, you know.
- Sorry, I didn't mean to--
- Yes, you did.
You just wanted
to let me finish
whatever I was
in the middle of.
Not bad.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
No, I mean, thanks
for sticking up
for me with Katrina.
- You figured it out.
- I did.
I was right about you.
Aren't you right
about everybody?
Yeah, pretty much.
And now I have something else
to be right about.
Katrina needs your help.
Maybe she does,
but if I'd thought
about the fact
that me staying would mean
someone I care about might
get fired...
I wouldn't have gone to Louis
in the first place.
And that, right there,
is the reason we were right
to keep you.
And as I see it...
You can either help Katrina
make the right decision,
or live with the fact that
she might make the wrong one.
Like she almost did with you.
Harvey,
what can I do for you?
I'll tell you what
you should have done for me.
Stop me from taking
the case from Alex.
And if you recall,
that's what I tried to do.
And then
you changed your mind.
Because I listened to you.
Oh, well,
you picked a hell of a time
to start doing that
because Zane set me up.
I don't care what Zane did,
you went after her
because it's who you are.
And you're supposed to be
saving me from myself.
Which is exactly what I did.
How the hell
do you figure that?
Harvey, Mike left.
What does that have to do
with this?
It has everything
to do with is.
Because the reason
he left is because
he finally came to terms
with who he is.
And now that he's gone,
who you are is a man
who wants back in the game.
Don't you see, you've been
to the top of the mountain.
You've proved you can
do it, and you may not
want to admit it, but...
you're getting tired
of just sitting up there,
enjoying the view.
Donna,
how's it gonna look
to the rest of the world
if I step down?
I'll tell you how.
Like no other firm
can touch us.
Not with you and Robert
doing what everybody knows
you were meant to do.
And by that...
I mean pulling off
the kind of shit
that only Harvey Specter
can do.
Katrina.
You wanted to see me?
- Yes.
Bridget, please sit down.
Am I getting fired?
Yes.
I'm afraid you are.
Katrina,
I know we merged,
but I have
a ton of student debt.
My landlord just raised my
rent, and...
I promised to pay for
my nephew's daycare
so my sister could go back
to school.
Please.
There's got
to be something I can do
to get a second chance.
I'm sorry,
Bridget,
but the decision's
already been made.
I do wish you the best of luck.
You know, life was simpler
when this was my office.
As I understand,
when you were in this office
you almost went to
prison for Mike Ross.
I don't see what
was simpler about that.
Yeah, you do.
Robert, you said
that I should come back
when I was ready to admit
that you were right.
Well, I'm back.
Takes a big man
to admit that, Harvey.
I appreciate it.
You're not gonna try
to hug me, are you?
I don't know what goes on
between you and Louis,
but I'll pass.
Then I guess this is
the part where I make
my first humble request
to my fearless leader.
That took about two seconds.
Let's hear it.
My office.
- What about it?
- I want it back.
In that case,
your fearless leader
is happy to comply.
What do you say we go out
and grab those burgers?
Not tonight, but we will.
I still have something I have
to take care of.
- You were right.
- About what?
It wasn't easy firing
those people.
- So it's done?
- It's done.
You mind if I ask
if Brian ended up
helping with this list?
He did.
And you were right
about him too.
Well, as long as we're
handing out "You were rights,"
You were right about being
the one to let those people go.
You mean it's good for
my growth.
No, I mean, I'm glad I didn't
have to do it. It sucks.
Hey, you want to grab
a drink or something?
- I'd love to.
- Katrina.
Robert.
Give me a second with
Red here, will you?
Of course.
I'll be in my office.
Am I in trouble?
Why,
you do something wrong?
I guess that depends on what
you mean by wrong.
I'm not here
because you're in trouble.
I'm here because Harvey
just asked me to swap offices
and then he told I was right.
And I doubt those words
have ever come out
of that man's mouth
without first having
a conversation with you.
You sound pretty sure
of yourself for a man
who's only been here
about ten minutes.
You think Rachel
didn't tell her father
about the mighty Donna Paulsen?
Guess I never thought of her
as much of a chatterbox.
Then again, she did tell me
about the time that you took--
Whatever it is.
Just remember,
once you say it out loud,
we can never pretend
that you don't know it.
And that,
Robert Lucas Zane,
is why
you are managing partner.
- Good night, Donna.
- Good night, Robert.
You really have no concept
of boundaries, do you?
You know,
most people would be here
to tell you they think
we got off on the wrong foot.
But I'm here to say
we got off on the right one,
And what foot is that?
The one where you
and I discover
we're not
so different after all.
I don't think
I'm anything like you.
You are.
Right down to the fact
that we both grew up in
Riverside, New York.
Which is why we'll both
always feel like outsiders
no matter how much we earn
their respect.
How do you know
that about me?
Because I do my homework.
Maybe we are alike.
That's all I wanted to say.
Except for one thing.
You told Jeremy Stiller
that you grew up on a farm,
and last I checked there aren't
any farms in Riverside.
And that little observation
is the reason
we got off on the right foot.
I don't follow.
There are three things
that happen
when I tell different people
different stories.
One, they don't recognize it.
Which means I don't need
to worry about them.
Two,
they know I did it,
but don't have the balls
to say anything.
Which means I need to worry
about them even less.
Or three, they call me on it.
And believe me,
three is my kind of guy.
Well, in that case,
welcome to the firm.
Glad to be here.
Oh, and by the way,
I would have won.
Alex.
It's 10:00 at night;
what are you doing?
I'm going through every one
of Samantha Wheeler's files.
'Cause a fight's coming,
and I'm gonna be ready.
Okay, listen to me.
Because, believe me,
I've been where you are before.
Don't start something
that you'll regret later.
Then what am
I supposed to do?
How 'bout you make
a friend now
that you'll be
happy about later.
Are you crazy? She's not
looking to make friends.
Maybe not, but, Alex,
listen to me.
In the long run,
this woman is going nowhere.
Got Harvey and me on your side.
You get the trifecta,
I don't care what she does.
Never gonna beat you again.
Are you suggesting I kiss
Robert Zane's ass?
'Cause I'm not gonna do that.
- No, Alex.
I'm just saying
get to know the man.
And how exactly would you
suggest I do that?
That's up to you.
I happen to know
the man plays golf.
So do you.
If it were up to me,
I would start right there.
Make yourself at home.
Don't mind if I do.
Well, as long as you're here.
You came through,
like always.
Thanks, Samantha.
- Like always.
What happened to, "You let me
down a time or two"?
Come on, you know I get like
that sometimes.
What's going on?
Something on your mind?
Yeah, there is.
I did what you asked and
now I have something to ask.
- What's that?
I don't want to just be
your Michael Clayton.
I want more.
- I'm married.
- Come on, Robert.
You know what I want,
and it's time.
Samantha,
we've been over this.
You get name partner, and
you're not going to be able
to operate the way
you always have.
You mean I won't be able
to clean up your messes.
My messes aren't
the only ones you clean up.
I believe you spend half
the time cleaning up your own.
Oh, is that what I spent
the last few days doing?
- Samantha?
- Robert, I want name partner.
And I want it before
the year is out.
Or what?
Before the year is out,
Robert.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
www.tvsubtitles.net