Previously, on "Suits..."
I want to talk to you
about doing more pro bonos.
If you want to take on a pro
Bono, knock yourself out.
What is a COO of a law firm
doing handing out pro bonos
in the first place?
- I just thought that it...
- Rhetorical question, Donna.
I don't care what you thought.
I need you to supervise
Brian Altman.
- Have someone else manage him.
- Damn it, Katrina.
This is your chance
to be senior partner.
I was just thinking about
where we were a week ago
when I thought you were
cold and heartless.
And I went from that
to being your best friend.
I wouldn't say best friend.
You want to know something
about me?
You go ahead and ask.
And how should I trust that
I'd get a straight answer?
Because I am
on this team now.
I've got its
best interests at heart.
- I'm getting a divorce.
- What?
I was hoping
that you could represent me.
It's my brother;
what am I supposed to do?
I think that this could bring
up a lot of shit for you.
He still loves you.
He deserves another chance
as a father.
It was one of the hardest
things I've ever had to do.
I swear
it took a piece of me, Donna.
You could look at it
like you chose to give
a piece of yourself.
Alex.
Can I talk to you
about something?
Sure, Donna,
what's going on?
Well, ever since I got
promoted
I've been looking for
a way to give back.
And it turns out
that a friend of mine
is working for a charity
that helps at-risk girls.
And I figured the best way for
me to give some of my time...
Would be to convince some
lawyers to give some of theirs.
Exactly.
Donna, I'd love to say yes,
but I'm slammed right now.
and a charity
like this deserves
more time than I can offer.
I appreciate you
hearing me out.
I'll find somebody else.
Donna, I have to ask.
Given how it went
the last time you took on
a pro Bono,
have you cleared this
with Robert?
I'd hate to see him bite
your head off a second time.
Trust me, Alex, I don't make
the same mistake twice.
Robert's good with it.
Then I hope you find someone
to handle it for you.
Louis, what can I do for you?
Not me. I'm here about what
you can do for Emmet Ford.
You mean the owner
of the hottest online retailer
in the world.
Yes I do. He wants to
go public; there's a problem;
and you need to drop
everything you're doing.
Louis, I can't right now.
I'm up to
my eyeballs in the
Ratchinson brief.
Then give it to someone else.
This is too important.
Well,
if it's so important,
why don't you
handle it yourself?
I can't.
Louis, what's going on?
Katrina, you need this
to make senior partner.
What? I thought
I had to show Robert
I could manage people
to make senior partner,
which I did.
It's not Robert.
Every partner gets a vote.
And Paul goddamn Porter wants...
Don't tell me.
That douchebag Hanrahan.
Yes.
Katrina, look,
I know I let you down,
and I'm sorry.
But you bring this home,
I promise
you will be senior partner
next quarter.
Okay, Louis.
I'll take care of it.
Good.
Now I have to go deliver
some more shitty news
to someone who's gonna be
less understanding than you.
I get it. You're going
through with the divorce,
but I don't see why you can't...
No, I'm not okay with it,
Marcus,
but I guess I have to be.
Look, I got to go.
Bye.
Louis, whatever it is,
does it have to be now?
I wish it didn't, Harvey,
but I got a call from
Dominic Barone a week ago.
Aston Martin put in offer
to acquire McKernon Motors.
And I assume
you're here to ask
where they should shove
that offer because...
I'm here to tell you
Dominic's taking it.
Louis,
if McKernon is acquired...
Dominic won't be
our client anymore. I know.
Undo it. Nevermind.
I'll call him myself.
Harvey, it is what he wants.
Bullshit, he doesn't know
what he wants.
Yes, he does.
And he's my client now.
It's a done deal,
and I need you to accept
what he wants,
even if it means losing him.
Louis.
I've been looking for you.
Joan Walsh is here.
Wait, what?
She's not on my schedule.
I know.
She says it's an emergency.
Well, I'm sorry I don't have
time for her right now, Donna.
- Why the hell not?
- Because...
I have an appointment
on my other schedule.
What's that supposed to mean?
It means I need to see Sheila
right now, okay?
And you know why.
Let me get this straight.
You're leaving the office
when a client has an emergency
so you can fool around
with your girlfriend.
- Harvey.
- Yes, I am.
And I know this isn't
the best time to ask,
but she is an old client
of yours.
So if you can
please take the meeting,
I will handle whatever it is
when I get back.
Sure, Louis,
you go ahead and enjoy
your afternoon delight.
I'll just be here letting
Dominic sell his company
and babysitting Joan Walsh
while you're gone.
Harvey. What are you
doing here? I was...
Expecting Louis?
Well,
he's not available right now,
but I hear you have
an emergency, Joan.
So why don't you read me in.
A model named Daisy Jones
posted a video claiming
my concealer gave her
an allergic reaction.
Sales on my new line
are tanking.
All right,
I'll take care of it.
Where is she based?
New York or Miami?
- Cleveland.
- I'm sorry?
She's not your typical model,
Harvey.
She's a digital influencer.
All right, well,
who is she managed by?
Her mother, last I checked.
Joan, how old is this person?
16.
Then,
with all due respect,
send her a gift basket
and be done with it.
Harvey, you don't get it.
This girl has
50 million followers.
We need to sue her
into the ground before
she tanks my whole company.
We also need to be
conscious of your image,
and suing a 16-year-old
isn't a pretty picture.
It's not the picture
I'm worried about, Harvey.
It's that video.
So are you going to find
a way to get it down,
or do I need to find
another firm who can?
♪ Suits 8x06 ♪
Cats Ballet Harvey Specter
Original Air Date on August 2
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ I'll even eat a bean pie,
I don't mind ♪
♪ Me and Missy is so busy,
busy making money ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ All step back,
I'm 'bout to dance ♪
== sync by elderman ==
@elder_man
♪ The greenback boogie ♪
Good morning, Donna.
Samantha.
What can I do for you today?
Actually,
I thought there might be
something I can do for you.
I heard you're looking
for representation
for your charity.
Oh, that's nice
of you to offer,
but I know how much
Robert leans on you,
and I don't think
he's gonna be okay
with me doing it
if it means you doing it.
Why do I get the feeling
that even if you would be
okay with me doing this
you aren't?
Okay.
Do you want the truth?
I don't think
you're the person for this.
Because you still
don't trust me.
Because you haven't
shown me I can.
Okay, have it your way.
I'm sure Alex
will knock it out of the park.
Oh wait,
he's too busy.
You could always try
one of those junior partners.
Of course, they're all
too afraid of Robert
to spend billable
hours on a pro Bono.
- Are you done?
- I don't know. Am I?
Not until you tell me why
you want this so much.
Well, if I told you
it's because I care
about the work this charity
does you'd never believe me.
So why don't we just say
it's because
a little birdie asked me to.
Okay, Samantha.
I'll send you their files.
Brian, there you are.
I need your help
with something.
Sure, what is it?
Emmet Ford hit a roadblock
getting listed on
the stock exchange
and we need to blow
that roadblock away.
Whoa, whoa, Katrina,
whatever this is,
you can handle this yourself.
Why are you coming
to me with it?
Three reasons.
One, you have more
stock exchange experience
than I do.
Two, I want a show of force.
And three?
Let's just say
Donna once said
that you make everyone
around you better.
And I need to be
at my best on this case.
- Then I accept.
- Then read up.
We're meeting them in an hour.
Donna, just the person
I was about to come see.
- Oh, is that a fact?
- You seem perturbed.
I am.
Because Samantha just asked
to represent my charity
and there's no way
she would have done that
if she hadn't
heard about it from you.
Donna,
you two got off on
the wrong foot,
and I know for a fact
she wants to fix it.
And how do you know that?
Because when
I came to her with this
She said it'll kill two birds
with one stone,
and one of those birds
was making good with you.
Well, I still wish
you hadn't gone to her at all.
Does that mean
I should tear up this check?
This is a donation
for $5 million.
That Samantha insisted I get
before she took on
your charity.
Donna,
she's serious about this.
Okay, Alex,
I'll give her a chance.
Thank you for this check.
Mr. Ford,
I'm Katrina Bennett.
This is Brian Altman.
It's nice to meet you both.
We've read up on
your situation,
but we want to hear it
directly from you.
Okay, here it is.
I've spent the last six months
trying to drum up interest
in our IPO.
And then at the eleventh hour,
the stock exchange
pulls a rug out from under me.
- Why would they do that?
- Ask Marc Aiken.
The Chairman of the board?
Yeah.
The jackass has
had it in for me
ever since we worked together
at Goldman.
The board said
they pulled support
because of concern over
our site's content,
but I know damn well...
It's just a pretext
for Marc to screw you over.
Exactly.
If I don't get
this infusion of capital,
I am dead in the water.
Then all we need
to do is show
this is bad faith
and you're in.
And that shouldn't
be too hard.
All we need
are those board minutes.
I tried that myself already;
they're sealed.
- Then we need to unseal them.
- How?
By getting it on record
that Marc Aiken
hates your guts.
All right,
I understand we're here
because of a few blackheads.
So what's it gonna take
to get that video down?
My client's complexion
is her livelihood, Mr. Specter.
Not only did this incident
harm her brand,
it brought her
emotional anguish.
It was so bad I couldn't post
a video for a week.
Except the one defaming
my client.
Well, I had to show people
what it did to my face.
It was shaming.
Which is why in addition
to the video staying up
we've prepared this.
Listen to me,
if every 16-year-old girl
filed suit every time
she wasn't happy with
what she saw in the mirror,
our legal system would
grind to a halt.
I'm not every
16-year-old girl, Mr. Specter.
And you want me to take down
that video and not file this?
I want $10 million.
I see.
So this is a shakedown?
This is a legitimate claim,
and your wisest
course of action
would be to write that check.
My course of action
is gonna be
to hit you with
a defamation suit
because you have no proof
our product caused
your break outs.
And I don't think
you understand
that I have
50 million followers
who will do anything
I tell them to.
So even if that video
comes down,
I can tell them not
to use your client anyway.
That's it.
I don't care how old you are.
You know what you're doing.
You deserve
what's coming for you,
and this meeting's over.
- Okay, Harvey.
- Okay, what?
Okay.
Why don't you make your jokes
about me and Sheila
procreating so we can get
to you filling me in
on Joan's emergency.
I don't need to fill you in,
Louis.
I got it from here.
No, you don't have anything.
You were just supposed
to babysit her.
That's the thing about
actually being at work, Louis.
Situations change
and you make adjustments.
This isn't a situation.
This is you taking my client.
And you were the one okay
with clients leaving
if that's what they wanted.
So that's what this is about.
Your mad because I let Dominic
do what was best for him.
No, this is about
you left the office
to get
your girlfriend knocked up.
I started working a case,
and I'm gonna finish it.
Don't you bring
Sheila into this.
I didn't, Louis.
You did.
Now, you listen to me closely
'cause I'm not
gonna say this again.
Your services are no longer
needed on this case.
Mr. Aiken, exactly how do you
feel about Emmet Ford?
- Ambivalent.
- Ambivalent?
You worked together
for seven years.
Asked and answered.
Where is this going?
It's going to the fact
that your client
deliberately tried to sabotage
Emmet Ford's IPO
because he doesn't like him.
That's bullshit.
Really,
then why did you punch him?
- What?
- Why would you throw
a punch at someone
if you like them?
I didn't say I like him,
and that incident
happened on
the trading floor at Goldman.
Throwing punches
was considered friendly.
I got to tell you, Marc,
it doesn't sound friendly.
I don't care
what it sounds like.
Then let me tell you
how it looks.
You had a fight;
you held a grudge;
and when you got
the chance to screw over
a man you hate,
you took it.
I didn't screw him over.
But you do hate him,
don't you?
Okay, you know what?
I can't stand him.
I think he's a sanctimonious
son of a bitch
and if I never seem him again,
it'll be too soon,
but I did not
keep him off that exchange.
Then if you're not going
to tell us the truth
about that,
the board minutes will.
You have no right
to those minutes.
We do, now that he's
admitted personal bias.
So either we can subpoena
those minutes
and show this tape
in open court,
or you can turn them
over today.
But you better decide fast
because I've already drafted
that subpoena.
You'll have them
by the end of the day.
And then I said,
"It's not the same."
And then he said,
"Well, you're the one
who's okay with clients
with leaving."
And then he brought up Sheila,
and then I got really mad,
and then I got really sad
and called you.
Now fix it.
Louis, customarily
I find your frustrations
with Harvey to be entirely
of your own making,
but in this instance,
it sounds like Harvey
may be the one in the wrong.
Holy shit,
I need to go out
and buy a lotto ticket
right now.
Louis,
stay with me.
You two have known each other
a long time.
You've had your ups and downs.
Yeah, I know, it's like
we're almost in a relationship.
Not almost,
it is a relationship.
Oh, my God.
I'm in a relationship
with Harvey.
Can I be the boy?
Oh, scratch that,
I don't even give a shit.
I'm in a relationship
with Harvey.
And would you like to work
on that relationship?
Or spend the rest
of the session
celebrating its existence.
I think we both know
the answer to that,
but I'll settle
for working on it.
In that case...
what would Harvey say
if you were to ask
him why he is so upset?
I don't know.
He's Harvey.
He'd say, "I'm right.
You're wrong."
Touch his hair and leave.
Louis.
If you cannot see him
as human being,
I cannot help you.
- What if I brought him in?
- Excuse me?
You do couple's counseling.
What if I brought him in
to work on our relationship?
That is not exactly
what I meant...
- You just said we're a couple.
- I didn't say that.
Well, then what did you say?
Because I don't know
what he's feeling,
but I do know
that we need help.
Okay, Louis.
If you can bring him in,
I'll help.
Did you finish reading
the minutes?
Yes. I read them twice
to make sure
I wasn't missing anything.
Well, you didn't.
All these show
is hours of Aiken lobbying
to keep Emmet's business
and everyone else lobbying
against him.
I know. He set us up.
So we'd spend half
the day wasting our time
while the clock on
that IPO is ticking.
Now I have to stay here
all night because
we're running out of time,
and I'm not losing this case.
Then I just have
one question.
Indian or Chinese?
Because if you're staying here
all night, I am too.
Indian.
Thanks, Brian.
Don't you look nice.
We doing costume changes in
the middle of the day now?
Okay, first of all,
it is not
the middle of the day,
and, second,
I'm going to a gala
for the charity
that you said
you didn't have time for.
Well, if I'd known you
were gonna dress like that,
I'd have made time.
And if had known
that a married man
was going to hit on me
at work, I would have
served him with papers.
Come on, baby,
don't be like that.
Seriously, Donna, I'm glad it
worked out with Samantha.
Thanks, Alex.
I'm glad it did too.
Brian, I don't know
where you found this place,
but this is the best masala
I've had since college.
I just realized
this is, like, our third dinner
we've had together,
and I don't even know
where you went to college.
Well, if you must know,
I went to Princeton,
but before you can ask about
my major, I couldn't Dec...
Holy shit, Princeton.
Brian, it's not
that big a deal.
Everybody here went
to Harvard Law...
I'm not talking about that.
I'm talking about Tony Gold.
Who's Tony Gold?
He was my rival on
the debate team in high school.
He knew Princeton was my dream
and that my parents couldn't
afford to send me
to the interview in person.
So Tony offered
to let me ride up
with his family
as an olive branch.
- How'd the interview go?
- He never picked me up.
Princeton thought I'd bailed;
he got in; I didn't.
Brian, that's horrible.
It is, but Tony came up
with a bullshit story
about why they never showed,
and I believed him.
Until his little brother
told me the truth
a few months later.
What are you saying?
I'm saying Tony couldn't
keep it to himself.
Because when you do something
like that...
You have to tell someone.
Which means all we need
to do is find
Marc Aiken's little brother.
You got a little masala
on your...
Other side.
Your... here.
Let me get it.
What?
I just made it
1,000 times worse.
You look like Ronald McDonald.
I thought you do this with
your son, like, every day.
Well, I haven't had
to do it with him in months
because his food is the train,
and he keeps it in the station.
- Ha ha, give me that napkin.
- No.
Not till after
I take a picture.
No, you are not taking
a picture of me.
Well, maybe you should
have thought of that
before you let me wipe sauce
all over your face.
All right, I'll get it off.
I don't think we should eat
anymore masala.
Donna, I cannot thank you
enough for your donation.
You're already making such
a difference.
Oh, please, Peggy,
you're the ones
making the real difference.
I'm just happy
I could help you do it.
Will you excuse me
for a minute?
Sure.
- Samantha.
- Donna.
I have to say I didn't expect
to see you here.
I didn't expect to be here.
Did you come to show me how
good you look all dressed up?
What if I came to see how
Miss Wheeler,
are you flirting with me?
And how would
that make you feel if I was?
Are you kidding?
I went to theater camp.
Hm.
But I would still like
to know why you're here.
I mean, you don't strike me
as the kind of person
who would come to an event like
this unless she had to.
I wouldn't,
but if I'm gonna represent
these people,
I need to know
what they do
and how they do it.
While we're on
the subject of working,
I got that check from Alex.
Is that your way of saying
you're good with me doing this?
It is, but it's not just
because of the money.
You're here showing interest.
That's just the kind
of representation
this place needs.
Well, in that case, maybe
we should hit up the food.
I may not have come
for the shrimp cocktail,
but I'm gonna eat the shit
out of some.
I've already had
16 oysters myself.
17th won't hurt anybody.
I don't know about you,
but not all the cocktails I
had last night were shrimp.
Thank you, Donna.
You didn't have to.
Just like you didn't have
to take on this charity.
But I got the impression
from Alex that he saw
a side of you that I hadn't,
and last night I think
I started to see it too.
Well, as long as
we're talking about last night,
I may have found
something wrong.
What do you mean?
I mean, charities typically
spend 5% of their budget
on fundraising,
but based on the disclosures
I got from your friend, Peggy,
they've been at 5.3%
for the last five years.
Sound like
a simple rounding error.
Donna.
I have a nose for
this kind of thing,
and I think Peggy
is up to something shady.
And the problem
with people who fix things
is they can't stop looking
for problems to fix.
You think I'm making this up?
I think you're making .3%
into more than it is.
And I think the devil
is in the details,
and I am telling you
this detail is trouble.
Okay.
If you're so sure,
I'll talk to Peggy.
Maybe I should be the one...
Samantha,
if my friend has been
lying to me,
I'm not gonna ignore it.
I'm gonna turn on
my spidey senses,
and I'm gonna find out
if you're right,
and what I want you to do
is not try to fix
this in the meantime.
Okay.
Let me know what you find.
Harvey,
we need to talk
because our relationship
needs tending.
Our what needs what?
You heard me.
We're in a relationship,
and it's not working.
Then break up with me
and go out with somebody else
'cause I'm busy.
Harvey, I am serious.
We're partners.
We need to work on
our relationship,
and we need help doing it.
Louis, what exactly
are you getting at?
- Dr. Lipschitz.
- Your therapist?
- Yeah, and he agreed...
- No.
- But...
- Louis, there's no way
I'm going to a session
with your therapist.
Actually it would be
for the both of us.
Are you fucking kidding me?
That's the dumbest thing
I've ever heard.
Well,
he thinks it's a good idea.
Which just goes to show
that he's an idiot,
and so are you.
Don't turn this on me
and don't talk about him
that way.
What's going on here?
Harvey won't go to
couple's counseling with me.
- What?
- Exactly.
No, not exactly.
Because you took my client;
you're upset about Dominic;
you insulted me, my therapist,
and the woman I love.
And none of that
would have happened
if you put the needs
of this firm
over your afternoon delight.
And here we go again.
Louis,
will you give us a minute?
Donna, I don't want
to talk about this.
Too bad,
because I heard the way
you spoke to Louis before
and just now,
and there's clearly
stuff going on with you
that you're not dealing with.
Probably has something
to do with
what you just went through
with Marcus.
This has nothing to do
with him getting a divorce.
He's what?
He called.
They're not gonna try
to work it out.
Well, I don't care
if you go see Lipschitz
or someone else, but you need
to deal with yourself.
And stop treating Louis
like you used to
because he's not
that man anymore.
And I thought you were neither.
- Okay, thanks for your time.
- Anything?
Nothing.
That was the 15th person
I've called
that knows Marc Aiken,
and no one says
they're anything more
than an acquaintance.
That tracks with
what Emmet told me.
The man has no friends,
no family,
just a bunch of associates
who can barely stand him.
The guy I just talked to
said he's got
a standing tee time
at Quaker Ridge
for the sole purpose of
advancing his career.
I bet it works.
My father would tolerate
anyone to play there.
- Your dad's a golfer?
- Yeah. I am too, actually.
Huh, I had no idea.
Well, I don't get to play
as much as I'd like.
Wait a second.
What?
If he has
a standing tee time,
he has a standing caddy.
And a caddy might not
be someone he confides in,
but if all he ever talks
about is business...
We need to get
to Quaker Ridge.
Let's go.
You go.
We're running out of time,
and if you get something,
we're going to need a complaint
ready to file with the SCC.
Oh, Harvey,
if you are here to tell me
that you think
another of my ideas is stupid...
I'm not here
to tell you that, Louis.
I'm here to say I'll go see
Lipschitz with you.
Do you really mean that,
or is this gonna be
like the time that you said
you would take me to dinner
for my 35th birthday
,and you never showed up.
It's not gonna be
like that time.
- And what about the time...
- Not that time either.
I'll show up for this.
I promise.
And that's exactly what you
said the time...
Louis, if you mention
one more time,
it will be like
all those times.
Then I want you to know
that I really appreciate
you doing this, Harvey.
And to save time
when we get there,
you should know that I sit
on the left-hand side
of the couch.
Fine.
And I probably don't need
to tell you this,
but you don't have
to bring your own tissues.
Why would I bring
my own tissues?
Because we're gonna be doing
some deep work, Harvey.
So if you need to have
a good cry,
I just want you to know
that you're safe,
and I will not judge you.
See you there, Louis.
Wait, do you think
we should hug now
to set the tone
or do it after...
okay, we'll do it after.
Good call.
Hey, what are you doing?
Don't act like
you don't know, Donna.
I've been fired.
What? How could I know that?
Because it happened after
Samantha Wheeler
called my CEO and put
a stop payment on that check.
Peggy, you have got
to believe me.
I had nothing to do with that.
What difference does it make?
My boss blamed me for
getting us involved with you,
and he fired me.
That's bullshit.
What's bullshit
is that I trusted you.
And now I'm out on my ass.
You can still trust me,
Peggy.
I swear I'm gonna
make this right.
What the hell
is wrong with you?
Donna...
I specifically told you
not to do anything
until you heard from me,
and you said you wouldn't.
I said I'd let you
talk to Peggy, and I did.
After you called up her boss,
put a stop payment on
that check, and got her fired.
I didn't call her boss
to get her fired.
I called because I decided
to trust your judgment.
What is that
supposed to mean?
It means I asked myself,
"What if Donna's right?"
What if the only thing
going on is some vendors
taking advantage of a charity.
So I called up the CEO
and offered a solution.
And he said, "No, thanks,
we like our current situation."
So you ran a stress test
after I told you not to.
I called a client
and made a suggestion.
- Don't bullshit me.
- Okay, fine.
It was a test,
but I'm not gonna let
a client donate $5 million
to anyone without knowing
what's what.
So I killed two birds
with one stone.
Which is exactly
what you said to Alex
and making good with me
was supposed to be
one of those birds.
God damn it, Donna,
why don't you ever seem
to believe me?
Maybe because you never
give anyone the full story.
You want the full story?
They are stealing money
from little girls.
Maybe that doesn't
matter to you,
but it sure as hell
as matters to me.
You don't know
what matters to me.
And there are about
500 different ways
you could have handled this,
and you picked the one
that cost me my friend.
So as far as I'm concerned,
I was right about you
all along.
Now that we've made
our introductions,
I'd like to start with Harvey
describing what he thinks
Louis' perspective
is on the situation.
I don't feel comfortable...
Please, just say the first
thoughts that come to mind.
About how Louis thinks?
Huh.
Let's see...
Cats, ballet, Harvey Specter.
Something like that.
That is not
what I sound like.
All right, Louis.
You wanna know
what you sound like to me?
"I've been jealous
of you since day one.
"You were always Jessica's
favorite and everyone else's.
"You got everything I wanted
without ever trying.
"In fact,
I'm trying to have a baby
"because, I-I-I think it will
take my mind off you
even though I know
deep inside it won't."
Tell him to stop.
He's being honest about
his feelings, Louis.
What about
your feelings about
who's fault
this whole thing was?
- Louis.
- What?
I should have known
you just wanted
to get me in here
to have him tell me
this is my fault.
It is your fault.
Louis, we are not here
to discuss fault.
Well,
then why the hell are we here?
Because he took my client;
he won't give her back;
and he needs to apologize
about what he just said
about me having a baby.
I am not apologizing
about anything.
You wanted me to come here.
You said this was a safe place.
And now you can't handle
what I think about
you trying to have a baby.
Oh, no, you don't get
to make this my fault.
Because it's always my fault,
but I thought this time
we could come here
so you could tell him
that it's his fault,
but if all you're gonna do
is mock me
and all you're gonna do
is coddle him,
well, then you can keep
Joan Walsh;
you can go to hell;
and this whole session is over.
Well,
this was a waste of time.
Maybe so,
but for what it's worth...
I think you have some things
you could work on.
And provided Louis was okay...
I'd be happy to talk
with you any time.
Alex,
I need you to reverse
that stop payment.
What?
I said I need you
to call up that client
and tell them to let
that donation go through.
Well, I'm not gonna do that
because Samantha told me
what's going on.
Samantha doesn't know
what's going on,
and you were wrong
to involve her.
- So this is about me.
- No, this is about the fact
that my friend just got fired.
Well, I'm sorry to hear that,
Donna, but I can't help you.
Then don't help me.
Help the charity.
Because you're taking money
away from people who need it.
Donna,
if I do what you're asking
I might as well tell my clients
they can't trust my advice.
And my advice to you
is get your head on straight.
You're saying I'm not seeing
this clearly.
I'm saying Samantha
specializes in shady shit.
So if she suspects
something's up
you might not believe it,
but I do.
And I'm not cutting
that charity another check.
- Almost done?
- Oh.
Sorry, Katrina.
That's okay.
I take it you were thinking
about something.
To tell you the truth,
I actually came in here
to think.
But I've hogged
this thing long enough.
It's all yours.
As long as you're here,
do you mind
if I ask you a question?
Of course, what is it?
Louis said if I win this case
I'll finally make
senior partner, but...
He's said that before,
and you wanna know
if this time it's true?
I do.
Then the answer is yes.
It is.
Thanks, Donna.
As long as you're here,
do you mind
if I ask you something?
What's going on with
you and Brian?
What?
I noticed when the two of you
were working together
last night you seemed
to have gotten...
closer.
We have.
We've become friends.
Looks like you might be
becoming more than that.
Donna, he's married.
He has a son.
I would never do it.
I know,
but I also know that the heart
doesn't always listen
to what the brain says
it would never do.
Well,
you don't need to worry
because I don't feel anything
for Brian except friendship.
Then good luck with the case.
Copier's all yours.
So what do you want do now,
Stan?
Tell me Drake the Snake
was my fault too?
Louis, I know our session
didn't go as planned,
but I do think there
is still some hope.
So...
I'd like your blessing
to begin seeing Harvey
one on one.
What? Are you fucking kidding me?
You're choosing his side again?
I am not choosing his side,
Louis.
I am trying to help
both of you.
No, you're not,
because anyone who has a choice
between Harvey and me
always chooses him.
You know it's my biggest fear,
and you made it out
like it was all my fault.
No, I didn't,
and I stand by my assessment.
There are aspects
of this situation
that are of Harvey's making.
Well, then why didn't you say
that to him, Stan?
Because, Louis,
when someone is hurting,
you don't throw stones
at them.
What do you mean
Harvey's hurting?
I mean, people lash out
when they are in pain.
He lashed out at you,
and if you care about
your relationship with him,
you will let me do my job.
What if I don't care about
my relationship with him,
and I'd rather keep you
to myself?
Louis, I know
how much you care
about Harvey
even when he hurts you.
That is something I have always
admired about you,
and I do not think you should
take it lightly.
All right,
he can see you,
but he doesn't have
my blessing.
Katrina, I talked
to Aiken's caddy.
I tried every trick
in the book. He froze me out.
We didn't just get
frozen out, Brian.
They slapped us
with a countersuit
for slandering Marc.
We just made it
1,000 times worse.
Shit.
- Look, maybe we can still...
- I can't fucking believe it!
Katrina, it's just a case.
No, it's not just a case.
It's my senior partnership.
What?
But I thought Louis said...
I know what he said,
but there was a hitch.
This was the case
to put me over the top.
- Why didn't you tell me?
- Because it's my career
and my responsibility.
Katrina,
I'm not just the other name
on this lawsuit;
I'm your friend.
If senior partner's on the line
for you, it is for me too.
Now, we can still...
Not just a name on a lawsuit.
- That's it.
- What's it?
The attorney of record
on this suit isn't
the same attorney
Aiken took the deposition with.
He changed lawyers in
the middle of the case.
What are you getting at?
They sent back
the deposition last night
and the new guy signed it.
Brian, it's one thing
to have him handle
the slander case,
but to sign off
on a deposition.
Holy shit.
The first guy knew
Aiken was lying,
and he wouldn't sign it.
He wouldn't suborn perjury.
Katrina, we got him.
I know.
Okay.
We're going to get that tape.
We're gonna look
at his reaction
when Aiken says he's innocent.
We're gonna find out
their entire history together.
I don't care
if it takes all night.
This is fantastic.
I'm gonna go order that masala;
you're gonna get it all
over your face;
I'm not even gonna tell you
about it this time.
You better tell me about it
just like you better
get extra naan.
Triple supreme naan it is.
I'm just gonna go order it,
call my wife real quick
to tell her not to wait up,
and then you and I...
Wait, stop.
No.
No what?
You're not staying tonight.
I can handle this myself,
and I'm going to.
Katrina, what's going on?
Did I do something wrong?
You've done nothing wrong,
Brian.
But you've got a wife
and a baby,
and I'm not going
to keep you from them
anymore than I already have.
Katrina, I told you
if your partnership's
on the line,
my partnership's on the line.
I know, but I got this.
Go home.
You mind if I come in?
No.
I was just about
to come see you.
Well, before you tell me why,
I'd like to apologize.
You would?
Yes.
I realized
I'm too close to this.
And instead of hearing you,
I lashed out, and I'm sorry.
You realized?
I went to see Alex.
Well, that's funny,
because I wanted
to apologize too.
You wanted to apologize?
Donna, I told you
I wouldn't take action,
and I shouldn't have.
But I couldn't help myself.
because I care about
the kids this charity
is supposed to serve.
But you wouldn't know that,
because like you said,
I never tell anyone
the full story.
And the reason
I never tell the full story
is because I just don't trust...
People.
Pretty much.
Yeah.
Alex talked to you after
he talked to me, didn't he?
He did.
We might have to do something
about that guy.
We might.
But not before we do something
about this situation.
Because I'm not gonna
let them get away
with scamming children.
I'm with you on that.
Then let me ask.
You read people.
Are you absolutely sure
Peggy wasn't in on this,
because they could have
fired her even if she was.
I am 100% sure.
Then I know what to do.
I'm glad you decided
to come in.
You mind if I ask how
you got Louis to agree
to let me see you?
I don't,
but I would prefer to ask:
when Louis came in
and said you were losing
this McKernon Motors,
how did you feel?
You want to just
jump right in, huh?
Yes, I do.
Well, how do you think
I felt? I didn't like it.
Because you were losing
your oldest client?
Because Louis told me
there was nothing
I could do about it.
And then Donna came in
and said Joan was there,
and Louis couldn't even
take care of her.
- And it irritated you?
- It infuriated me.
- Why?
- Because he told me
that I couldn't have
what I wanted
and then he put
his own selfish interests
above the firm's.
Forgive me, Harvey,
but isn't that Louis'
historical concern about you?
This is different.
I think perhaps
it is different
because he is the one
doing it to you,
and more importantly,
what those
selfish interests are.
What are you getting at?
When you two were here,
you spent
quite a lot of time
on Louis having a baby.
So?
So would you ever want
to have a baby? Or a family?
I have a family,
and if you're gonna say
this has something to do
with my brother's divorce...
I didn't even know your
brother was getting a divorce.
Well, he is.
- That must be painful.
- Of course it's painful.
My family's falling apart,
and at the same time
I'm getting it rubbed
in my face
that Louis' family is growing.
Forgive me, Harvey,
but...
Louis did not rub anything
in your face.
No, he didn't.
But perhaps it feels that way
because for the first time,
Louis has something
in his life that you do not.
Jesus Christ, you're saying
I'm envious of Louis.
And what if you were?
I'd ask what in God's name
am I supposed to do with that?
Does is it occur to you
to share that with him?
No, even if I wanted to,
he's pissed off at me.
He would forgive you
in a moment.
And even if he did,
I'm afraid to...
To what, Harvey?
Louis makes space
for the people
in his life whom he loves.
He makes space for people
like Sheila and a baby,
but...
But what?
But once he has that baby,
he might not make space for me.
Where would you get
a notion like that,
that Louis wouldn't
have time for you?
Because they leave.
Everyone leaves:
Mike, Rachel, Jessica,
my sister-in-law.
Everyone.
Well, I can tell you
if you keep treating
Louis like this,
you may cause him
to leave yourself.
James Davenport?
I'm Donna Paulsen,
and this is my colleague
Samantha Wheeler.
The same Samantha Wheeler
that had a $5 million donation
yanked from us?
The Samantha Wheeler
who offered you a venue
for your next event
for a fraction of the one
you've been using,
and you said no.
Which means you cut a deal
with your current venue
where you overpay and they
kick back a percentage to you.
Specifically,
.3% of your annual budget.
- Get out of my office.
- I don't think so, James.
Because we may not have
had time to find proof,
but a reporter will.
Especially after we tell them
that you fired
an innocent woman
just because a potential donor
asked a few questions
about your books.
When you put it that way,
it sounds like
he did all this
to cover his guilty ass.
Maybe we should give that
to the "Journal."
That's a nice turn of phrase.
Thank you, Donna.
What do you want?
We want you to step down
and name
Peggy Davis
as your replacement.
- You can't be serious.
- You don't want to find out
how serious we are, James.
Because you're looking
at two pissed-off women
who know exactly what you did
and how to prove it.
You'll have my resignation
by tonight.
Good.
And don't look at me like that.
If it wouldn't mean
your charity
would go out of business,
you'd be spending
the next five years in prison.
Hey.
How'd it go?
We won.
Listen, about last night...
Brian, I didn't mean
to come off like...
You didn't come off
like anything.
I just wanted to thank you
for not making me stay.
- But I thought you wanted...
- I know. I wanted to help.
But Julie and I,
we had a great time.
Austin slept through the night,
and we actually stayed up
and watched
"The Breakfast Club."
What's that?
Uh, just Julie and my
favorite movie of all time.
- I've never heard of it.
- Oh, my God.
You've never even heard of it?
You have to see it.
I'm bringing you a copy.
Brian,
you don't have to do that.
I know I don't,
but that's what friends do.
Friends.
Yeah, friends.
That's what we said, right?
Yes, it is.
And thanks, I would love
to see it sometime.
Hey, you want to get
some lunch?
Sure.
I mean, that's also
what friends do, right?
Am I your first friend?
You know you're not.
Come on, let's go.
You get
that letter of resignation?
Right here.
And Peggy's job offer
is on its way.
- Look, Donna...
- Listen, Samantha...
Let me go first this time.
I was thinking
about how I don't trust people.
And I thought
maybe I should start.
And then I thought,
maybe I should start
by telling you
why I cared so much about this
charity in the first place.
Is this a rosé story
or a martini story?
Whiskey.
How about tonight?
That would be nice.
Meet you in the lobby
in half an hour?
You got it.
See you down there.
I'm glad I caught you in here
of all places.
Why's that?
Because we have
a lot of history here.
And it seems
like the right place
for me to make things right.
You must have gone
to see Stan.
I did.
Thank you for that.
Make things right.
Thanking me.
What went on in there?
Among other things,
he helped me realize
I care about you;
I value you;
and I was afraid of...
Losing me?
Which is why
you pushed me away.
Oh, my God.
You pulled a Litt.
Harvey, you became me.
Louis,
I wouldn't go that far.
Oh, no, you would.
And you did.
We are brothers
from another mother.
And if you don't say that
right now,
I'm gonna tell everyone
you're afraid of losing me.
- Louis.
- Right now.
Starting with Paul Porter.
We're brothers
from another mother.
I'm sorry, I couldn't...
could you repeat that?
- No, Louis, I couldn't.
- Why not?
Because I know
you're about to record it
on your Dictaphone.
And what if I am?
Because if you don't
say it again,
I'm gonna tell everyone
you're afraid of losing me.
And if you say that
one more time,
our friendship's over,
and I'm never looking back.
Because I suffered
a momentary weakness,
but let's not forget
who's who in this situation.
I'll never mention it again.
Now, put your hands
where I can see 'em.
- Why?
- Just do it.
What the hell
did you do that for?
Because, you and me
are going out tonight.
I'm gonna say
a lot of nice things to you,
and there isn't gonna be
any record of it.
I can live with that.
Wait a minute.
How long did it take for you
to come to that with Stan?
- About 25 minutes, why?
- I don't believe it.
You're even better at therapy
than I am.
Maybe I am.
But trust me.
Stan likes you better than me,
and he always will.
- You really think so?
- No, Louis, I don't.
Wait a minute.
Does this mean
I get to have Joan back?
You sure can.
And your first order
of business
is gonna be telling her
we filed suit
against a 16-year-old
that's gonna make her
look like shit.
What?
You really did that?
What can I tell you, Louis?
The fear of losing you
makes a man do crazy things.
Well, in that case,
after Sheila and I
are pregnant,
do you want to go mudding?
- No, Louis, I don't.
- Well, h...
== sync by elderman ==
@elder_man
www.tvsubtitles.net