Previously on "Suits"...
Get on the ground.
Wallet and phone.
You weren't there!
You don't know the shit
I went through!
The same thing that happened
to you happened to me.
Are you sure the two of us
working so closely together
is a good idea?
It might get complicated.
It's not fair that
my reputation
in this firm takes a hit
when you are the one--
- I was the one that what?
- Where have you been?
I've been looking
for you all morning.
Hey, if you must know,
I overslept.
I'd love to go out again,
Thomas.
- Is tonight too soon?
- Let me check my calendar.
- Yep, I'm free.
- I have an idea.
If we work together for a year
and it's successful,
you'll be
on the junior partner track.
That sounds like a plan.
- Harvey, this is Thomas.
- Kessler. We've met.
Here's another one. Oh.
Your grandmother did not
want to go to the beach
in Nice, but I insisted.
Oh, my God, Mom, you were hot.
Donna, please.
I was smokin' hot.
Well, if you got it, admit it.
Sweetie, I really appreciate
you indulging me.
It's always nice to look back
at this trip but...
it's just so much more fun
with you.
I'm not indulging you, Mom.
I love it, too.
Then what do you say
we make an album of our own.
- What do you mean?
- The last few years
have been tight,
but I've been saving up.
And you and I
are going to Paris
for two weeks,
right after you graduate.
- You're kidding.
- I am 100% not kidding.
Mom, this is amazing.
I wanna see it all.
Notre Dame, the Louvre,
the cafés.
Do you really think
we can do all that?
We can do anything you want
because I finally understand
why that trip
was so special
for my mom.
And now I get to have
all that with you.
Okay, just the way you like
it, vanilla with two splashes
of "why would anyone
want their coffee this sweet"?
You seem particularly happy
this morning.
- I am.
- Any reason?
Other than the fact that you
woke up
next to this 5"9 stack
of fantastic?
As a matter of fact, there is.
Um, do you remember
that meeting
I had to leave early
for the other day?
You mean the morning
after our first time
when you snuck out of here
like you robbed a bank?
You know, funny you should
say that, because...
I feel like I robbed a bank
this morning.
What do you mean?
Well, we've been negotiating
to expand our retail presence.
We were at an impasse, and now
we're full steam ahead.
- Thomas, that's fantastic.
- It is.
It's gonna take us
to a whole other level.
But the real reason I'm so
happy is that there isn't
anyone I'd rather share
this with than you.
There he is,
the man himself,
the Babe Ruth
of the legal profession.
Flatter me all you want,
Simon.
You got me over here at 8:00,
and I don't even like
to be up at 8:00,
so what do you got?
The answer to
our tenant problems.
I'm assuming you mean
Restoration
pulling out of the deal.
- I do.
I've invited someone else
to take their seat.
- Who's that?
- Thomas Kessler Furniture.
They're up and coming,
they're about to sign
a huge deal with my major
competitor, and I want them.
- You gotta be kidding me.
- Is there a problem?
Simon, aside from the fact
that we represent Kessler,
which is a conflict,
I can get
Restoration back to the table.
I don't want them
back at the table.
- But I thought we--
- Harvey, think about it.
They're a national chain,
they're flush with cash,
and we can only build
so many malls.
Which means
if we're gonna increase
our revenue going forward--
You need up and coming
tenants who will trade
a piece of the upside
for a break on rent.
Welcome to the conversation.
Okay, Simon.
Yet, I still feel
you're checking your swings,
so what's your concern?
No concern.
You want Kessler, you got 'em.
Louis, this is so much fun.
I'm so glad
we're finally doing this.
Of course, Sheila,
when I told you
that our baby
comes first, I meant it.
And speaking of coming first,
imagine our little love bug
rolling to the playground
in this bad boy.
- Wait, is this--
- Yup.
"Paternity Magazine"'s
top pick.
Yeah, and it's also $2,000.
Louis, can we really ask people
to buy this for us?
Sheila, let me explain
something to you.
All of our friends
are rich,
and as any rich person will
tell you,
gifts are the truest form
of love.
So in other words,
scan that mofo.
Scan the shit
out of that bad boy.
Hello?
- Louis Litt?
- Yeah, this is.
This is Detective Bukowski,
was your wallet stolen
recently?
Yeah, it was.
How could you possibly know--
We believe we may just have
arrested the man who stole it.
- Oh, my God.
- Would you be willing to
come down here
and identify him in a lineup?
Sir, I can assure you
he won't see you.
He won't even know who you are.
Yeah, I'll come right down.
Just let me know
where you're at.
Thanks.
♪ Suits 8x15 ♪
Stalking Horse
Original Air Date on February 20, 2019
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ I'll even eat a bean pie,
I don't mind ♪
♪ Me and Missy is so busy,
busy making money ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ All step back,
I'm 'bout to dance ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
♪ The greenback boogie ♪
All right,
bring 'em in.
As I said,
they won't be able to see us.
If you see the man who
mugged you, just let me know.
Get on the ground and don't
you fucking look at me.
Mr. Litt,
do you recognize anyone?
Number six.
Number six, step forward.
Are you sure?
We need you to be sure.
- Wallet and phone.
- It's him, I'm sure.
Good, we appreciate
the cooperation.
The DA's office will be
in touch about testifying.
Testifying? I thought
I just had to identify him.
But you also said
you were assaulted.
Unless you want to let him
plead to a misdemeanor,
you need to appear in court.
Yeah, of course.
Take the rest of 'em out.
- Alex, you got a second?
- Actually, Harvey,
I'm running a two-minute drill
right now, so no.
Well, I need you to take
a look at this anyway.
What is it?
Simon Lowe wants
Thomas Kessler
to be their anchor
in 20 new malls.
Well, I'm sorry to say,
that's my two-minute drill,
and I'm at the one-yard line
with another mall owner.
- So?
So I haven't known Thomas
long but I know he doesn't like
to deal in bad faith.
- This isn't bad faith, Alex.
He didn't even know
this deal was coming,
and he sure as hell didn't know
how good it would be.
- Good or not, it's a conflict.
- Take a look at the offer,
then tell me
he won't wave conflict.
Damn.
A 50% haircut on rent
for 10% of our gross?
These guys are serious.
Pretty sure it beats
whatever you got cooking.
- How'd you come up with this?
- I didn't.
- My client did.
- I don't believe it.
I've been busting my ass
for months on this
and your client comes to you
with this.
Shit just falls out of the sky
for you, doesn't it?
You don't wanna know what
high school was like for me.
No, sir,
I do not.
All right, I'll take it to him,
but we better get them
in a room fast
because Thomas isn't going
to pull out of his deal
without looking Simon
in the eye
and seeing he's for real.
You wanted to see me?
Yes, in fact,
I have a present for you.
Your first client.
I don't understand.
Brian, if we're going
to follow through
on you being promoted
and working on your own,
we need to do this.
Right?
You're right.
Who's the client?
Bespoke Handbags.
Their landlord found out
they use ammonia,
they never disclosed it,
and they're being kicked
out of their building.
- That's bullshit.
This is just a ploy because
they found a new tenant.
And what are you going
to do about it
because they have us
on a technicality
and they know it.
- I'm gonna figure out
who the new tenant is
and try to stop it.
Thus proving yourself worthy
of this client.
Except there are thousands
of potential tenants out there.
How am I gonna figure out
who it is?
That, good sir,
is your problem.
No, it isn't.
It's ours.
Brian, the whole point
of this with--
- Here me out.
Remember that algorithm
you used to determine
who should stay
and who should be fired?
Of course.
PATTIE.
Well, if you could
use it for that--
I can alter it for this.
Okay.
Though you realize
this still means
we're working together.
- With one key difference:
You're working for me,
and I don't tolerate slackers,
so have that shit ready
by 10:00 tomorrow.
I got a case to win.
- Donna.
- Harvey.
I wanna talk to you
about last night.
You mean LeBron's game winner
against the Nicks?
You know what I mean.
I wanna talk to you about me
seeing Thomas,
and the truth is,
I told Louis
and I meant to tell you, but--
Donna, you don't have
to tell me every time
you start seeing a client.
- That's the thing.
I don't just want to tell you
because he's a client.
I wanted to tell you
because,
even though it's really early
on, I--I really like him.
Donna, if you really
like him, I am happy for you.
You're never gonna believe
this, but--
I got a proposal for him
from Simon Lowe.
They want him to be
their home goods anchor.
Well, that's incredible,
but--
The other deal, I know.
I spoke to Alex about it
and he agreed,
this one's better,
and we set up a meeting
for them tonight.
Thank you,
Harvey.
I wish I could take credit
for it, but it wasn't my idea.
No, I mean,
thank you for understanding.
And as far as the deal goes,
credit or not,
Thomas's business means
everything to him
so I really appreciate it.
All right, I got a situation.
I need to talk to you about it.
What kind of situation?
That scum bag who mugged me?
They just arrested him.
They called me down to ID him,
but that wasn't enough.
Now they want me to get
on the stand and point
the finger at him.
- Louis, what are you saying?
- You want me to go with you?
- I'm saying I want you
to tell me
that it's okay not to go.
I'm sorry,
but I can't do that.
- Why the hell not?
- Because...
I get that you're scared, but
if you don't take the stand,
no amount of self defense
is gonna take that fear away.
The only thing that can
is confronting him.
You don't understand.
When I saw him, I was right
back in that alley.
Trust me,
no one gets that more than me.
But I promise, if you do this,
I will be with you
every step of the way.
Alex, this is Simon Lowe.
And of course, Simon?
Thomas Kessler.
I've been a fan of your work
for a long time.
I recognize that table.
I hope to have more just like
that anchoring my malls.
- Shall we?
- Mm-hmm.
Look, I won't lie,
I'm intrigued by your offer,
but you're asking me to back
out of a deal at the 11th hour,
and I need to know that I'm not
just a backup plan.
Well, then I won't lie
to you either.
If the other deal hadn't run
into trouble,
you wouldn't be here,
but it did,
and there were 15 companies
I could've gone to
that weren't about to close
a deal with someone else
but I chose you.
'Cause I believe in you.
Thomas, I don't take
your relationship
with our firm lightly,
so believe me when I tell you
this is a good offer
and I stand behind it.
Then gentlemen, I'd say
we have ourselves a deal,
With one stipulation: When
my client commits, he commits,
so we need to know you're gonna
follow through on this.
Well, Alex, we had a feeling
you'd say something like that,
which is why we're prepared
to issue a press release
tomorrow morning announcing
the whole thing.
You would do that even before
we ironed out the fine print?
Well, that stuffs
for the lawyers, huh?
We're businessmen.
And if you're who I think
you are
a handshake
is enough for me.
Let's try this again.
What happened that night?
He pulled a gun on me,
forced me into the alley,
then stole my wallet
and my phone.
Did he hurt you?
Yes,
the assailant hurt me.
Louis,
we have been over this.
Facts don't affect juries
the way feelings do.
You have to share
your pain with them.
- I can't.
- I know you think that, but--
You don't know, because
you've never had to let
someone see what he did to you.
How he made you helpless
and scared like a child.
Louis, have you ever asked
one of your clients
to hide their pain?
- Of course not.
- But this is different.
- The only difference is
now you're the client.
- Goddamnit, Samantha!
Don't you think I know that?
All right, that's enough.
Look at me.
If you don't put him away,
he will haunt you
for the rest of your life.
You are doing this so you won't
ever have to be afraid again.
So do not be afraid
of your emotions now.
When he pointed
the gun at me...
It was...
I had never been
more afraid in my life.
And then he forced me
into the alley.
And then he made me
get on the ground.
Then he pressed the gun
in the back of my head.
He demanded my wallet
and my phone.
But I only gave him my wallet
because my phone had
pictures of my fiancé on it.
So I...
I begged him to let me keep it.
I mean, there was $1,000
in the wallet.
Wasn't that enough?
But he said that he would say
when it was enough.
Then he kicked me.
All I could think about
was the woman I love
and the baby that we were
never gonna have
because I was gonna die
in that alley.
Mr. Litt, is the man
who did that to you
in this room right now?
Yeah,
he's sitting right there.
Thank you,
Mr. Litt.
Your cross.
We have no need to cross
Your Honor because everything
Mr. Litt
just said is irrelevant.
What?
Your honor, the date on the
warrant doesn't match the date
of the search therefore all
the evidence against my client
is inadmissible and I move
for charges to be dismissed.
What--wait,
but he can't do that.
- He's guilty.
- Mr. Litt, I'm sorry.
The search was illegal.
By order of the court,
the defendant is free to go.
Harvey, I gotta say,
that was an impressive display
last night.
Damn straight it was.
Listen, did you get
the paperwork
I sent over this morning?
- Yeah, I did.
I hate to waste
everyone's time,
but I won't be signing it.
Why the hell not?
Well, it turns out
Restoration
came back to the table.
When exactly did that happen?
About an hour ago.
Simon, I'm only
gonna ask you this once:
Was this whole thing designed
to get Restoration
back to the table?
It was designed to either
get them back
or to take a chance
on an up-and-comer.
Either way,
my malls don't sit empty.
Simon, you said
you were doing this deal.
You used me
to help sell him on it.
Then you shook his hand
and lied to his face.
I said what I needed to to
make a deal happen and I don't
need to justify myself
to my own goddamn lawyer.
Now, this is happening,
and I need Restoration
to think that the Thomas deal
is still on.
I know how negotiations work,
Simon.
And I know how privilege
works,
so if you tell anyone about
this, be it Thomas, or Alex,
or the Queen of England,
we'll be done.
All right, that should be
the last variable.
What's it say?
Hold on, it's calculating--
goddamnit.
It only narrowed the list
down to 800.
Well, that's a lot lower
than what we started with,
so maybe we can--
- What, get it down to 300?
What difference will it make?
We have less than a day.
Look, what do you
want me to say?
It was an idea, Katrina.
I didn't know the program
wouldn't work this time.
I know, Brian, I'm sorry.
I'm just...
Wait a second.
The program
didn't work this time,
but the program didn't work
last time either.
It said other people
were more valuable than you.
And while I love being
reminded of that
I don't see how that--
- Think about it.
PATTIE was wrong
because she didn't take
into account your intangibles.
I had to be convinced
to keep you.
You mean we need to convince
that property owner
that our client
is more valuable
than whoever they want
to replace us with.
Exactly.
Samantha, whatever it is--
I wanna talk about what
happened in court today.
Doesn't matter what happened
in court, because it's over.
I'm here because
it doesn't have to be.
You--
Are you--no,
I'm not breaking the law.
Louis,
he assaulted you.
You cannot let him
get away with it.
He did get away with it,
Samantha.
He walked away.
And now
I'm gonna do the same thing.
Don't you get it?
You can't do that.
- Not with him out there.
- Damnit, Samantha.
You don't think I know
how dangerous he is?
He fucking knows where I live.
I'm not gonna risk it.
Louis, he's a bully.
And bullies only have power
if you let them.
No, bullies only have power
because they have guns
and knives and nothing to lose,
but I do,
and the only reason that
criminal out there knows that
I have a family is 'cause I let
you convince me to do this.
Well, I'm not gonna make
that mistake again.
What I'm gonna do is
I'm gonna let it go
and I don't want to hear
another word about it.
Harvey, what's the story?
You guys sign that deal yet
because--
We can talk about the deal
in a minute, Alex.
I need to ask you something.
It's hypothetical, but--
What's going on?
You got two clients,
both in a deal together.
One bills seven figures,
the other five.
They both wave conflict,
then you find out the big one
was planning to screw over
the little one.
Son of a bitch.
This isn't hypothetical.
This Simon Lowe
and Thomas Kessler.
- Answer the question.
- You know the answer.
You stick with the bigger
fish, but it doesn't matter
who's a bigger client
because you can't
break privilege anyway.
- I know.
Then why the hell
are you telling me?
I'm telling you
because I don't like it
and we may not have to tell
Thomas but that doesn't mean
we can't do something about it.
And since I'm not supposed
to know about this
and you're not supposed to
undercut your client,
what are we supposed to do?
Look,
Simon will stick with Thomas
if Restoration falls out
again.
So we're gonna make
that happen.
Are you crazy?
In what world does that
not get back to Simon?
The world where I can get
someone to do it for us.
Well, if you're gonna do
that, what do you need me for?
The backup plan,
which is to get
Thomas's original landlord
to beat Simon's deal.
They won't even take my call.
Alex, one of us is gonna get
this thing done,
but we don't have much time,
so are you in or you out?
I can get to you any time.
No.
No!
I'm in.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah, I'm sure.
- Just tell me what I have to do.
- Nothing.
Consider the matter handled.
- Wha--how are you gonna--
- Louis,
just let me do what I do.
- No, I'm not gonna just
sit on the sidelines.
I wanna be a part of it.
I don't think
that's a good idea.
Samantha, I'm not gonna
live in fear
my whole life.
You said it yourself.
The only way that's gonna
happen is if I stand up to him.
Then be prepared
to testify again.
Because I have a feeling new
evidence is gonna come to light
that links him
to that mugging.
I'll be ready.
Damnit, I don't care
if your firm has conflict.
I need this.
Yeah? Well, I'll remember
that the next time
you come to me for a favor.
Harvey, do you have a second?
Of course, Donna.
What do you need?
Well, it's just, Thomas
is so excited about this deal.
I wanna take him out to
celebrate and I was wondering,
do you think that it's gonna
close by tonight
or by tomorrow night?
It won't be tonight.
We still need to get approval
from Simon's board.
But wouldn't the board
approve it
before approaching him?
- Well, they did in concept.
Now they just need
to approve the actual deal
which takes a beat.
I get it.
This is about Elaine Phillips.
I heard she's in Norway,
and you don't know when
she'll be back
and you don't want me
to have to keep
this from Thomas.
That's right.
You got me.
No, Harvey.
There is no Elaine Phillips.
And when I asked you
about this deal closing
you got a look on your face
and I want to know why.
We are not having
this conversation.
Yes, we are,
because I can't make sense
of why you're acting like this
other than Thomas's deal
is in trouble.
I'm not gonna tell you
what's going on.
And I'm not leaving
until you do,
and if I do leave,
I'm just going to call him
and tell him
that something's going on so--
Okay.
You know what...
All right,
you wanna know?
Simon was using Thomas
as a stalking horse.
- I don't believe this.
- Donna, we can fix it.
Fix it?
There is no fixing it.
Thomas isn't going to want to
be in business with Simon
when he finds out about this
no matter what you do.
And he's not going to
to find out about it
because if we tell him
we betrayed our other client.
- And what about this client?
- Tell you about this client.
I went to Alex
to get us out of this.
He's gonna try and get Thomas's
original mall owner
to sweeten the deal.
- What are you going to do?
I'm gonna try to get
Restoration to back out,
and either of these things
can work
but only
if we don't tell Thomas.
You are putting me
in a really shitty position.
No, Donna, Simon put us all
in a shitty position.
I'm busting my ass
to get us out of this.
I just need you to trust me.
You wanna tell me
what's going on
with you and Louis Litt?
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about
the fact I heard
about what happened in court
yesterday, and I know you.
You're not
about to let this lie.
So what if I'm not?
So I want you not to do
whatever it is I know
you're going to.
Look, if this is about
plausible deniability,
don't worry about it.
Consider yourself out of it.
It has nothing to do
with plau--
Samantha,
you cannot do what we did.
I'm telling you,
you'll regret it.
Bullshit.
- You didn't regret it.
- Yes, I did.
And since when is that?
Because the last time
we talked about it
you were right as rain.
Last time we talked
about it was eight years ago.
And you don't know
what happens over time
when you do something
like that.
He's hurting, Robert.
Louis is hurting.
You saw what he was like
when it happened.
You saw what I was like
when it happened to me.
So what am I supposed to do?
I want you to promise me
to find another way.
Donna,
I was just thinking about you.
I was just thinking about
you too, Mom.
Funny how that happens.
What's on your mind, honey?
Do you remember
my senior year
when we were gonna go
to Paris?
Of course I remember.
Why?
Well,
I have a decision to make.
One side is work and the other
side is someone I care about.
Actually, both sides involve
someone I care about.
I bet I can guess
who the work side involves.
But what does that
have to do with Paris?
Do you regret giving Dad
the money?
No, I don't.
Even though
it didn't work out?
Well,
how could I have known that?
Because dad
let you down before.
Donna, your father
has never let me down.
Not in the ways that matter.
What do you mean?
Your father is the kindest,
gentlest,
most loving man
I have ever met,
and if I hadn't shown
faith in him,
it would have eaten away at him
for the rest of his life.
So...
if you had it all
to do over again,
would you make the same choice?
I can't tell you that,
but what I do regret
is we never took that trip.
So go with your gut
but don't let
the once in a lifetime
chances pass you by.
Hey, Mom.
What do you say
we go to Paris next year?
I say yes.
Mr. Barrow, this isn't
about amounts of ammonia
so small they're a technical
violation of our lease.
This is about you having
another tenant
willing to pay more.
Who I may or may not have
doesn't matter.
It should, because we're
willing to offer you
something they're not.
10% equity in the company.
A fledgling company
with unproven revenue.
No, Morgan,
they're more than that.
You see,
when you look at our client
you see a naive, young,
entrepreneur and not much else.
And on paper
that's exactly what she is.
But sometimes
who someone is on paper
isn't who they are at all.
My client may be young,
but she's brilliant,
and hard working,
and most importantly,
passionate.
That's why I'm proud
to work with her
and why if you get in
on the ground floor right now
you won't need to worry about
leases or any of that anymore,
because you'll be on an island
somewhere sipping piña coladas
paid for by the brilliant
decision you made today.
The only thing I'd be paying
for is some snake oil
and a silver tongue
because that's the biggest load
of sappy bullshit--
- Shut your mouth.
This man is
defending his client's honor.
He's doing it by offering you
something
you don't even deserve
and I've had it.
- Katrina.
- You think I don't know
who your mysterious
other tenant is?
I do.
And if a food distribution
company rents space
that's been exposed to
significant amounts of ammonia
without you disclosing it,
you'll go to prison.
You can't do this.
Yes, we can,
you piece of shit.
In fact,
that offer just went away.
So keep us in or kick us out
but your next tenant
isn't going to be
the goddamn one
you had in mind.
I've never seen you
like that.
Where did that come from?
It came from knowing
this is your first client,
and I wasn't going
to let them beat you.
Just like you've done
for me countless times.
But how did you even know
what company it was?
I didn't.
But 50%
of PADDIE's predictions
were food companies,
so I bluffed.
If it had turned out
they made clocks
we would have been
in big trouble.
What?
You continue to surprise me.
Because I never saw you
as someone
who'd take a chance
on a 50/50 bet.
I wouldn't have
before I met you.
Well, then I guess
I've made you a better lawyer.
I meant in my mind
it was 50/50
if keeping you on
was going to work out.
I don't believe it.
You're gambling,
you're making jokes,
- Who are you?
- Well, I'll tell you who I am.
I am the person
who is proud
to officially give you
your first solo client.
Thanks, Katrina.
I really appreciate it.
I can't wait to go home
and share the news.
What's going on?
Did you take care of it?
Change of plans.
What do you mean
change of plans?
I didn't even know what the
plan was in the first place.
Yes, you did.
I was gonna do something
illegal
and now I'm not gonna
do that anymore.
What's the new plan.
Are you talking
about leveraging--
Yes, I am.
- Samantha, this is a child.
- I know what it is.
Then you of all people,
coming from where you
come from, should know that
doing this could ruin her life.
Only if it doesn't work.
Which is why
we'll make it work.
- No, we're not.
- Then I'll do it alone.
I don't think you heard me.
You said you don't
want to live in fear.
No, I said
I wanna go after him.
This is going after him.
Goddamn it, it's his family!
It's a family.
I know it is,
Louis.
But it's your family, too.
So what do you wanna do?
Look, all I'm saying is,
would it be so terrible
if Thomas Kessler became
the official furniture
of the United Nations?
I'm sorry, am I going on too
much about this expansion?
Because we can go out
right now,
don't have to talk
about it at all.
No, no, no, it's not that.
It's just--
I haven't been feeling well.
Yeah, you know, I had that
same feeling earlier today.
How so?
My original mall owner
called me.
He wants me back.
He even offered a much better
deal than Simon.
Thomas, that's fantastic.
Why would that make you
feel bad?
Because I already have a deal
in place with Simon Lowe.
It was hard to tell him
you're backing out?
No, it was hard to tell Glen
that I was passing.
What?
- You passed on a better deal?
- Not formally,
but when I told him
Glen gave me up
until 10:00 tomorrow
to decide and...
Look, I'll take it
as a courtesy
but I really don't need to.
I shook Simon's hand.
He's my guy.
- What?
- Nothing.
It's one of the things
that I admire about you.
You're a man of your word.
But speaking of not feeling
well, I think I'm just gonna
go get some ginger ale.
Oh, Donna, come on.
Don't be silly.
- Let me get it for you.
- No, no, no, actually,
I think I need some fresh air.
You stay here, I'm gonna be
back in ten minutes.
- Sure?
- I'm sure.
- Hello?
- What's going on
with getting
Restoration to back out?
Thomas didn't tell you?
Alex got his original landlord
to crush Simon's offer.
He did tell me, Harvey,
and he also told me
that he's not taking it,
and it disappears tomorrow.
Shit.
Look, we can still fix it.
How the hell
are we going to fix it?
I can get Restoration
to back out.
And what if you don't?
Because Thomas is going to lose
his expansion and I'm not
gonna let that happen.
Neither am I, Donna.
This thing isn't over.
I just need you to have faith.
I'll text you in the morning
but please,
don't do anything
until you hear from me.
Okay, Harvey.
I'll wait to hear from you.
What are you doing here?
We're here because we know
the mother of your child
is the recipient of Section 8
housing benefits
and she's in danger
of losing them.
- What are you talking about?
- That kind of assistance
can't go to someone
with a criminal history.
She doesn't have
a criminal history.
- But you do.
- I don't live there.
Oh, really, 'cause you said
you did when you got arrested.
Also have a gas bill
with your name on it.
If we go to the housing
authority with this
you'll lose your daughter.
- Bullshit.
No, not bullshit, Maurice.
You're getting evicted.
You think Family Services
is gonna
let your little girl
be homeless?
What do you want from me?
Your money back?
'Cause that ain't happening.
What I want is for you
to turn yourself in
and admit what you did.
You think that's
what's happening here?
I know that's what's
happening here.
Nah, you ain't doing that.
Why do you think I picked you?
I could'a taken ten people
into that alley,
but the second I saw you
I knew you were my guy.
You stupid motherfucker.
When you held that gun
to my head,
you told me not
to look at you
and I was afraid.
Do I seem afraid now?
'Cause only one person's
making a phone call tonight.
You're turning yourself in
or I'm calling
the Housing Authority.
No way you put a woman
and child on the street.
I'm not putting her there,
Mo.
You are.
Watch.
Nah, you ain't doing that.
I know where you live.
You've reached the
New York Housing Authority.
Hi, Housing Authority,
I'd like to report
a Section 8 violation.
- Put the phone down.
Well, there's a woman who's
living with a criminal
and she intentionally is
leaving his name off the lease.
- I said put it down.
- You can call Family Services
because the woman's name--
- You mother--
What's it gonna be?
'Cause in another two seconds
they'll have your name.
Okay, I'll make the call.
Well, no,
I just made it for you.
- 911. Say hi.
- 911, what's your emergency?
- I want to report a crime.
- Sir, what did you witness?
I ain't a witness.
I'm the one who did it.
Am I interrupting?
No, I was just reading.
Tennessee Williams.
I know it might cost a little
more,
but if anyone is doing one of
his plays when we're in Paris--
Actually, honey, that's what
I wanted to talk to you about.
- Paris.
- What about it?
Your dad has a building
he wants to buy,
and in order to secure
the loan we're gonna ha--
He needs our Paris money.
Honey, it doesn't mean
we're not gonna go,
it just means we can't go
this year.
But you saved for so long,
and if you use
the money for this--
It--it's not like that.
In two years we're gonna have
our money back, plus more,
and then we're gonna be able
to go for a month,
instead of two weeks.
You're not sure
this is gonna work, are you?
I forgot you can do that.
Donna, I promise you,
we are going to Paris.
I understand.
Another year.
You know, I gotta say,
I may be coming around
to your way
of making coffee after all.
Thomas, Simon Lowe was using
you as a stalking horse.
The deal you made was
a ploy to get
Restoration Hardware
to the table.
You're their backup plan.
That's why your deal
hasn't closed yet.
And why are you the one telling
me this and not my lawyer?
'Cause Alex
is trying to fix it,
and so is Harvey but I don't
know that they're going to be
able to fix it and you said
that your other offer expires
this morning and I don't wanna
be responsible.
Donna, you are not
responsible for anything, okay?
So what are you going to do?
I'll tell you what
I'm not gonna do.
Let the company that I spent
my life nurturing
get taken out at the knees
just when
it's starting to walk.
Thomas, I didn't see we had
a meeting on the books.
We didn't, but don't
worry, this won't take long.
I'm going with Glen.
Thomas,
that's great.
I'll get on it right away.
Well, listen,
first things first,
I wanna issue a press release
this morning.
I don't want the world to think
that we're going with Pierpont.
- Listen--
- Unless there's some reason
why you wouldn't want me
to announce the fact
that I'm pulling
out of the deal.
- You know?
- You're damn right I know.
Donna told me.
And she wouldn't have had to
if you hadn't
kept this from me.
I kept it from you because
I shouldn't have even known.
And you got that deal from Glen
because I made it happen.
What you did was leverage him
into a better deal
based on Pierpont's offer
which is something
I never would have
even wanted.
Which is why I'm taking Glen's
offer at the original rate
and I'm putting out
an announcement about it.
Thomas, you do that,
it screws over the guy
who told us about this
in the first place.
I'm sorry, Alex.
This is my business
and my reputation.
I'm putting out a message out
there that I'm not going to
act in bad faith
or be treated in bad faith.
So either you put out
that press release
or I'm gonna do it myself.
Brian, how are you
this bright morning?
I'm okay, Katrina,
but there's something
I have to tell you.
By all means,
go right ahead.
Last night I was having
dinner with Julie
and I started telling her
about us and the case
and what we did for Bespoke.
Where are you going
with this?
The whole time I was talking
I wasn't talking about the case
or the client,
I was talking about you.
And Julie said
you sound so great,
we should have you over
for dinner,
and then she saw
a look on my face.
Brian.
She asked if anything
had ever happened between us.
- And I said no.
- And nothing ever will.
But even if it doesn't,
I can't feel this way
about someone who isn't Julie.
Brian,
what are you saying?
I can't work here anymore.
What?
- No, you can't--
- I have to.
Then I'll go to Louis
right now
and you can be someone
else's associate.
Stop.
Brian, please don't do this.
It's gonna be okay.
I promise.
No, it's not.
But I respect your decision.
Good-bye, Katrina.
Harvey, where the hell
have you been?
I've been texting you
for two hours.
Alex, I know we're running
out of time,
but I think I've got a way
to get Restoration
to drop out.
- It's too late for that.
Your problem's going to be
keeping Restoration in.
What are you talking about?
Donna told Thomas everything.
That's--no.
- How could she do that?
- I don't know,
but what I do know is he
dropped out and he's taking out
a full paid ad
in the journal to say it.
Fuck. All right.
Right now, I gotta call Simon
and tell him to close
that Restoration deal
as soon as possible.
- It's too late for that.
They called and demanded a 30%
reduction or they're gone.
Look, I know it's a setback,
but Thomas isn't the only
stalking horse out there.
I can find you--
You're not gonna find me
anything until you can tell me
you're not behind this.
Simon,
I didn't tell Thomas a thing.
And you're telling me
he didn't either, when the two
of you are just standing here
talking about my deal?
I don't even know
what you're talking about.
All I know if my client dropped
out and I was doing
your attorney a solid
by informing him.
Bullshit.
Someone let Thomas know,
and since you're the only
person with the full story,
it had to be you.
And yet here you are,
lying right to my face.
- Simon.
- Save it, Harvey.
You're fired.
What the hell did you do?
I did what I said
I was gonna do.
You said you were gonna find
another way.
I did find another way.
Bullshit.
A man up and confesses
to a crime?
You blackmailed him.
No, I used something he did
to get him to confess
to something else he did.
- That is not blackmail.
- It's messing with shit
you don't have business
messing with.
It has unintended consequences.
Robert, I've had about enough
of your
unintended consequences
bullshit.
So either tell me
what you are talking about
or shut the fuck up
Because Louis didn't get
the wrong guy
and neither did you and I.
And don't you tell me we did.
Don't you see,
it's not about the wrong man.
It's about taking matters
into your own hands
and what happens
when you do that.
You know, Robert,
I just don't get it.
Louis is safe now.
How can you
not see that as a good thing?
I know it's a good thing
for Louis, Samantha.
What I'm afraid of is,
it's gonna become
a bad thing for you.
Louis, can I talk to you
for a second?
Of course, Brian, but if this
is about Bespoke Handbags,
I already approved you
as our lead council.
Actually,
that is why I'm here.
I can't be
their lead council.
Yes, you can, Brian.
Because you deserve them,
which is why I want you
to take them with you.
But before I let you go,
I wanna know if this is about
what's been going on between
you and Katrina.
- What--how could you--
- I suspected a few weeks ago
and then she told me.
- Then all I can say is
it's about doing what I have
to, to protect my family.
And I say I want you to take
Bespoke with you
because you've earned them.
- I don't know what to say.
You don't have to say
anything.
Because as big
as this city is, Brian?
It is a very small world.
We're gonna see you
in court some day,
and when we do--
- I won't go easy on you.
- Good man.
- Are you sure about all this?
Come on, Brian.
You're doing this
for your family.
Trust me,
no one understands
sacrificing for their family
more than me.
I'm proud of you.
Whatever it is,
I don't want to hear it,
so you can turn around.
- Harvey.
Donna, Simon fired me.
as he had every right to do
because I trusted you
to keep your mouth shut
and you didn't.
- Because I couldn't.
- What the hell does that mean?
It means I wasn't gonna
let someone I care about
get screwed when I had
the power to stop it.
In other words,
you chose him over the firm.
- Yeah, I did.
I'm not gonna feel bad about it
because I always put
the firm first whether it is
Mike's secret,
or Coastal Motors,
or a thousand other things.
Then don't feel bad about it,
Donna,
but get out of my office.
Okay, I see what this is.
I see what
you're really upset about.
I'm upset
because I lost a client.
No, you are upset because
I chose Thomas over you.
- Is that what you think?
- Yeah, it is.
Then you don't know anything,
because the only reason
I was breaking my back to save
his deal is because I know
how much he means to you.
If it was anyone else,
I never would have told you
or Alex in the first place.
Then what are you
so mad about?
Because you didn't give me
a chance
to fix it
when you said you would.
You lost faith in me.
For all the time
that we have been together,
that has never happened.
Harvey, if there's anyone
in the world
I have faith in
it's you.
But the clock was striking
midnight and I had to make
a choice
and it is just a client.
Can't you understand that?
Am I interrupting?
What are you doing here,
Daniel?
I'm here because Simon Lowe
just hired me
as outside council
for Pierpont Malls.
All the lawyers in the world
and he just happened
to call you?
No, Donna, I called him,
and when I offered my services
free of charge,
he gladly accepted.
And what services
would those be?
Embezzling?
Extortion?
Suing this firm on behalf
of my new client.
You're a glutton
for punishment, Daniel.
- You know that, right?
- Talk tough all you want,
but you broke privilege
and now I'm gonna make you pay.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
www.tvsubtitles.net